<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 24px;">Hair Salon</span>
        </p>
        <p>This setup is for hair salons providing hair-related services such as hair cutting, brushing, coloring, hair and scalp treatments, beard and mustache shaping.</p>
        <p>A typical flow involves a client visiting the hair salon’s website to book an appointment. He selects from a variety of services:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>a simple brushing (30 minutes)</li>
            <li>an haircut  &amp;amp; a brushing (1 hour)</li>
            <li>a color, an haircut  &amp;amp; a brushing (3 hours)</li>
        </ul>
        <p> &amp; He then selects his preferred hairdresser according to the availability. &amp; </p>
        <p>
            During the service execution and depending on the client's needs and preferences, additional services such as conditioning, scalp massages, or other treatments may be offered. Those will be accounted for during the payment process
            using Point Of Sales (POS). Once the customer is ready to check out, the salon can also sell him haircare and styling products.
        </p>
        <p>The salon also offers a loyalty program to reward loyal customers. &amp; </p>
        <div class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc" data-oe-protected="true">
            <div class="o_knowledge_toc_content">
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">
                    Business Flows
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">
                    Flow 1: Website  &amp;gt; Appointment &amp; 
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2">
                    Website: Request an appointment
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2">
                    Appointment: Confirm Check-in
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">
                    Flow 2: POS
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="5" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2">
                    Customer check out
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="6" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2">
                    Loyalty program
                </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="7" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2">
                    Add additional services or products after the visit
                </a>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Business Flows</h1>
        <h2>Flow 1: Website  &amp;gt; Appointment &amp; </h2>
        <hr />
        <h3>Website: Request an appointment</h3>
        <p>From the website: &amp; </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Go to the Appointment menu</li>
            <li>Select the service you want</li>
            <li>Pick the hairdresser you wish to meet</li>
            <li>Schedule your visit by leaving your contact details</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This will create an appointment in the hairdresser calendar. The customer contact details are automatically added. &amp; </p>
        <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">Note: If the customer wishes to, he can reschedule or cancel his appointment later on. &amp; </blockquote>
        <h3>Appointment: Confirm Check-in</h3>
        <p>From the appointment app, manage easily the next appointments planned by going to Staff Schedule. &amp; </p>
        <p>Once the customer arrives in the Salon, click on his appointment then on "Confirm Check-in". It greens the appointment. If the appointment is not confirmed, the appointment becomes red once the time has passed.</p>
        <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
            Note: You can also edit a planned appointment. From Staff Schedule, click on the relevant appointment then click on Edit. You can then modify the attendees, date, length, appointment type or simply delete it. Attendees will be
            informed by email. &amp; 
        </blockquote>
        <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">You can also create an appointment yourself by clicking on the + icon appearing while hovering a time slot.</blockquote>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Flow 2: POS</h2>
        <hr />
        <h3>Customer check out</h3>
        <p>Once the service has been executed, it's time for the customer to checkout and pay for it. &amp; </p>
        <p>From Point Of Sale (POS), open a new session and select the product variant that were used. &amp; </p>
        <p>Example: &amp; </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Haircut (Short Hair)</li>
            <li>Brushing (Short Hair)</li>
        </ul>
        <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
            Note: Using products variants feature, you can give a single product (example: an haircut) different characteristics (hair length). On the product page, go to Attributes  &amp;amp; Variants tab and specify the Attribute (Hair length) and
            the values it can take (short or long). By clicking on Configure, specify the extra price for each value.
        </blockquote>
        <h3>Loyalty program</h3>
        <p>In your salon, you use a loyalty program. It helps with &amp; </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Retaining clients by rewarding their repeated visits</li>
            <li>Boosting your revenue by encouraging clients to try more services and purchase products.</li>
            <li>Setting apart from competitors and attracting both new and existing clients.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>You offer a 20€ discount after 5 visits of 50€. In POS:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Add the customer to your order in POS by clicking on "Customer".</li>
            <li>If the order is above 50€, the points are automatically added to the customer’s account. After 5 visits, 20€ will be automatically discounted after clicking on Reward. &amp; </li>
            <li>In our example, select the customer 4 who has gained 5 points already and click on Reward.</li>
        </ul>
        <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
            Note: You can create and configure several loyalty programs by going to POS  &amp;gt; Products  &amp;gt; Discount  &amp;amp; Loyalty. The setting needs to be activated beforehand.
        </blockquote>
        <h3>Add additional services or products after the visit</h3>
        <p>During the visit, additional services were offered: a scalp treatment and some hair care. Add it to the order. &amp; </p>
        <p>The customer wishes to buy the shampoo that you used. Add the shampoo bottle to the order as well. &amp; </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Click on Payment to confirm the order. &amp; </li>
            <li>Select the payment method.</li>
            <li>Click on Validate.</li>
            <li>You can print the receipt, email it to your customer, create an invoice or start a new order.</li>
        </ul>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Hair Salon</field>
        <field name="sequence">4</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
