<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="crm_lead_2" model="crm.lead">
    <field name="name">Jessica Martinez's Marriage</field>
    <field name="partner_id" ref="res_partner_25"/>
    <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
    <field name="team_id" ref="sales_team.team_sales_department"/>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[
      <div data-oe-version="1.1"><strong>HINTS : </strong></div>
      <ul>
          <li>Click the cogwheel icon, then "Request Signature" to send out a contract template to the customer</li>
          <li>Attach tags to opportunities to easily categorize and sort them</li>
          <li>Set up activities in the chatter for follow-ups</li>
          <li>Use the "<strong>Meetings</strong>" smart button to set up a meeting with the client</li>
          <li>Get an overview of all your quotations with the "<strong>Quotations</strong>" smart button</li>
      </ul>
    ]]></field>
    <field name="priority">2</field>
    <field name="stage_id" ref="crm.stage_lead3"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('crm_tag_2'), ref('crm_tag_3')])]"/>
    <field name="expected_revenue">18500.0</field>
  </record>
  <record id="crm_lead_3" model="crm.lead">
    <field name="name">Sarah Davis's Marriage</field>
    <field name="partner_id" ref="res_partner_29"/>
    <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
    <field name="team_id" ref="sales_team.team_sales_department"/>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[
      <div data-oe-version="1.1"><strong>Hints : </strong></div>
        <ul>
            <li>You can install the <strong>Appointments app + Website app </strong>to let customers book consultation appointments</li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Activities to plan follow-ups and keep track of next steps</strong></li>
        </ul>
      <div><br /></div>
    ]]></field>
    <field name="stage_id" ref="crm.stage_lead1"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('crm_tag_2'), ref('crm_tag_3')])]"/>
    <field name="expected_revenue">18500.0</field>
  </record>
  <record id="crm_lead_1" model="crm.lead">
    <field name="name">John Smith's Marriage</field>
    <field name="partner_id" ref="res_partner_26"/>
    <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
    <field name="team_id" ref="sales_team.team_sales_department"/>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[
      <div data-oe-version="1.0">Subject: Inquiry About Full-Service Wedding Planning</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>Dear WeddingCompany</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          I hope this message finds you well. My name is John, and I am reaching out to inquire about your full-service wedding planning offerings. My fiancée and I are in the early stages of planning our wedding, and we are looking for a
          professional team to help us create a memorable and seamless experience.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          We are envisioning a wedding that reflects our personalities and love story, and we would appreciate your expertise in bringing our vision to life. Here are some details about our wedding that we hope will help you understand our needs:
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          1. <strong>Date and Location</strong>: We are considering a wedding date in [insert month and year], and we are looking at venues in [insert preferred location or city]. We would love your recommendations for venues that can accommodate
          our guest list.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>2. <strong>Guest Count</strong>: We anticipate inviting around [insert number] guests, and we want to ensure that the venue can comfortably accommodate everyone.</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          3. <strong>Theme and Style</strong>: We are leaning towards a [insert theme, e.g., rustic, elegant, modern, etc.] theme, with a color palette of [insert colors]. We would love your input on how to best execute this vision through decor,
          floral arrangements, and overall ambiance.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>4. <strong>Budget</strong>: Our budget for the wedding is approximately [insert budget range]. We would appreciate your guidance on how to allocate our budget effectively across different aspects of the wedding.</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          5. <strong>Services Needed</strong>: We are interested in a comprehensive package that includes venue selection, vendor coordination (catering, photography, entertainment, etc.), timeline management, and day-of coordination. If you
          offer additional services such as design and decor, please let us know.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          6. <strong>Special Considerations</strong>: We have a few special requests, including [insert any specific requests, such as dietary restrictions, cultural traditions, etc.]. We would like to ensure that these are thoughtfully
          incorporated into our wedding plans.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>
          We would love to schedule a consultation to discuss our vision in more detail and learn more about your services, including pricing and availability. Please let us know your available times for a meeting, either in person or virtually.
      </div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>Thank you for your time, and we look forward to hearing from you soon!</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>Best regards,</div>
      <div><br /></div>
      <div>John [Last Name]</div>
      <div>[Contact Information]</div>
      <div>[Optional: Wedding Date]</div>
    ]]></field>
    <field name="stage_id" ref="crm.stage_lead2"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('crm_tag_1')])]"/>
    <field name="expected_revenue">22500.0</field>
  </record>
</odoo>
