<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">HVAC Services</field>
        <field name="icon">🧊</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="last_edition_uid" ref="base.user_admin"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0" data-last-history-steps="1993687538069157">HVAC Services</h1><p>Hello there!</p><p>You just installed the Odoo for HVAC Services package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your bar efficiently.</p><p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Demo - Use Case (In the next Knowledge Article)</p></div></div><div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div><p><br></p><h1><strong>Basics</strong></h1><hr><p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p><ul><li>Use the <strong>Sales App</strong>&nbsp;to record any&nbsp;new ordering.</li><li>The&nbsp;<strong>Project App</strong>&nbsp;and <strong>Field Service App</strong> will ensure a great follow up of every order and help you plan, execute and monitor installations, maintenance and repairs.</li><li>Manage your stock thanks to<strong> Inventory App</strong> and <strong>Purchase App</strong>.</li><li>Easily find installed devices from the <strong>Contact&nbsp;App</strong>&nbsp;thanks to warranty module.</li><li>Monitor refrigerant consumption and waste from the <strong>Field Service&nbsp;App</strong>.</li></ul><p><br></p><h1><strong>Use case</strong></h1><hr><p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products, sale orders and more.</p><p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p><p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Bar &amp; Pub package and check the related box</p></div></div><p><br></p><h3>📜 Managing&nbsp;orders</h3><hr><p>From the <strong>Sales App</strong>, you can manage your orders.</p><h5>Installation</h5><ul><li>You are ready to sign&nbsp;your first customers? To do so, open the Sales App, create a new order and the customer.</li><li>Fill in the form by creating or selecting a customer contact.</li><li>Select a quotation template to save time for an installation.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Save time preparing the quotation templates which correspond to your frequent segments!</p>
            </div>
        </div><ul><li>Send your quotation for online signature.</li><li>Confirm the order to close your deal and then create and confirm the invoice to bill your customer.</li></ul><h5>Maintenance</h5><ul><li>Create anew sale order but this time select the Maintenance quotation template.</li><li>Select your customer and then add the serials of devices to be maintained.</li><li>Send and confirm the order for the maintenance to be running.</li></ul><p><a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/18.0/applications/sales/sales.html">🎓&nbsp;Sales</a></p><p><br></p><h3>📅 Planning and execute services&nbsp;</h3><hr><p>The <strong>Field Service&nbsp;App</strong>&nbsp;is the place to plan and follow up work to be done on customer sites.</p><h5>Planning tasks</h5><ul><li>Open the Field Service App and navigate to the To Schedule Tasks from the All Tasks menu.</li><li>Define the Planned Date and Assignee for those tasks.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Note that maintenance tasks are defined as recurrent every year.<br>This means that once done, next year, a new task will be created automaically for you to plan!</p>
            </div>
        </div><ul><li>You can open the Planning by User to appreciate the planned tasks for the coming weeks.</li><li>The map&nbsp;of interventions is as well available from the My Tasks menu, by default today's ones.</li></ul><h5>Executing tasks</h5><p>Now Mike and Tom have some heavy duties as technicians...</p><ul><li>They will open their tasks of the day to work on it from the Field Service App.</li><li>First they'll start the task which trigger a time counter.</li><li>Then the worksheet can be filled in while performing the work.</li><li>If working on some products other serialized products, they can add them in the Lots/Serial Numbers tab, so that this task would be part of the history of those devices as well.&nbsp;</li><li>When consuming products during interventions, they can add it as well to the task from the Products smart button.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Note that if the Task field Under Warranty is checked, neither the time spent on this task nor the products would be charged to your customer.</p>
            </div>
        </div><ul><li>Last but not least, they will confirm the delivery of the device, validating the delivery to customer from the smart button at the top of the screen.</li><li>When all is done, the task can be marked as done, which stops the time counter and fill in a timesheet input.&nbsp;<br>Alternatively to the time counter, they could directly create a new timesheet input in the Timesheet tab.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">📱</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is supported on mobile as well!<br>Make sure your technicians <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/18.0/administration/mobile.html">install the Odoo Progressive Web App</a> to access and manage their tasks when on customer's site.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h5>Billing repair tasks</h5><p>You can now see that the task is done. In the case of a repair, the time spent and consumed products can be billed to your customer.</p><ul><li>Open the sale order for this repair, from the smart button at the top of the task.</li><li>Create an&nbsp;invoice, which will expense the reported timesheet inputs and products added.</li><li>Check&nbsp;the invoice and then confirm it for payment.</li></ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/18.0/applications/services/field_service.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓&nbsp;Field Service</a></p><p><br></p><h3>📦 Managing inventory and purchases&nbsp;</h3><hr><p>Managing your stock and resupply to never get out of stock happens in the <strong>Inventory App</strong>, while the<strong> Purchase App</strong> focuses on transactions with your suppliers.</p><h5>Replenishment rules</h5><p>For most products, you might want to have at all time some available.</p><ul><li>Open the Replenishment from Operations menu in the Inventory App.</li><li>See that replenishment rules are defined for some products, some are under an Auto trigger and some other are under a manual trigger.</li><li>For products which become low on stock and below the rule minimum, you can order some in a click.<br>This creates a purchase order with the to order quantity with your best supplier<br>Order some AC to prevent running out!</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Auto trigger for replenishment rule runs once a day and automatically creates a purchase order with appropriate quantities that you only have to confirm.<br>This helps you not even to have to wonder whether to order or not those to keep your business running.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h5>Manual purchase orders</h5><p>Other products such as cleaner product might not be tracked and would be ordered when getting out of stock.</p><ul><li>Open the Purchase App, where 2 new orders are in request for quotation stage.<br>One comes from the auto replenishment rules and the other from your order request.<br>There are two since you don't expect those products from the same supplier.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Define for each product the list of potential supplier in the Purchase tab to leverage the replenishment rules.</p>
            </div>
        </div><ul><li class="oe-nested"><ul><li>Open the Third company purchase order and add a line for consumable products when you need, the Com Koil Cleaner in this case. Then confirm your purchase order and expect the delivery shortly!</li><li>Open now the Fourth company order and confirm it as well.</li></ul></li></ul><h5>Receiving deliveries</h5><p>Your supplier deliveries&nbsp;are here, it's time to validate them!</p><ul><li>Open the open Receipts from the Inventory App Overview.<br>Since you made two orders, you expect two receipts.</li><li class="oe-nested"><ul><li>Open the Third Company order.<br>If everything matches, validate the order!</li><li>Open now the Fourth Company order.<br>Since those products come with serials, you need to input them. Click on the Details button for each line and fill in the serial numbers.<br>Once done, you can validate the order.</li></ul></li></ul><p>Your stock is now at its best!</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To save time and prevent typo mistake when inputing the serial number, you can install and leverage the <strong>Barcode App</strong>!</p>
            </div>
        </div><p><a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/18.0/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html">🎓&nbsp;Inventory</a>&nbsp;<a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/18.0/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase.html">🎓&nbsp;Purchase</a></p><p><br></p><h3>🔎&nbsp;Finding customer devices and their history&nbsp;</h3><hr><p>Finding in a sec the devices at a customer location and accessing their operation history is paramount for your business. You can keep track of this at all time from the <strong>Contact App</strong> with relationships with <strong>Field Service App</strong>.</p><p>A customer call you for an incident on a device?</p><ul><li>Open the Contact App and find your customer, Jessica Martinez in this case.</li><li>Open her Lots/Serial Numbers from the smart buttons at the top of the screen.</li><li>In the case of private customers, they might not have many devices like in Jessica's case.<br>But if needed, you could leverage the search bar at the top!</li><li>Note that the first delivery date of this device to your customer is available for you to know whether or not is still is under warranty.</li><li>A maintenance indicator&nbsp;is here to help you know at first sight whether this device is under ongoing maintenance contract or not.</li><li>Open the serial to access its details information:</li><li class="oe-nested"><ul><li>The Transfers lists you the deliveries of the device.</li><li>The Sales links the sale order for this device.</li><li>The Maintenance's&nbsp;links the sale order for Subscriptions of this device.</li><li>The Field Services gives you access to all tasks related to this device to capture the last maintenance and repair tasks.</li></ul></li></ul><p><br></p><h3>📊&nbsp;Monitoring refrigerant consumption&nbsp;</h3><hr><p>From the <strong>Field Service&nbsp;App</strong>, you can monitor the consumed refrigerant products given heavy regulations apply to those products.</p><ul><li>Open the Refrigerant Consumption report from the Reporting menu of the Field Service App.</li><li>Break down is available through time, by product and with "added" and "removed" distinction. This reporting relies on field service worksheets filled up by technicians.</li></ul><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Assign the Refrigerant category to refrigerant products you need to monitor from the Inventory or Sales Apps.</p><p>Only the products of this category are available for selection from the field service worksheet.</p>
            </div>
        </div><p><br></p><p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br></p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p><p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our&nbsp;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>&nbsp;, and feel free to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a>&nbsp;if you need help!</p></div></div><h2><br></h2><h1><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></h1><hr><p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p><ul><li>Leverage the<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Barcode App</font></strong> to manipulate products and serials without mistake.</li><li>Setup your website for free and get leads passively with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website App </font></strong>and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM App</font></strong>!</li><li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment in&nbsp;<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>.</li></ul><p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-fill-primary">Reach us</a></p></div></div><h1><br></h1><h1><strong>Final word</strong></h1><hr><p>You might have tested the Accounting Firm package with or without demo data.</p><p>In any case, you may have written records in journals which are not deletable and which might be an issue for your traceability.</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then to create a new one for your own usage.</strong></p>
            </div>
        </div><p><br></p><div class="oe-hint" style='box-sizing: border-box; color: rgb(55, 65, 81); font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, "Segoe UI", Roboto, "Helvetica Neue", Ubuntu, "Noto Sans", Arial, "Odoo Unicode Support Noto", sans-serif, "Apple Color Emoji", "Segoe UI Emoji", "Segoe UI Symbol", "Noto Color Emoji"; font-size: 14px; font-style: normal; font-variant-ligatures: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: 400; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: 2; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; widows: 2; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-stroke-width: 0px; white-space: normal; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); text-decoration-thickness: initial; text-decoration-style: initial; text-decoration-color: initial;'><br></div>
        ]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
