<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url('/members_club/static/src/binary/ir_attachment/1317-mindfulevening.jpg')","background_color_class":"o_cc3 o_cc","background_color_style":"","opacity":"0.2","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":""}]]></field>
    <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_1"/>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="name">Slow Down to Go Further: A Mindful Evening at The Clubhouse</field>
    <field name="subtitle">How a simple breathing workshop helped our members rediscover presence, purpose, and calm</field>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1'), ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[
            
<p>Last Thursday evening, the lights in the library room were dimmed, the noise of the city left at the door, and a circle of cushions awaited curious members ready to explore something a little outside their usual rhythm: stillness.</p>
<p>We welcomed mindfulness coach <strong>Leona Vervain</strong>, known for her grounded, no-nonsense approach to meditation and breathwork. With a background in neuroscience and a decade of experience leading retreats across Europe, Leona guided us through a 90-minute session called <em>“The Art of the Pause.”</em></p>
<h3>The Power of Presence</h3>
<p>The evening began not with silence, but with laughter, as Leona shared her own struggles with slowing down in a world that celebrates speed. “I used to think productivity was my personality,” she said. “Then I burned out—and found that what I’d been avoiding all along was silence.”</p>
<p>What followed was a simple yet powerful practice: guided breathing, a short seated meditation, and a few gentle exercises to reconnect with the body. No incense. No awkward chants. Just presence.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“I didn’t expect to feel such a shift after only a few breaths,” said member <strong>Sophie L.</strong></p><p>
“It was like someone turned the volume down on my brain. I walked out feeling 10 pounds lighter.”</p>
</blockquote>
<h3>Real Conversations, Real Connection</h3>
<p>After the session, members gathered over herbal tea and small bites in the lounge. What was striking wasn’t just how calm the room felt—it was how open everyone became. </p>
<p><img src="/web/image/members_club.ir_attachment_1318" alt="woman in white tank top and black leggings doing yoga during daytime" class="img img-fluid o_we_custom_image"></p>
<p>Conversations that began with “How did that feel for you?” quickly turned into meaningful discussions about boundaries, burnout, and balance.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“I came because I was curious. I left with a new perspective—and three great book recommendations,” said <strong>Marc T.</strong>, a longtime member.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>“There was something healing about seeing other people wrestle with the same things I do,” added <strong>Elena M.</strong> “It made me feel less alone.”</p>
</blockquote>
<h3>Slowness is a Skill</h3>
<p>What this evening reminded us is that slowness isn’t laziness—it’s a skill. One we rarely practice, and yet deeply need. In the midst of full calendars and constant noise, it was refreshing to press pause, not just individually, but together.</p>
<p>Events like these are part of The Clubhouse’s ongoing intention to offer not just entertainment, but nourishment—for the mind, body, and spirit.</p>
<p>We’re grateful to Leona for holding such a safe, welcoming space—and to every member who showed up with openness and intention.</p>
<p><strong>Next up:</strong> Stay tuned for our <em>Silent Mornings</em> pilot sessions launching in June—quiet co-working, guided journaling, and intentional starts to the day.</p>
<p>Because sometimes the most powerful thing you can do… is breathe.</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
