<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1  class="oe-hint"><span class="display-4-fs"><strong>Campsite</strong></span><br/>
        </h1>
        <p>Hello there!</p><p>You just installed the Odoo for Campsite package. By doing so, we have installed a
            bunch of necessary apps to run your bar efficiently.</p><p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to
            improve your experience.</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import
                    demo data and try the Demo - Use Case (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p><h1 >
            <strong>Basics</strong>
        </h1><hr/><p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p><ul>
            <li>Plan, check in and and check out bookings with the <strong>Campsite App</strong></li>
            <li>Manage your customers from the <strong>Contact App</strong></li>
            <li>Promote your offers through the <strong>Website App</strong></li>
        </ul><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h1 >
            <strong>Use case</strong>
        </h1><hr/><p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products,
            sale orders and more.</p><p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows
            you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p><p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free
            to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt;
                    Upgrade your package and check the related box</p>
            </div>
        </div><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h3 >🌐 Online booking and reviews</h3><hr/><p>You Campsite is online and future guests found it!</p><h4 >Booking a pitch</h4><ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Website App</strong> and navigate to the Stay Offers.</li>
            <li>Click one of the offers to book.</li>
            <li>Adjust the rental dates, click the book button and then proceed to checkout.</li>
            <li>Click the Pay with demo button, and then Pay button to mimic the payment.</li>
            <li>Once confirmed, the payment is done and the order booked seamlessly!</li>
        </ul><p>You're now waiting for your guest to arrive.</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>At any time from the guest order, use the Send message capability in the chatter
                    to exchange with your guest.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h4 >Leaving a review</h4><p>They were happy about their stay, let's ask them to leave a review.</p><ul>
            <li>Anyone can create a portal account on your database.<br/>Open your website home page
                in a private tab to do so.</li>
            <li>Once done, logged in as a portal user. </li>
            <li>Open a stay offer page from the website and scroll down to the Customer Reviews section.</li>
            <li>Adjust the number of stars, leave a comment and send it!</li>
        </ul><p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/ecommerce.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓
                eCommerce</a>
        </p><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h3 >🗓️ Manage bookings</h3><hr/><p>From the <strong>Campsite App</strong>, you can manage your bookings.<br/>The
            Campsite App relies on the Rental and Planning Apps binding, with a few
            customizations.
        </p><h4 >Let's book a pitch!</h4><p>You have a future guest on the line willing to book a pitch? </p><ul>
            <li>Open the Campsite App to appreciate the currently planned bookings with the
                Schedule.</li>
            <li>During an available period, click, drag and drop on a pitch line to create a slot.</li>
            <li>Click the Create Order to open the order form.</li>
            <li>Select or create a customer and then confirm the booking!</li>
        </ul><h4 >They want multiple pitches?</h4><ul>
            <li>You now know how to create a new order.<br/>Let's replicate the previous steps but
                this time, without confirming the order (just saving it as draft).</li>
            <li>Once done, let's click, drag and drop on another pitch line to create a slot.</li>
            <li>This time click the Add to last order button to add this pitch to the booking and
                voila!</li>
            <li>Once done adding all the necessary pitches, click on a recently added slot and then
                click the rental order link.</li>
            <li>Check information and then confirm the booking.</li>
        </ul><h4 >Your customer wants to stay longer?</h4><ul>
            <li>Type in the customer name in the Schedule search bar filtering by Customer.</li>
            <li>Click the tail of the corresponding booking and drag it to the requested date.</li>
        </ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Alternatively, switch to the list view, which is more suitable if the booking is
                    not during the visualized date range and update the booking date range.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h4 >Willing to upgrade a booking?</h4><ul>
            <li>Still from the Campsite App Schedule, simply drag and drop a booking to another offer, from small pitch to large pitch for example!</li>
        </ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Alternatively, switch to the list view, and then change the resource.<br/>Be
                    careful not to double book a resource with such change!</p>
            </div>
        </div><h4 >Blocking a bungalow</h4><p>You are repairing a bungalow or simply welcoming family and don't want guests to book it?</p><ul>
            <li>Open the Campsite App Schedule.</li>
            <li>On the bungalow to block line, click, drag and drop to create a slot.</li>
            <li>This time, simply leave a note about the why this is booked and save the slot.</li>
        </ul><p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/rental.html"
               class="btn btn-secondary">🎓Rental</a>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/planning.html"
               class="btn btn-secondary">🎓Planning</a>
            <a href="https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/19.0/booking_engine"
               class="btn btn-secondary">🎓Booking Engine</a>
        </p><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h3 >😎 Welcome guests</h3><hr/><p>Welcome your guests as well from the <strong>Campsite App</strong>.</p><h4 >Check guests in</h4><p>You welcome your first guests, awesome!</p><ul>
            <li>Open the Campsite App and then navigate to the orders from the menu.</li>
            <li>From the search bar select the Today filter to see to check in and to check out
                orders.</li>
        </ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Alternatively, type in the search bar and select the appropriate filter.</p>
            </div>
        </div><ul>
            <li>Open the order of you just arrived guests.</li>
            <li>Click the Check in button to confirm they are now staying at your place!</li>
        </ul><h4>Trace guest attendance</h4><p>Recording the guest attendance is an obligation in numerous countries.</p><ul>
            <li>Still from their Rental Order, open the Guests tab.</li>
            <li>Add here as many of them as needed.</li>
            <li>Assign them a resource, which helps you keeping track.</li>
        </ul><h4 >Record guest identity</h4><p>You noticed that the Identity Check highlights whether you captured all the
            necessary information for a guest?</p><ul>
            <li>If not OK, then click the contact, fill in the Identity section and save the
                contact.</li>
        </ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You could customize this section to add the identity document picture or extra
                    fields at your convenience with studio. Just be careful, such customizations can
                    quickly become messy.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h4 >Deliver extra services</h4><p>Now that they relax, you can offer extra services to make your guests fill even more
            comfortable!</p><ul>
            <li>At any time during their stay, open their rental order from the Campsite App.</li>
            <li>Add a line with Plancha or a Fan.</li>
            <li>Save the order with those extra services.</li>
        </ul><p>At the end of their stay, your guests will pay for all those extras.</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Alternativelly, you can use the Front Desk from the POS App, selecting the
                    customer, adding any additional services and then paying with the customer
                    account. At the end of the stay the customer account will be charged as well.</p>
            </div>
        </div><p>
            <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/essentials/contacts.html">🎓
                Contacts</a>
        </p><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h3 >🍸 Beyond a place to stay</h3><hr/><p>You have an Campsite but may be providing numerous peripheral services and offers.<br/>Here
            is how you might centralize those and bind them to your customers in a single database.</p><h4 >Bar &amp; Restaurant and extra services</h4><ul>
            <li>Open the POS App and select one of the register, the Bar for example.</li>
            <li>Add some products to the ongoing order and send it to the preparation display and
                bring them to your guests.</li>
            <li>When they ask for the bill, you can charge them directly or add the bill to their
                customer account.<br/>To do so, open the corresponding order from the table or from
                the order list and select the customer to charge.<br/>Click the payment and the
                validation buttons!</li>
        </ul><p>They will balance their customer account during the check out!</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>If you're not certain customers have ongoing bookings, before charging their customer accounts, open their contact details from their menu (from the customer list) and ask for the room they stay in<br/>Note: Their room is listed in the Guests tab of their order.</p>
            </div>
        </div><p>Don't be limited to those examples, you could have a paddles and kayaks available or even bikes to rent!</p><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓
            POS</a> <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale/preparation.html">🎓 Preparation Display</a></p><p>
            <br/>
        </p><h3 >👋 Wave your guests</h3><hr/><p>Again, the <strong>Campsite App </strong>helps you manage the end of the stay!</p><h4 >Check guests out</h4><ul>
            <li>Open your guest order from the Campsite App.</li>
            <li>Click the Check out button to capture they left their spot .</li>
        </ul><h4 >Manage the city tax</h4><p>You may have noticed the city tax were added to the guest order from the moment they
            checked in.<br/>This is because city taxes are to be billed to spent nights in practice
            and not in theory.<br/>Let's adjust them now.</p><ul>
            <li>On the City Tax line, adjust the number of guest x nights delivered.</li>
        </ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Example: A bungalow for 2 is booked for 4 nights, two guests were here for the first
                    three nights but only one stayed the last night. Then the guest x nights is
                    2x3+1x1=7.</p>
            </div>
        </div><p>Those city tax are now due as well as any other additional services consumed during the
            stay.</p>
        <h4 >Charge your guests</h4><ul>
            <li>Once your guest order is all set after check out, create an invoice from their order.</li>
            <li>If they paid orders at any point of sale with their customer account, their customer account due amount will be displayed as well as a button for you to settle the associated orders.</li>
            <li>Click the Settle PoS Orders button to add the corresponding order lines.</li>
            <li>When all is in order, confirm their invoice for payment.</li>
            <li>Proceed to the payment with your terminal and set the invoice as paid.</li>
            <li>Don't forget to send them their invoice!</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o-paragraph">
            <br/>
        </div><p>
            <em>Don't forget to thank your guests with a warm goodbye!</em>
        </p><p>
            <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting/taxes.html">🎓
                Taxes</a>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓
                Invoicing</a>
            <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html">🎓 POS</a>
        </p><p><br/></p>
        <h3 >🔢 Running multiple places</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>You may be running multiple places at the same time and most likely be willing to run them all from the same database.<b/>We got you covered with this using multiple companies or branches!</p>
        <h4>Managing your businesses</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Settings App</strong> and reach the companies from the menu Users &amp; Companies.</li>
            <li>From there you can add new companies.</li>
            <li>You can as well select your company and in the Branches tab define branches.</li>
        </ul>

        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>The strength of Odoo is to separate the accounting and many other aspects which are company dependent!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>Once defined, you can switch between companies or branches from the company selector at the top right of your screen.<br/>This will expose depending on where you are, only the selected companies and branches data.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <div class="o-paragraph">Each company can have its own website!</div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h4>Employee assignations</h4>
        <p>Now that you have several companies or branches, you may want some of your employees to access only to some of them in case they always work in some of your places.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Settings App</strong> and reach the users from the menu Users &amp; Companies.</li>
            <li>Select one of your employee.</li>
            <li>From the Roles sections, you can select the companies and branches this employee shall have access to as well as the default one.</li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Adjusting your offers in consequence</h4>
        <p>Two options are now available to you with multiple companies and branches:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Share your stay offers across your companies and branches (default behavior);</li>
            <li>Setup company or branch specific offers when relevant.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>In any case, the resources are company and branch dependent.</p>
        <p><strong>Shared offers</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Created offers are assigned no company nor branch (default behavior).<br/>As a result, they are available from all companies and branches, as well as all websites from those.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <div class="o-paragraph">They as well share the same pricing, defined at the stay offer level, which has its pros and cons.</div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Company specific offers</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>When creating an offer, assign them a company or a branch.<br/>As a result, they are available only for the selected company or branch, and will be available only from its website.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <div class="o-paragraph">This setup is relevant in case of place specific offers or when pricing varies between places.</div>
                <div class="o-paragraph">It enables each place manager to adjust the stay offers with greater flexibility without impacting other places.</div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/general/companies.html">🎓
                Companies</a>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website/configuration/multi_website.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓
                Websites</a>
        </p>
        <p> <br/></p><p>
            <br/>
        </p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your
                    Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p> Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel
                    free to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need
                    help! </p>
            </div>
        </div><h2 >
            <br/>
        </h2><h1 >
            <strong>Do you want to go further?</strong>
        </h1><hr/><p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p><ul>
            <li> Organize your employees' schedules with<font class="text-o-color-5"> <strong>
                Planning</strong></font><strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-5"> App</font>
                </strong><font class="text-o-color-5">.</font></li>
            <li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment i<font class="text-o-color-5">n </font><strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-5">Accounting App</font>
                </strong><font class="text-o-color-5">.</font>
            </li>
            <li>Open the door for more custom workflows and actions with the power of <strong>Studio
                App</strong>.</li>
            <li>In case you outsource or rely more heavily on suppliers, the <strong>Purchase App</strong>
                will help you to manage those aspects.</li>
        </ul><p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-fill-primary">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div><h1 >
            <br/>
        </h1><h1 >
            <strong>Final word</strong>
        </h1><hr/><p>You might have tested this package with or without demo data.</p><p>In any case, you may have written records in journals which are not delete-able and which
            might be an issue for your traceability.</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" contenteditable="false" role="status">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>
                    <strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then
                        to create a new one for your own usage.</strong>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div><p>
            <br/>
        </p><div class="oe-hint o-paragraph" style="box-sizing: border-box; color: rgb(55, 65, 81); font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Ubuntu, 'Noto Sans', Arial, 'Odoo Unicode Support Noto', sans-serif, 'Apple Color Emoji', 'Segoe UI Emoji', 'Segoe UI Symbol', 'Noto Color Emoji'; font-size: 14px; font-style: normal; font-variant-ligatures: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: 400; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: 2; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; widows: 2; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-stroke-width: 0px; white-space: normal; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); text-decoration-thickness: initial; text-decoration-style: initial; text-decoration-color: initial;">
            <br/>
        </div><p>
            <br/>
        </p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Campsite - Start here!</field>
        <field name="icon">🏕️</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
