<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Odoo for Concert Halls</h1>
        <p>
            Running an escape-room venue is a race against the clock—both for your players and for you as an operator! Odoo brings all your daily tasks into one sleek dashboard, so reservations, payments, and follow-ups happen automatically while you focus on creating thrilling puzzles.
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>Basics</h2>
        <p><strong>Apps &amp; What They Do:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website 🌐:</strong> Show rooms, stories, prices; capture reservations in real time, sell gift cards</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Appointments 📅:</strong> Let guests pick room, date, time from your live calendar, turns choices into confirmed slots, locks room capacity.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Point of Sale 🛒:</strong> Sell walk-ins, snacks, drinks, souvenirs with barcode speed.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>CRM 🎯: </strong>Track inquiries, group events, corporate deals, repeat-player campaigns.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
        <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
        <h3>Website 🌐</h3>
        <div>
            Your website becomes the control room of your escape business — not just a digital brochure. Customize landing pages, link directly to your scheduler, and turn curiosity into confirmed bookings. The site is fully responsive,
            multilingual, and SEO-friendly.
        </div>
        <div><br/></div>
        <p><strong>How to use it</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Build engaging room pages using the <strong>drag-and-drop website editor</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Highlight themes, difficulty, group size, and age range using <strong>structured blocks</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Embed <strong>booking widgets</strong> that sync with Appointments &amp; Booking.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Enable <strong>multi-language and mobile-friendly</strong> layouts.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Connect <strong>Google Analytics</strong> and monitor conversion performance.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Website Documentation</a></p>
        <h3><strong>Gift Cards 🎁 </strong></h3>
        <p>Gift Cards are a powerful upselling tool during holidays, birthdays, and corporate events. They allow customers to prepay a game for friends or teams — generating cash flow even before a slot is booked.</p>
        <p><strong>How to use it</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create <strong>gift card products</strong> in the Products menu in the Sales or Point of Sale app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Sell them via <strong>Website or POS</strong>.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales/products_prices/ewallets_giftcards.html?highlight=gift" class="btn btn-secondary">Gift Cards Documentation</a></p>
        <h3><strong>Appointments 📅</strong></h3>
        <p>
            This app makes scheduling intuitive for customers and efficient for your team. Whether it’s a small group or a company team-building event, players can choose their preferred slot, answer custom questions, and receive instant confirmations. It’s all synced behind the scenes with room capacity.
        </p>
        <p><strong>How to use it</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Set up <strong>schedules and time slots</strong> per room and per day.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add <strong>custom questions</strong> (team size, occasion, language).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Enable <strong>email/SMS confirmations and reminders</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>View bookings in <strong>calendar or list format</strong> internally.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>Each appointment becomes a booking record, storing key details like room, players, language preferences (<strong>just create another question)</strong>, and payments.</p>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/appointments.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Appointments Documentation</a></p>
        <h2>Point of Sale 🏧</h2>
        <p>The Point of Sale module turns your front desk into a fully operational sales hub. Sell tickets to walk-ins, offer snacks and drinks, and upsell merchandise — all from a sleek touchscreen interface that’s fast and easy to use.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create products like <strong>entrances, snacks, drinks, souvenirs, gift cards</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Accept <strong>cash, card, and mobile payments</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Print or email <strong>receipts instantly</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track sales per staff member with <strong>session reports</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Optional: connect to <strong>Inventory and Accounting</strong>.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html">Point of Sale Documentation</a></p>
        <h2>CRM 🌟</h2>
        <p>The CRM app is perfect for handling special requests, partnerships, or team-building inquiries. Manage leads from your website or referrals, track conversations, and schedule follow-ups to turn them into confirmed group events.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Organize leads by <strong>type</strong>: corporate, school, private, etc.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>pipelines</strong> to track enquiry > quote > contract > event.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Schedule <strong>calls, meetings, and follow-ups</strong> directly in the chatter.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Analyze deal performance with <strong>reporting tools</strong>.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-secondary">CRM Documentation</a></p>
        <h2><strong>Tips for Success</strong></h2>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Keep your <strong>room capacity settings accurate</strong> to avoid conflicts and last-minute panic.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>custom questions</strong> during booking to tailor the experience (e.g. birthday surprise? team-building?).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Promote <strong>gift cards</strong> on your homepage and in your POS for holidays and events.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Regularly review your <strong>CRM pipeline</strong> to identify group deals or repeat visitors.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Offer small <strong>POS bundles</strong> (drink + souvenir combo) to increase average spend.<br/></p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <hr/>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <p>Once your core operations are running smoothly, consider expanding your toolset:</p>
        <p>Want to manage more than just bookings?</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting</strong>: Automatically log payments, close sessions, and generate tax reports.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sign</strong>: Send and receive digital contracts for team events, partnerships, or corporate clients.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Planning</strong>: Build your weekly staff schedule based on room bookings and predicted attendance.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Project</strong>: Manage the development of your next room — from concept to construction to launch.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>With Odoo, your escape room operations aren't just automated — they’re leveled up. Curious how far you can go? Let’s open the next door. 🗝️</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Escape Rooms</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="icon">🚪</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
