<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.1">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>Food Trucks</strong>
            </span>
            <br />
        </h1>
        <p>With the Food Trucks Industry Package, you have all you need to manage your business from customer bookings to invoicing, including a point-of-sale system and much more. </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Basics</span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>Use the <strong>CRM app</strong> to manage your opportunities</li>
            <li>Send quotations to prospective customers through the <strong>Sales app</strong>
            </li>
            <li>Manage your presence at events using the <strong>Field Service app</strong>
            </li>
            <li>Invoice your customers using the <strong>Invoice app</strong>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>📕 Bookings</h3>
        <p>In some cases, you will get bookings from customers (coporate, etc.) for you to attend an company event or other similar events. </p>
        <h3>✅ CRM </h3>
        <p>Incoming opportunities can be registered into your CRM. Manage opportunity stages in the kanban view, categorization using tags, to-do's and reminders using activities, and communication through the chatter. </p>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html">CRM Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <h3>📊 Sales</h3>
        <p>Once you have all the information regarding this opportunity, you can make a new quotation. Define how long you'll be staying, and if relevant, other things you will be charging to the customer. </p>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html">Sales Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <h3>🚗 Field Service</h3>
        <p>
        When your prospective customer confirms the sale, a new task is created in your field service app, and linked back to your sale order. You can manage assignations, needs, and so on from there and obtain a handy overview of your
        planning. 
        </p>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/field_service.html">Field Service Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <h3>🥨 Point of sale</h3>
        <p>
        While on the field, you can take orders and payments from your customers or from the attendees through the Point of Sale app. The app is a fully featured point-of-sale solution that supports menus, products, quantities, discounts,
        pricelists, custom notes, and many other features. 
        </p>
        <p>Handle all your customers in a breeze and get a nice overview of your income through the reporting features that are integrated in Odoo. </p>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html">Point of Sale Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <h3>✨ Invoicing</h3>
        <p>If applicable, you can invoice your presence to your customer through the invoice app. You can configure your invoice templates to include terms &amp; conditions, as well as other handy features. </p>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">Invoicing Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <ul>
                    <li>If applicable, you can of course directly manage your events directly in the Field service app without going through the CRM and Sales app. </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>
                    <strong>Tips for Success</strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Categorize your products and food combos to obtain statistics on what you're selling</li>
                    <li>Create activities in the CRM to ensure you're keeping track of open opportunities</li>
                    <li>Explore extra Odoo apps that might be interesting for your specific business, they're all included in your subscription ! </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>Install the <strong>Social Marketing App </strong>to manage your social media presence. </li>
            <li>Take a look at the <strong>Email Marketing App</strong> to let past customers know what you're up to ! </li>
            <li>Manage your <strong>Purchases and Inventory</strong> in Odoo as well. </li>
            <li>Did you know you can also get a full <strong>Accounting</strong> suite in Odoo? </li>
            <li>Need a Website? No problem, Odoo can do it as well. </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Food Trucks</field>
        <field name="icon">🚌</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
