<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Architect Industry</h1>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 16px;">
                This industry is made for architects that sell all kind of architectural services such as feasibility studies, schematic design, design development, worksite follow-up, energy efficiency assessment.
            </span>
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <div><br/></div>
        <h1>Business flows</h1>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Basics</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Project App</b>: Orchestrate complex architectural projects by managing distinct phases like schematic
                design, development, and construction.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Timesheets App</b>: Ensure profitability by accurately tracking time spent on design drafting, client
                meetings, and site visits.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>CRM App</b>: Centralize client interactions to effectively manage leads and convert design proposals into
                signed contracts.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Documents App</b>: Securely organize, version, and share critical files such as architectural drawings,
                permits, and blueprints.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Sales App</b>: Create professional proposals and contracts tailored for architectural services, streamlining
                the agreement process.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Invoicing App</b>: Maintain healthy cash flow by billing clients flexibly based on project milestones or
                actual time spent.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Knowledge App</b>: Centralize design standards, building codes, and internal guidelines to ensure consistency
                across the team.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Manage leads in the CRM</h2>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                The CRM App is designed to let architecture firms easily manage new prospects, called "Opportunities" in Odoo. Track expected revenue, manage communications, and never forget to reach out to interested parties. Opportunities get created in the CRM by filling the "Contact us" form on the website, or manually by a salesperson.
            </span>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    <span style="font-size: 14px"
                        >Create automated actions to never forget to execute your next steps to keep your business growing, for
                        example:</span>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li style="font-size: 14px">A phone call activity is created when there's a new opportunity</li>
                    <li style="font-size: 14px">
                        A to-do activity is created when the opportunity moves to the "needs analysis" stage"
                    </li>
                    <li style="font-size: 14px">
                        <span style="font-size: 14px">A reminder to cancel the opportunity is created when the quotation is sent</span>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <span style="font-size: 14px">
                        <span style="font-size: 14px">Learn more on how to automate your business using <strong>Odoo Studio</strong></span>
                    </span>
                    <br/>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-primary">
                CRM Documentation
            </a>
        </p>
        <h2>Create Quotations</h2>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px"
                >When it's time to provide the customer with an estimate, a quote can be created by clicking the "New Quotation"
                button on the opportunity. These can also be pre-filled using the Quotation Template feature. Quotation
                Templates allow you to quickly choose a preset that contains sections and their products - especially useful
                when you're working with similar, elaborate templates.
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <span style="font-size: 14px"
                    >A set of architectural services have already been created and can be edited to match the architects'
                    services.
                </span>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-primary">Sales Documentation</a>
            </span>
        </p>
        <h2>Architectural Projects</h2>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">Once a quotation has been confirmed, a project is automatically generated in the Project app, with associated tasks.
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <span style="font-size: 14px">
                    It's the heart of your architectural work. It's where you'll track the advancement of the various tasks,
                    generate new invoices (if needed), and assign tasks to employees and contractors alike. Track your
                    timesheets, margins, purchase orders, and more using the project menu to quickly access relevant information.
                </span>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <img src="/web/image/architects.ir_attachment_1" class="img-fluid"/>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px"><span style="font-size: 14px">Use the Project Menu to quickly access</span></span>
        </p>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html" class="btn btn-primary">Project Documentation</a>
            </span>
        </p>
        <h3>Documentation</h3>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px">
                <span style="font-size: 14px">
                    Use the documents app to store and share all project documents. Sub-workspaces get created for each project, and link to these sub-workspace can be shared with customers so that they have a direct access to all produced documents.
                </span>
            </span>
        </p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Architecture Firm</field>
        <field name="sequence">2</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">68.59</field>
        <field name="icon">📏</field>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
