<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>BikeHub</h1>
            <p>
                This master guide combines Odoo's specialized packages for the bike industry. It covers both long-term
                subscription business models (Bike Leasing) and traditional retail, online, and workshop setups (Bike Shop) into a
                single, connected operational workflow.
            </p>
            <p>
                By linking your front-end sales channels directly with background inventory, workshop tracking, and billing, Odoo
                ensures your operations stay organized while offering a smooth experience to your clients.
            </p>
            <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
            <h2>Basics</h2>
            <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Point of Sale (PoS)</font></b> manages bike and accessory
                        sales directly in the store.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Sales App</font></b> create and manage quotations, sales
                        orders, and long-term leasing contracts.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The CRM App</font></b
                        > tracks new customer inquiries, manages long-term leasing leads, and organizes sales pipelines.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The eCommerce App</font></b> sell bikes, configurations, and
                        recurring subscription plans online with a customizable web store.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Project App</font></b> organizes and tracks repair tasks,
                        deadlines, and parts used in the workshop.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Planning App </font></b
                        >organizes and allocates technician shifts, manages workshop repair schedules, and tracks resource
                        availability.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Inventory App</font></b> tracks bike and parts stock,
                        including serial numbers and automated rental return schedules.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Purchase App</font></b> manages vendor orders, restocks
                        parts, and handles supplier delivery minimums.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Website App</font></b> manages your online presence and allow
                        customers to book appointments or test rides.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b><font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165)">The Helpdesk App</font></b> manages warranty claims, leasing
                        customer support, and general service requests.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire
                        workflow.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Use Case</h2>
            <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
            <p>
                You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with
                this package using Odoo.
            </p>
            <p>
                Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps,
                delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!
            </p>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        <strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to
                        <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Interior Design package</strong> and check the related
                        box.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Managing Orders</h2>
            <h3>Selling Bikes and Accessories In-Store</h3>
            <p>Manage in-store transactions for bikes, accessories, or specific parts with the Point of Sale (PoS) app.</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Open the Point of Sale App and start a session by clicking on your register.</p></li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Add products to the cart by scanning barcodes or searching manually and manage bikes with product variants
                        (e.g. frame size, color) to keep a single product reference while tracking specific configurations for
                        stock, pricing, and availability.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Proceed to payment by using the selected method; cash, card or on the Customer Account if you let the user
                        pay later (e.g. if you order the specific model from the manufacturer for the client.)
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li><p>Inventory levels update automatically after each sale.</p></li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">✅</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        <b>Configure Optional Products:</b> Suggest relevant accessories such as helmets, locks, or lights by
                        configuring them as optional products, which appear during checkout to encourage upselling.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h3>Selling Bikes via the eCommerce</h3>
            <p>
                Sell bikes and services online using the Website and eCommerce apps, providing a complete digital shopping
                experience for your clients.
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Configure your website to present your bike catalog, services, and brand mission with a clean and structured
                        layout.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Organize products by category (e.g., VTT, Cargo, Electric) to help users quickly find the right bike type.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Enable test ride bookings by integrating the Appointment app, so users can reserve a slot to try a bike
                        directly from the product page.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Set up payment and delivery methods: let customers choose between home delivery or in-store pickup, and
                        secure transactions with trusted payment gateways.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Allow leasing clients to pick recurring plans (Monthly, Quarterly, or Yearly) with prices automatically
                        driven by your predefined, selectable pricelists.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <h3>Manage Orders via the Sales App</h3>
            <p>
                Handle Services of Repairs and Maintenance, as well as customized long-term leasing options through the Sales app,
                with integration to CRM, planning, inventory, and communication tools.
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <b>Lead Acquisition:</b> Track incoming requests for fleet leasing or high-end custom bikes inside the
                        <b>CRM app</b>. Inquiries from your website contact forms or emails automatically generate a new opportunity
                        card in your sales pipeline.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Drag and drop leads through pipeline stages (e.g., <i>New</i>, <i>Qualified</i>, <i>Proposition</i>) and
                        launch a specific quote directly inside the card by clicking the <b>"New Quotation"</b> button, which links
                        the CRM history directly to the Sales app.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Open the Sales app from the main dashboard to view generated documents, or create a Sales Order manually by
                        setting the required fields for a subscription (Customer, Pricelist / Recurring, Until, and Products).
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Use the Chatter feature inside the order or the CRM card to easily communicate with the customer, log phone
                        calls, and finalize details like delivery dates and renting durations.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>Confirm the Sales Order to trigger the appropriate actions:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <p>
                                For bike or parts sales, a delivery order is generated, reserving the product from stock and
                                updating the inventory accordingly.
                            </p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>
                                For repairs or maintenance, a task is created automatically under the "Workshop" Project, and a
                                service slot can be assigned to a mechanic using the <b>Planning app</b>.
                            </p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Send the finished proposal via email for the customer to confirm instantly with an official digital
                        signature. Once all tasks related to the Sales Order are marked as done, the order becomes collectible and
                        notifies the customer via an automated email.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        <b>Customize customer notifications:</b> Personalize the "Order Ready" email by enabling Debug Mode,
                        navigating to Email Templates, and editing "Sales Order: Order Ready". You can also configure automated
                        messages via SMS and WhatsApp using Odoo’s marketing automation and messaging integrations.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Repair and Maintenance Workflow</h2>
            <p>Handle all repair, maintenance, and long-term asset inspections efficiently with the Planning and Project apps.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Open the <b>Planning app</b> to check your assigned repair shifts, scheduled jobs, or workshop priorities.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Select your assigned task from the "Workshop" Project to begin the repair. Log each product used (e.g.,
                        brake pads, chains) directly on the task line. These will be automatically added to the related Sales Order
                        and invoiced later.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        For specific repairs, track the time spent working your shift using the Timesheet feature, allowing accurate
                        billing based on time spent.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Mark the task as Done when completed. Once all tasks linked to the Sales Order are in this stage, a
                        notification email will automatically be sent to the customer confirming that their bike is ready.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Complete the repair and maintenance worksheet using a Worksheet Template (e.g., checklist of performed
                        operations, technician name, signature field,...). The client can sign it upon collection.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        When the customer returns to pick up the bike, open the Point of Sale (PoS) app, load the related Sales
                        Order (quotation), and proceed with the payment. Odoo allows retrieving existing quotations in the PoS for
                        seamless final payment processing.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">🔎</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        Filter repair tasks by Serial Number to view a bike’s repair history; helpful for recurring maintenance
                        actions like annual oil checks on specific components.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Customize your project stages in the “Workshop” project: add columns like “Waiting for Parts” to better
                        track blocked repairs waiting for a parts delivery, or “Ready for Pick-Up" when the repair is done.
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h3>Handle warranty cases through the Helpdesk app:</h3>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Open the “Warranties / After-Sales / SAV” team in the Helpdesk app to manage all warranty tickets and
                        general leasing support inquiries.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Create a ticket to verify the warranty or answer support questions. You can automate ticket creation by
                        sharing specialized email aliases (e.g., warranties@bike-shop.odoo.com or help@qfr-bike-leasing.odoo.com)
                        which turn incoming messages into tickets automatically.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Link the ticket to the related Sales Order Line and the matching Workshop task (e.g. repair on the client’s
                        Cube bike). Move the ticket to the “Sent to Brand” column and use an Email Template to contact the brand for
                        warranty confirmation.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Based on the brand’s response, check or uncheck the "Warranty" box on the Workshop task to reflect whether
                        the repair is covered.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Inventory &amp; Stock Replenishment</h2>
            <p>
                Manage bike parts, showroom items, and long-term rental stock efficiently using the Purchase and Inventory apps to
                avoid shortages and streamline restocking.
            </p>
            <h3>Manual Purchase Orders</h3>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>Create a Purchase Order from the Purchase app when specific parts (e.g., tires, brakes) are running low.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>Select your preferred vendor based on pricing or delivery performance to optimize purchase conditions.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>Once the purchase is confirmed, send the Request for Quotation (RFQ) via email or confirm it manually.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        When the goods arrive, click the “Receipt” smart button to validate the incoming shipment and add parts to
                        your inventory.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        In the Contact app, manage your preferred vendors and set reminders/warnings if there is a minimum order
                        amount required to get free transport costs.
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <h3>Automated Reordering</h3>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Go to the Inventory app and open the product (e.g., brake pads). Use the Smart Buttons on the product page
                        to access the Reordering Rules.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Set the minimum and maximum stock levels. Define the quantities that will trigger automatic restocking
                        (e.g., Min: 10, Max: 50).
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Let Odoo handle reorders automatically. When forecasted stock drops below the minimum, Odoo will generate a
                        Purchase Order based on your settings.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        For confirmed lease orders, an inventory delivery is built automatically to track the specific bike. You
                        must fill in its unique serial number, and Odoo will create a return reminder activity matching the end date
                        of the leasing contract.
                    </p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        Use the auto-post feature to automatically generate and send recurring invoices to leasing customers
                        according to your preferred method (email, snail mail, or e-invoicing).
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        Add vendor lead times on each product to anticipate delivery delays and organize procurement planning
                        accordingly (e.g., 5-day lead time for imported suspension forks).<br />
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Workflow Example</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    A new corporate lead inquires online about fleet leasing; a pipeline opportunity instantly populates in your
                    <b>CRM app</b>.
                </li>
                <li>
                    You configure the client's custom order right inside the CRM opportunity card. Choose bike sizes and colors
                    easily, add optional extras like helmets, and select a quarterly payment plan.
                </li>
                <li>
                    You generate and send a Sales Order directly from the CRM card, which the customer confirms using a digital
                    signature.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Odoo automatically schedules a service or assembly slot in the <b>Planning app</b> and generates a delivery slip
                    tracking the bike's serial number in the Inventory app.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Your mechanics complete the final setup check during their planned shift, add any extra setup parts used to the
                    task, and mark the project task as Done.
                </li>
                <li>The customer gets an automated email letting them know the bike fleet is ready for pickup or delivery.</li>
                <li>
                    Finish the payment when the customer picks up the items directly from the PoS using the linked order, or let the
                    system automatically post monthly/quarterly leasing invoices.
                </li>
                <li>Stock updates automatically, and missing parts are reordered based on minimum levels you’ve set.</li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🎉</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>
                        You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your
                        business needs. Discover more about Odoo by diving into our documentation and academy, and feel free to
                        request a demo if you need help!
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Do you want to go further?</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Add the Employees App to manage your mechanics and sales team profiles, contracts, and roles.</li>
                <li>
                    Use the Planning App to organize broader schedule shifts for your front desk, workshop team, and retail store
                    managers.
                </li>
                <li>Simplify accounting and financial tracking with the Accounting App.</li>
                <li>
                    Engage your customers using Email Marketing, SMS Marketing, and Marketing Automation based on their CRM buying
                    history.
                </li>
            </ul>
            <div
                class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
                data-oe-role="status"
            >
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                    <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                    <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary" rel="noreferrer">Schedule a demo</a></p>
                </div>
            </div>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">BikeHub</field>
        <field name="icon">🚲</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_position">20.209999999999983</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
