<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="hr.job_cto" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Chief Technical Officer</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>You will take part in the consulting services we provide to our partners and customers: design, analysis, development, testing, project management, support/coaching. You will work autonomously as well as coordinate and supervise small distributed development teams for some projects. Optionally, you will deliver Odoo training sessions to partners and customers (8-10 people/session). You will report to the Head of Professional Services and work closely with all developers and consultants.

The job is located in Grand-Rosière (1367), Belgium (between Louvain-La-Neuve and Namur).</p>]]></field>
    <field name="requirements"><![CDATA[Bachelor, master or engineering degree in Computer Science or equivalent by experience
Preferably at least 1 years of experience
Interest for enterprise application development
Customer-minded
Willing to travel abroad occasionally for short term missions.
Passion for the Internet and its culture
Quick and autonomous learner, problem-solving personality, enthusiastic when faced with technical challenges
Team spirit and good communication
Required skills:
Good knowledge of object oriented programming, object modeling, relational databases, Unix/Linux platform
Fluent in English, especially read and written
Nice-to-have skills:
Good knowledge of Python
Good knowledge of HTML and Javascript
Knowledge of UML-like modeling
Good language skills, other than English (Dutch and French preferred, others welcome)
            ]]></field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_rd"/>
    <field name="company_id" eval="False"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_permanent"/>
  </record>
  <record id="hr.job_consultant" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Consultant</field>
    <field name="no_of_recruitment">5</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>We are looking for a Consultant to provide expert advice and strategic solutions,
                driving business growth. Strong analytical skills and a proven track record in delivering results are
                essential.
            </p>]]></field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_ps"/>
    <field name="company_id" eval="False"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_interim"/>
  </record>
  <record id="hr.job_developer" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Experienced Developer</field>
    <field name="no_of_recruitment">5</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>We are looking for an experience developer to join our Web team.
                Someone who can snap out of coding and perform analysis or meet clients to explain the technical
                possibilities that can meet their needs.
            </p>]]></field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_rd"/>
    <field name="company_id" eval="False"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_permanent"/>
  </record>
  <record id="hr.job_hrm" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Human Resources Manager</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>A Human Resources (HR) Manager is responsible for overseeing an organization's workforce and ensuring
                that all HR functions are effectively managed. This includes recruiting, hiring, onboarding, and
                training new employees, as well as managing employee relations, performance, and compensation. The HR
                manager also ensures compliance with labor laws and company policies, while fostering a positive work
                environment. They may handle conflict resolution, conduct employee evaluations, and implement programs
                to improve employee engagement and retention. Additionally, HR managers play a strategic role in
                aligning the workforce with the organization's goals and objectives.
            </p>]]></field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_administration"/>
    <field name="company_id" eval="False"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_permanent"/>
  </record>
  <record id="hr.job_marketing" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Marketing and Community Manager</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>The Marketing Manager defines the mid- to long-term marketing strategy for his covered market segments
                in the World. He develops and monitors the annual budget in collaboration with Sales. He defines the
                products and customers portfolio according to the marketing plan. This mission requires strong
                collaboration with Technical Service and Sales.
            </p>]]></field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_sales"/>
  </record>
  <record id="hr.job_trainee" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Trainee</field>
    <field name="description"><![CDATA[<p>You participate to the update of our tutorial tools and pre-sales tools after the launch of a new version of Odoo. Indeed, any new version of the software brings significant improvements in terms of functionalities, ergonomics and configuration.
You will have to become familiar with the existing tools (books, class supports, Odoo presentation’s slides, commercial tools),
to participate to the update of those tools in order to make them appropriate for the new version of the software and, for sure,
to suggest improvements in order to cover the new domains of the software.
You join the Implementation Assistance department. This team of 3 people go with Odoo’s clients in the set up of the software. Your role will be
to animate webinars in order to show the different functionalities of the software.
to be involved in the support of the customers and
to answer to their questions.
You help the support manager to set up new support services by
being involved in the treatment of new cases,
contributing to the set up of a new politic,
being involved into satisfaction surveys in order to have a better knowledge of how the support given is seen by the customers.</p>]]></field>
    <field name="requirements"><![CDATA[You speak fluently English and French (one other European language is a +)
At the time of your traineeship at Odoo, you will be in the last year of a Master or Bachelor Degree (ideally in the following sector: Business Management, IT Management, Computer Sciences)
You have a software and new technology awareness
You are ready to join a young and dynamic company, you are able to work in a “start up” fast paced environment, hands on attitude
You are approachable, honest and a fun team player
If you have development competencies, we can propose you specific traineeships]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="planning.job_quality_control" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Quality Control Inspector</field>
    <field name="no_of_recruitment">5</field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_ps"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_permanent"/>
  </record>
  <record id="planning.job_maintenance_technician" model="hr.job" forcecreate="1">
    <field name="name">Maintenance Technician</field>
    <field name="no_of_recruitment">5</field>
    <field name="department_id" ref="hr.dep_ps"/>
    <field name="contract_type_id" ref="hr.contract_type_permanent"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
