<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <record id="knowledge_article_36" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Project Specification</field>
    <field name="icon">📝</field>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
  </record>
  <record id="knowledge_article_37" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Kevin Smith Project</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[
      <div class="oe-hint"><span class="h1-fs"><strong><u>Kevin Smith Project</u></strong></span></div>
      <div><span class="h3-fs"><strong><br></strong></span></div>
      <div><span class="h3-fs"><strong>Manufacturing Bom Instruction</strong></span></div>
      <br />
      <br />
      <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
      <h2>1. Frame Fabrication (Laser &amp; Forming)</h2>
      <p>The frame must be perfectly concentric to prevent the belt from mistracking.</p>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Laser Cutting:</b> Load the DXF files for the inner and outer side profiles.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> Cut the side rails from 10-gauge (3mm) sheet metal. Ensure the arc length ($L$) is calculated as $L = \theta \times R$, where $\theta$ is the angle in radians.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p><b>Detail:</b> Cut mounting slots for rollers at specific intervals (usually every 5–10 degrees) to allow for minor tracking adjustments.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Bending/Rolling:</b> If the design uses a continuous plate rather than faceted segments:</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> Run the side rails through a plate roller to match the precise radius of the bed.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Cross-Member Prep:</b> Cut C-channel or square tubing to the exact "width" of the conveyor.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> Deburr all edges to prevent belt snagging.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>2. Bed Plate &amp; Slider Bed Assembly</h2>
      <p>This is the surface the belt slides on. It must be smooth and low-friction.</p>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Sheet Cutting:</b> Laser cut the "fan-shaped" bed sections.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> If the conveyor is wide, cut the bed into 30-degree segments to reduce material waste (nesting).</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Countersinking:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Drill and countersink holes into the bed plate so that the flat-head screws sit <b>below</b> the surface of the metal.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Safety Check:</b> Any protruding bolt head will tear the belt within minutes of operation.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>3. Tapered Roller Machining</h2>
      <p>Standard straight rollers will not work; the outer edge of the belt travels faster than the inner edge.</p>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Lathe Turning:</b> Take high-density polyethylene (HDPE) or steel tube blanks.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> Turn the tubes on a lathe to create a taper. The ratio must match the radii:</p>
              <p>$$\frac{\text{Diameter}_{outer}}{\text{Diameter}_{inner}} = \frac{R_{outer}}{R_{inner}}$$</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Bearing Press:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Press-fit precision ball bearings into both ends of the tapered rollers. Insert a through-shaft (typically 12mm or 15mm hex or round).</p>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>4. Drive &amp; Tail Pulley Integration</h2>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Lagging the Drive Pulley:</b></p>
          <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Action:</b> Apply a rubber "lagging" (vulcanized or glue-on) to the drive pulley. This prevents the belt from slipping under load.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Shaft Alignment:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Mount the drive and tail shafts into the side frames using flanged bearings.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Precision Step:</b> Use a laser level to ensure the drive shaft is perfectly perpendicular to the center-line of the curve.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>5. Belt Preparation &amp; Guidance</h2>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Edge Beading:</b> * <b>Action:</b> High-frequency weld a PVC "V-guide" or "Bead" to the underside of the outer radius of the belt.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Track Installation:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Install a UHMW (Ultra-High Molecular Weight) plastic guide track along the outer side frame. The belt bead will "lock" into this track to counteract the centripetal force pulling the belt inward.</p>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>6. Final Assembly &amp; Squaring</h2>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Frame Squaring:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Bolt the cross-members to the side rails. Measure the distance between the inner and outer rails at the start, middle, and end of the curve. The variance must be $&lt; 1mm$.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Belt Tensioning:</b></p>
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p><b>Action:</b> Thread the belt through the rollers and around the drive/tail pulleys.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p><b>Tracking Run:</b> Power on the motor at a low frequency (10–15Hz). Observe the belt. Adjust the take-up bolts on the tail pulley until the belt stays centered in the guide track.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
      <h2>7. Electrical &amp; Safety</h2>
      <ul>
        <li>
          <p><b>Motor Mounting:</b> Bolt the gearmotor to the drive shaft torque arm.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Wiring:</b> Connect the motor to the VFD.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
          <p><b>Guard Installation:</b> * <b>Action:</b> Install "Finger Guards" at the pinch points where the belt meets the end rollers. These should be cut from 1/8" clear polycarbonate for visibility.</p>
        </li>
      </ul>
    ]]></field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_36"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
  </record>
</odoo>
