<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 data-oe-version="2.0">Odoo for Sport Events</h1>
        <p>Welcome to the Odoo Sport Event Management package!</p>
        <p>Whether you're organizing marathons and trail runs, triathlons, or competitive tournaments, Odoo centralizes every part of your operation. From planning and vendor coordination to material inventory, event publishing, sponsorships, and staff scheduling, Odoo empowers sports event professionals with fully integrated tools.</p>
        <p>Odoo centralizes every part of your operation. From organizing events and syncing with sponsors and partners to managing event materials with inventory and scheduling staff, Odoo empowers sports event professionals with fully integrated tools.</p>
        <p>Odoo improves team coordination, boosts your event's online presence, and ensures that every piece of your event runs smoothly; so you can focus on delivering an unforgettable experience for sport lovers, partners, and spectators.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>Basics</h2>
        <p>You can access every installed app in your Odoo database from your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Events</font></strong>: Plan and manage sport competitions, races, or tournaments.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website</font></strong>: Promote events, sell tickets, and gather sponsorships online.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase</font>: </strong>Order ravitaillement supplies, gear, equipment, and other essentials for sport events.<strong></strong><br/></p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Inventory</font></strong>: Track sports gear, event equipment, merchandise, and manage stock of all materials.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font></strong>: Manage relationships with sponsors, partners, and key contacts.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Project</font></strong>: Organize event planning, deadlines, and task responsibilities.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Planning</font></strong>: Create staff schedules, assign roles, and manage shifts.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Documents</font></strong>: Centralize spreadsheets and materials checklists.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sign</font></strong>: Digitally sign sponsorship agreements or volunteer forms.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Survey</font></strong>: Gather feedback from participants, staff, and sponsors.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Use Case</p>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Sport Events Package </strong>and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Organize Your Sport Events</h3>
        <p>Plan and launch your sport event using <em>Project</em>, <em>CRM</em>, <em>Events</em>, and <em>Website.</em></p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Set up a project</strong> in the <em>Project</em> app to assign and track tasks such as venue booking, course setup, and sponsor contact.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Add your event details</strong> in the <em>Events</em> app, including dates, locations, ticket types, and capacity.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Record and manage sponsor details</strong> in <em>CRM </em>and add them on the<em> Event </em>when it's confirmed</p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        <p>In <em>CRM</em>, create a new opportunity for each sponsor or partner. Record all discussions, meeting notes, and agreed conditions.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Once terms are approved, send the sponsorship contract via the <em>Sign</em> app for a quick, legally binding e-signature.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>In the <em>Events</em> app, open your event and use the <em>Sponsor Smart Button</em> to add the confirmed sponsor. Upload their logo and details.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Use the <em>Website</em> app to promote sponsors with their logos, descriptions, and (if relevant) booth details so attendees know where to find them.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Assign<strong> </strong>booths or areas for sponsors. For example, Sports sponsors your trail race. They have a booth at the finish line where they sell running equipment and promote their latest trail gear. </p>
                    </li>
                </ol>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Publish the event</strong> on your <em>Website</em> with an attractive description, photos or videos from previous editions, practical info such as schedules and accessibility, and registration forms.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <ul>
                    <li>Add specific questions to the registration form in the <em>Events</em> app, such as emergency contact details or T-shirt size, so you collect all necessary information from participants during the registration process.</li>
                    <li>Use the Barcode app to scan tickets and give participants their race bibs or event packs easily.</li>
                    <li>Create pricelists  to offer specific prices tailored to different groups, such as partners, athletes with a license, or staff members. </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Purchase Your Event Materials</h3>
        <p>Streamline purchasing for sport event supplies using the <em>Purchase</em> app.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create a purchase order</strong> in <em>Purchase</em> when you need ravitaillement supplies, race bibs, signage, timing systems, volunteer uniforms, or safety equipment.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Select the right vendor</strong> by comparing prices, delivery times, and supplier reliability to ensure quality and timely delivery.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Send a Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> to suppliers directly from Odoo or confirm the order when you've made your choice.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Track the order</strong> in <em>Purchase</em> to monitor expected delivery dates.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Receive the goods</strong> using the <em>Receipt</em> smart button and validate them to update your records.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Manage Your Sport Material Inventory</h3>
        <p>Keep sports gear and event materials organized with the <em>Inventory</em> app.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Open the Inventory app</strong> and find the product or equipment to manage (e.g., finish line arch, water station tables, first aid kits).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Categorize products</strong> into groups like Apparel, First Aid, Technical Equipment, and Merchandise.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Organize  and Monitor stock by locations</strong>: Create clear storage locations in Odoo such as <em>Merch &amp; Apparel</em>, <em>Ravito</em>, and <em>Equipment</em>. This helps you and your team find materials quickly when setting up for the event.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Use Smart Buttons</strong> to view stock moves and track the history of each item.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Set Reordering Rules</strong> by defining minimum and maximum stock levels. Example: Keep at least 200 gels in stock, and replenish up to 500 when you drop below the threshold.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Automate reordering</strong> so when stock falls below the minimum, Odoo generates a purchase order automatically.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <ul>
                    <li> Add vendor lead times on each product to plan ahead. For example, if importing race medals takes 10 days, set that lead time so you order in time.</li>
                    <li>Export your inventory list from Odoo to a spreadsheet and create a column for “Quantity Required” for a specific event. Event managers can fill in this column so the Inventory Manager can compare it with “Quantity on Hand” and instantly know what needs to be reordered.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Keep Your Community Engaged with Your Website</h3>
        <p>Promote new events and connect with your community using the <em>Website app</em>.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create engaging announcements </strong>and highlight reels to promote upcoming events.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Add contact forms </strong>for participants to send questions, feedback, or requests.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Showcase your value proposition and current sponsors</strong> with logos, testimonials, and success stories. Include a sponsor interest form that, when submitted, automatically creates an opportunity in the CRM. This allows your team to track sponsor activity, follow up effectively, and work toward converting them into long-term partners.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Schedule Your Staff</h3>
        <p>Assign and communicate staff roles via the <em>Planning</em> app.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Build Shift Schedule:</strong></li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>Define your event hours (e.g., 7am–8pm, race day and setup days)</li>
                    <li>Create roles like “Security,” “Medical Staff,” “Registration Desk,” or “Course Marshal,” and assign them to each team member’s record, on <em>Employee</em> app</li>
                    <li>Use the auto-plan feature to assign staff based on their availability and expertise.</li>
                </ol>
            </li>
            <li><strong>Communicate Efficiently</strong></li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>Each staff member can view their schedule via their portal or receive it by email</li>
                    <li>Need to make last-minute changes? Drag-and-drop scheduling updates keep everyone informed instantly.</li>
                </ol>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Handle Invoices and Expenses</h3>
        <p>Manage event finances with the Invoicing and Expenses apps.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Log expenses</strong> like staff accommodation the day before the event, catering, or travel.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Categorize expenses</strong> (Logistics, Accommodation, Meals, Travel) for clear reporting.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Generate invoices</strong> for sponsors, partners, or booth rentals.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Track payments</strong> and send reminders for overdue invoices.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Send Surveys to Stay Connected</h3>
        <p>Collect feedback using the Survey app.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create surveys</strong> on event organization, facilities, or satisfaction.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Send them to participants,</strong> staff, and sponsors after the event.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Analyze responses</strong> to improve future events (e.g., add more ravitaillement points) or to use them to demonstrate the event's impact on local tourism when negotiating new editions or funding.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Example Workflow for a Sport Event</h3>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Project app</strong></font> to organize the event by creating tasks, assigning assignees, setting deadlines, and tracking progress.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Create the event in the<strong> </strong><font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Events app</strong></font> with all details (dates, locations, ticket types, and capacity) and, after negotiating sponsorship deals in <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>CRM</strong></font> and finalizing contracts in <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sign</font></strong>, add confirmed sponsors with their booth locations.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Promote the event on the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Website</strong></font> with sponsor logos, descriptions, media from previous editions, practical info, and ticket registration.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Check your entire <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">inventory</font></strong>, update the spreadsheet with the quantities required for the event, and identify any shortages.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Based on that list, the logistic manager can reorder missing items by creating purchase orders in <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase</font></strong> for essentials like hydration points, signage, and timing equipment.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign staff shifts in <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Planning</strong></font> for setup, race marshaling, registration, and cleanup.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Run the event: thanks to the inventory list, the logistics manager knows exactly what to bring; use the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Barcode</strong></font> app to scan participant tickets and assign bib numbers; check your staff planning and enjoy the event.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Send a post-event survey via <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Survey</strong></font> to participants and partners, then review income and expenses in <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing </font><span style="font-weight: normal;">and</span><font class="text-o-color-1"> Expenses </font></strong>before closing the project.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>Do You Want to Go Further?</h2>
        <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your Sport Event company:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Manage all event-related finances seamlessly using the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting</font></strong> app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Set up a <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale (PoS)</font></strong> system to sell food, drinks, and merchandise on-site with integrated stock tracking.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Leverage <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Social Marketing</font></strong><font class="bg-o-color-3 text-o-color-1">​</font> to share event highlights and engage your audience online.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Integrate <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">WhatsApp </font><font class="text-o-color-2"><span style="font-weight: normal;">and/or</span></font><font class="text-o-color-1"> VoIP</font></strong> to communicate instantly with your team during the event.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Offer <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">memberships or subscriptions</font></strong> for regular access to your events.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>

  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Odoo for Sport Events</field>
    <field name="icon">🏅</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_25"/>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
