<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo auto_sequence="1">
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1 class="oe-hint">Food distribution</h1>
    <p>Hello there!</p>
    <p>You just installed the Odoo for <strong>Food distribution</strong> package. By doing so, we
      have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your business efficiently.</p>
    <p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve
      your experience.</p>
    <div data-oe-role="status"
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
      contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo
          data and try the Demo - Use Case (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
    <br />
    <br />
    <h1>
      <strong>Basics</strong>
    </h1>
    <hr />
    <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Use the <strong>Manufacturing App</strong> to efficiently plan and execute production
        orders to meet customer demand.</li>
      <li>Process manufacturing work orders with instructions from the <strong>Shopfloor App</strong>
        .</li>
      <li>Manage the purchase of raw materials from the <strong>Purchase App</strong>.</li>
      <li>From the <strong>Inventory App</strong>, keep track of produced lots and expiration dates.</li>
      <li>Generate crystal clear quotations with the <strong>Sales App</strong>.</li>
      <li>Invoice your customers from the <strong>Invoicing App</strong>.</li>
    </ul>
    <br />
    <br />
    <h1>
      <strong>Use case</strong>
    </h1>
    <hr />
    <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products, sale
      orders and more.</p>
    <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you
      can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
    <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to
      add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
    <div data-oe-role="status"
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
      contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal"
        aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade
          your Bar &amp; Pub package and check the related box</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <br />
    <h3>📜 Managing orders</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>From the <strong>Sales App</strong>, you can manage your orders.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>You are ready to sign your first customers? To do so, open the Sales App, create a new
        order and the customer.</li>
      <li>Fill in the form by creating or selecting a customer contact.</li>
      <li>Select a quotation template to save time for an installation.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Save time preparing the quotation templates which correspond to your frequent segments!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
      <li>Send your quotation for online signature.</li>
      <li>Confirm the order to close your deal.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>You can now hurry to manufacture the needed products, deliver them prior sending the invoice
      to bill your customer.</p>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html"
        class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Sales</a>
    </p>
    <br />
    <h3>🗓️ Planning your production</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Whether you want to plan your production based on existing sales orders, or based on a
      forecast, you can use the master production schedule from the <strong>Manufacturing App</strong>
      .</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the Master Production Schedule from the Planning menu.<br />Don't panic, this will become
        your best buddy to optimize your production!</li>
      <li>First, you might want to fill in your estimated Forecasted Demand for your finished
        products, in this case, Mayonnaise Bucket and Dispenser.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>A good practice might be to keep those forecasts up to date for the coming months with
          your sales, so that the manufacturing team plans at best the production at all time
          accordingly!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
      <li>Depending on your current stock level, an appropriate replenishment suggestion will be
        created for the final product and its components via the indirect demand, for instance here:
        the Bucket and the Dispenser, as well as the Mayonnaise down below.</li>
      <li>When hovering the on the Order button for a product Replenishment, a cell is highlighted.
        Clicking this button orders the corresponding product for that period according to the
        Replenishment input.<br />This creates a manufacturing order or a purchase order depending
        on the product configuration.</li>
      <li>There is some stock of Buckets and Dispensers so no need to order some for the ongoing
        period.<br />However, you need to order Mayonnaise Buckets to meet your forecast!</li>
      <li>Doing so, you have generated a new manufacturing order which is now visible for your
        operators. </li>
      <li>Also order the Mayonnaise so you can fill those buckets with sauce.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success"
        aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You can see that the replenishment for the Mayonnaise comes as multiple of the batch
          size. You can adjust this editing the Mayonnaise Production Schedule from the pen icon
          near its name.</p>
        <p>This is great but you might be producing more Mayonnaise than you planned to package...</p>
        <p>No worries, simply increase the Replenishment for a product packaging Mayonnaise to grow
          the indirect demand of Mayonnaise just below your Actual Replenishment.<br />This way, you
          make sure to package all you can, to deliver your customers according to your forecast,
          and have some buffer to start from next month. </p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p>Now let's see how spread the work load from the resulting manufacturing orders.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the list of manufacturing orders from the Operations menu.</li>
      <li>Open the Mayonnaise Bucket for example since packaging such a quantity may not happen in
        one day.</li>
      <li>Near its name, click the gear icon and select the split option.<br />Define the Max Batch
        Size to correspond typically to the packaging of a Mayonnaise tank, 35 buckets in for
        example.</li>
      <li>Define dates to plan those smaller orders along the corresponding period to smoothen the
        load and then proceed to the split.<br />As a result, the initial order has been split into
        multiple smaller orders.</li>
      <li>Now come back to the list of manufacturing orders and open the calendar view from the top
        right hand side.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>The Gantt view is available as well for even more intelligible planning from version 19.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
      <li>Drag and drop manufacturing orders to spread evenly the load between Mayonnaise
        manufacturing and packaging into buckets and dispensers.<br   />You're all set for production!</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary"
        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/manufacturing.html">🎓
        Manufacturing</a>
    </p>
    <br />
    <h3>🥘 Manufacturing quality products</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Some plan, others produce... Open the <strong>Shop Floor App</strong> to manufacture
      products.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>All Manufacturing Orders here are Ready to manufacture by default but you can play with
        the filters at top right of the screen to see them all.</li>
      <li>Click on one of the Ready orders to produce some Mayonnaise.</li>
      <li>Follow the step from each operation to prepare your Mayonnaise batch.</li>
      <li>Click the Close Production button at the end of the tile when done with all steps. Great
        you manufactured you first Mayonnaise batch!</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success"
        aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You registered your first lot of Mayonnaise. Note that it is possible to change the lot
          number prefix from the product form, in the Inventory tab.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
      <li>Let's now package the Mayonnaise now: Click on a Mayonnaise Bucket order to start the
        packaging.</li>
      <li>Follow as well the steps and close the production. Great, you now have some products to
        ship to delight customers.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You can setup your Bill of Material to reflect on you production processes with or
          without steps, with embedded quality checks like in this example or after a production.</p>
        <p>The Bill of Material is accessible from the Manufacturing App Products menu.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>The Mixing tank work center is configured with setup and cleanup time. Take advantage of
          this capability to optimize your operations!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p>
      <a
        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/manufacturing/shop_floor/shop_floor_overview.html"
        class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Shop Floor</a>
    </p>
    <br />
    <h3>📦 Managing your supplies</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Producing efficiently is key for your business and doing so without running out of supplies
      is paramount. Let's open the <strong>Inventory App</strong> to see how to handle this aspect.</p>
    <h5>Replenishment Rules</h5>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the Replenishment from Operations menu.</li>
      <li>Some rules are defined to easily resupply ingredients and containers.</li>
      <li>You can see you're about to get low on Vinegar and Mustard in the Forecast.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You can see the forecast clicking the chart icon. Down below, you can see that this is
          the
          outcome of all the planned Manufacturing Orders...</p>
        <p>As an Inventory Manager you need to make sure that the production team never runs out of
          supply!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
      <li>On the Vinager Replenishment rule, hit the Order button. This creates a Purchase Order for
        this product according to the min and max input, which you can edit. Hit the Order button
        for
        Mustard while you're here to add those items to the recent Purchase Order.</li>
      <li>Having to follow up on supplies stock might be a repetitive task and you might forget...
        To
        help you with that, you can automate those orders. Filter on Auto Trigger in the left hand
        side tab to see already automated Replenishment Rules. Those rules will be triggered
        automatically to ensure you never run out of containers, that would be a shame to through
        away tasty Mayonnaise by lack of Buckets...</li>
    </ul>
    <h5>Expiration Dates</h5>
    <ul>
      <li>While you are using <strong>Inventory App</strong>, open the product catalog from the
        Products menu. This gives you a more comprehensive view of the different products you
        manipulate.</li>
      <li>Open one of the finished product and navigate to the Inventory tab.</li>
      <li>Here you can find some logistical data to optimize your deliveries.</li>
      <li>The Dates section allows you to detail the expiration dates of your products.</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success"
        aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Between production and deliveries, by default, the product picking is organized in FIFO.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h5>Purchase Orders</h5>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the <strong>Purchase App </strong>and the recently created Purchase Order.</li>
      <li>The products from the Replenishment Rules you triggered are here but not all products have
        Replenishment Rules at this stage. For some products or other suppliers you need, you can
        chose to add them manually to a Purchase Order and even create new Purchase Orders.</li>
      <li>Add some Salt and Sugar to secure suppliers for longer on those sides.</li>
      <li>Now Send the Request For Quotation to your supplier if willing to iterate on price for
        example.</li>
      <li>Confirm the Purchase Order when in agreement with your supplier.</li>
      <li>There now is a smart button at the top of the Purchase Order to reach the associated
        delivery. Hit the Deliveries smart button to open the delivery.</li>
      <li>When the truck arrives and you add those to your stock, validate the delivery to update
        your stock levels. Don't forget to set the Lot reference in the details of the delivery
        lines. You're now ready to product Mayonnaise for some time!</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>To save time and prevent mistake of typo in the Lot inputs, you might want to work with <strong>Barcode
          App</strong>!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p>
      <a
        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html"
        class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Inventory</a>
      <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary"
        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase.html">🎓
        Purchase</a>
    </p>
    <br />
    <h3>💸 Invoicing your customers</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>One last step prior billing with the <strong>Invoicing App</strong>, delivering!</p>
    <ul>
      <li>From the Sale Order you confirmed, you can find a smart button to the associated delivery
        at the top.</li>
      <li>Validate the delivery to your customer to complete the job.</li>
      <li>Now come back to the Sale Order which you can bill since delivered.</li>
      <li>Create an Invoice, send it to your customer and confirm it to get paid for your hard work!</li>
    </ul>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info"
        aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Working on your pricing to optimize your margin? You leverage the "Compute Price from
          BoM" action available from the Product form or any Products list.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p>
      <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary"
        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">🎓
        Invoicing</a>
    </p>
    <br />
    <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"></p>
    <div data-oe-role="status"
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
      contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal"
        aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo
          setup to fit your business needs.</p>
        <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a
            href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation﻿</a> and <a
            href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free to <a
            href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h2></h2>
    <br />
    <br />
    <h1>
      <strong>Do you want to go further?</strong>
    </h1>
    <hr />
    <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Leverage the<strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1"> Barcode App</font>
        </strong> to manipulate products
        and serials without mistake.</li>
      <li>Take advantage of the power of <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">Manufacturing App</font>
        </strong> with Manufacture To
        Order (MTO) capabilities.</li>
      <li>Use the <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">Maintenance App</font>
        </strong> to keep all your work
        centers up and running.</li>
      <li>Introduce more capabilities from the <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">Quality App</font>
        </strong> to meet the requirements
        from your market.</li>
      <li>Setup your website for free and get leads passively with <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">Website App </font>
        </strong>and <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">CRM App</font>
        </strong>!</li>
      <li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment in <strong>
          <font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font>
        </strong>.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
    <div data-oe-role="status"
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
      contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal"
        aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
        <p>
          <a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a>
        </p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h1></h1>
    <br />
    <br />
    <h1>
      <strong>Final word</strong>
    </h1>
    <hr />
    <p>You might have tested this package with or without demo data. In any case, you may have
      written records in journals which are not deletable and which might be an issue for your
      traceability.</p>
    <div
      class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
      data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success"
        aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>
          <strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then to create a
            new one for your own usage.</strong>
        </p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </template>

  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Food distribution</field>
    <field name="icon">🥫</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
  </record>
</odoo>
