<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1><strong>Odoo for Pet Groomers</strong></h1>
        <p>
            Odoo helps pet grooming businesses run smoothly by centralizing appointments, pets, sales, and inventory in one
            integrated system. From booking a grooming session to tracking each pet’s history and completing payments, Odoo
            reduces manual work and lets you focus on delivering great care to pets and their owners.
        </p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><br/></h2>
        <h2>Basics</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Appointments</strong> – Let customers book grooming services online with predefined services and
                availability.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Calendar</strong> – Visualize and manage grooming sessions, staff schedules, and availability in one
                place.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Pets</strong> – Store detailed profiles for each pet, including breed, size, notes, and grooming
                history.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Sales</strong> – Create service orders, manage pricing, and prepare transactions before payment.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Point of Sale</strong> – Quickly charge grooming services and retail products at the counter.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Inventory</strong> – Track grooming products, retail items, and stock levels in real time.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><br/></p>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Appointments 📅</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The Appointments application allows pet grooming businesses to offer online booking for their services while
            maintaining full control over availability, durations, and working hours.
        </p>
        <p>
            Customers can easily choose a grooming service, select a suitable time slot, and confirm their visit without calling
            the salon. This reduces administrative workload while ensuring bookings automatically follow your operational rules.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    Define <strong>grooming services</strong> such as wash, haircut, nail trimming, or full grooming packages.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Set the<strong> duration per service</strong>, and define working hours.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Let customers <strong>book online</strong> from your website or a shared booking link.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Automatically capture customer details during booking.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Reduce missed appointments with <strong>automatic confirmations and reminders</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Create a professional, self-service booking experience without staff intervention.</p></li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/appointments.html" class="btn btn-primary">Appointment Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Calendar 🗓️</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The Calendar module provides a clear, real-time overview of all grooming sessions, making it easy to see who is
            working on what and when. It centralizes appointments in a visual layout, helping grooming teams stay coordinated,
            avoid overlaps, and quickly adapt to schedule changes throughout the day.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Automatically display appointments booked through <strong>Appointments</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign <strong>specific groomers</strong> to sessions.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Identify busy periods and underused time slots.</p></li>
            <li><p>Coordinate multiple groomers working in parallel.</p></li>
            <li><p>Avoid double-booking rooms, equipment, or staff.</p></li>
            <li><p>Quickly reschedule appointments with drag-and-drop.</p></li>
            <li><p>Synchronize your calendar with Google Calendar or Outlook Calendar for easy access on the go</p></li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar.html" class="btn btn-primary">Calendar Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Pets 🐾</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The Pets application allows groomers to maintain detailed profiles for every animal they care for, shifting the
            focus from transactions to long-term pet care. Each profile stores essential information such as breed, size,
            behavior notes, and grooming history, enabling consistent and personalized service at every visit.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create <strong>one profile per pet</strong>, linked to its owner.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Record breed, size, age, temperament, and special handling notes.</p></li>
            <li><p>Store allergies, skin conditions, or grooming restrictions.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Link pets directly to <strong>appointments and sales orders</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Review previous grooming sessions to maintain consistency.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Serve households with <strong>multiple pets</strong> more efficiently.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            This app shifts your business from customer-centric to <strong>pet-centric</strong>, which dramatically improves
            service quality.
        </p>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="image.png" src="/web/image/pet_groomer.ir_attachment_1309"/>
        </p>
        <h2><br/></h2>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Sales 💼</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The Sales module helps grooming businesses formalize services into clear, structured orders before payment. It
            allows groomers to define what was provided during a session, add optional treatments or products, and ensure
            pricing is transparent and consistent across customers.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create a <strong>sales order</strong> from the appointment.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Add grooming services as line items.</p></li>
            <li><p>Include optional extras like special shampoos or treatments.</p></li>
            <li><p>Adjust pricing based on pet size, coat condition, or time spent.</p></li>
            <li><p>Maintain a clear breakdown of what was provided.</p></li>
            <li><p>Keep a traceable document before checkout.</p></li>
        </ul>
        <p>The Sales module acts as the commercial bridge between grooming services and payment.</p>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-primary"
                >Sales Documentation</a
            >
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><strong>Tip</strong></p>
                <p>
                    Go to Settings > Sales > Quotation Templates to make selecting quotation templates available to everyone in just one click, in any Sales Order.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Point of Sale 🧾</strong></h2>
        <p>
            Point of Sale allows grooming salons to complete transactions quickly and efficiently at the counter. It is designed
            for fast service, enabling staff to charge grooming sessions and retail products in a single flow while supporting
            multiple payment methods.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Convert the <strong>sales order</strong> into a POS transaction.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Accept cash, card, or other digital payment methods.</p></li>
            <li><p>Sell grooming services and retail products in one checkout.</p></li>
            <li><p>Apply discounts, promotions, or loyalty benefits.</p></li>
            <li><p>Issue printed or digital receipts instantly.</p></li>
            <li><p>Speed up queues during busy hours.</p></li>
        </ul>
        <p>This ensures a smooth, professional end to the customer experience.</p>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-primary">Point of Sale Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <hr />
        <h2><strong>Purchase &amp; Inventory 📦</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The Purchase application enables users to quickly send requests for quotations, compare vendor prices, and confirm
            purchases that are tracked in the Inventory application.
        </p>
        <p>
            The Inventory application gives grooming businesses full visibility over the products they sell and consume daily.
            It tracks stock movements in real time, ensuring essential supplies such as shampoos or accessories are always
            available when needed.
        </p>
        <p><strong>How it’s used in a grooming business:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li><p>Track shampoos, conditioners, brushes, treats, and accessories.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Automatically reduce stock when items are sold through <strong>POS</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Consume products internally during grooming services.</p></li>
            <li><p>Monitor minimum stock levels for critical supplies.</p></li>
            <li><p>Identify best-selling retail products.</p></li>
            <li><p>Prevent overstocking or emergency reorders.</p></li>
        </ul>
        <p>Inventory connects operational usage with financial visibility.</p>
        <p>
            <a
                href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html" class="btn btn-primary">Purchase &amp; Inventory Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p><br/></p>
        <div
            data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <h2><strong>Tips for success</strong></h2>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Go through <strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides">Odoo's eLearning</a></strong> videos for great
                        tips on how to use each different app
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Don't neglect marketing! Odoo offers a comprehensive marketing suite for email marketing and social
                        media accounts.
                    </li>
                    <li>Create automatic resupply rules for stock that is running low</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sign</strong> – Digitally manage consent forms, liability waivers, and service approvals.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Planning</strong> – Organize employee shifts, workload distribution, and time-off.</p>
            </li>
            <li><strong>HR Apps </strong>- Manage employees, recruitment, and time off using Odoo’s HR suite.</li>
            <li><strong>Survey</strong> - Track client satisfaction &amp; feedback using Odoo Survey</li>
        </ul>
        <div
            data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Pet Groomers</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_10"/>
        <field name="icon">🐾</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>
  </odoo>
