<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
      <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0">Driving School</h1>
      <p>Hello there!</p>
      <p>You just installed the Odoo for Driving School package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your Driving School efficiently.</p>
      <p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
          <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
              <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Demo - Use Case (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h1><strong>Basics</strong></h1>
      <hr />
      <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
      <ul>
          <li>Sell lessons, exams and packs from the <strong>Sales App</strong></li>
          <li>Manage waiver with the <strong>Sign App</strong></li>
          <li>Let your customers book lessons online thanks to the<strong> Appointment App</strong></li>
          <li>Manage your employees' shifts with the <strong>Planning App</strong></li>
          <li>Manage your vehicles with the <strong>Fleet App</strong></li>
          <li>Generate visibility through the <strong>Website App</strong></li>
      </ul>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h1><strong>Use case</strong></h1>
      <hr />
      <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products, sale orders and more.</p>
      <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
      <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
          <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
              <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Driving School package and check the related box</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h3>📜 Sell and consume</h3>
      <hr />
      <p>From the <strong>Sales App</strong>, you can manage your orders.</p>
      <h5>Sell packs</h5>
      <ul>
          <li>You are ready to sign your first customers? To do so, open the Sales App, create a new order and the customer.</li>
          <li>Fill in the form by creating or selecting a customer contact.</li>
          <li>Select a quotation template to save time for a B driving license for example.</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>Save time preparing the quotation templates which correspond to your frequent segments!</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <ul>
          <li>Send your quotation for online signature.</li>
          <li>Confirm the order to close your deal and then create and confirm the invoice to bill your customer.</li>
          <li>You can then grant the learner access to your portal to book lessons from the Contact form, via the gear icon near the contact name.</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>
                  When selling products such as packs, this credits loyalty cards which points will be consumed during lessons and exams.<br />
                  You can configure those from the Sales / Products / Discounts &amp; Loyalty menu.
              </p>
              <p>Note that the quotation templates with packs of hours will as well charge the loyalty cards.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🌐</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>
                  The website is as well configured with eCommerce App.<br />
                  This means that customers can directly buy packs, and lessons from your website and then book lessons!
              </p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <h5>Lessons and exams</h5>
      <p>
          When a customer comes for a lesson paid ahead, it's time to consume it from his loyalty card.<br />
          You can book lessons from the Appointment App and make learner pay as follow, or let them book lessons by themselves as described in below section.
      </p>
      <ul>
          <li>Open the lesson to be booked from the Appointment App.</li>
          <li>On its calendar view, create a new booking adjusting dates and contact.</li>
          <li>Then open the Sales App and create a new sale order for this customer but this time add the product corresponding to the lesson or exam.</li>
          <li>At the bottom of the quotation, click the Reward button and chose the applicable reward, which brings the quotation total to zero.</li>
          <li>Confirm the order to consume this lesson from the loyalty card and let your customer in!</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>You can as well directly create quotes for one lesson without having to use the loyalty card.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Sales</a></p>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h3>📝 Get signed waivers</h3>
      <hr />
      <p>To manage waivers, we take advantage of the <strong>Sign App </strong>from the customer form.</p>
      <ul>
          <li>Open the <strong>Contact App </strong>and create a new customer record filling in especially the email address.</li>
          <li>Save your new contact.</li>
          <li>Click the gear icon near the contact name and reach the Request Signature popup.</li>
          <li>Select as template the waiver to be signed and Send it for signature.</li>
      </ul>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>You can define your own waiver form from the Sign App, within the templates.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <ul>
          <li>While the document is pending for signature, you can reach if from the smart button at the top of the contact form labelled Signature Requested and Resend the request.</li>
          <li>Once your customer has signed the waiver, a message captures the signed document in the contact chatter!</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>The Contact chatter is the best way for you to interact seamlessly with your customers sending them emails. This turns out very handy to plan exam sessions with traceability!</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <p>
          <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/essentials/contacts.html">🎓 Contacts</a>
          <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/sign.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Sign</a>
      </p>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h3>📆 Lessons' booking</h3>
      <hr />
      <p>To help you planning lessons without the hurdle of assigning slots to learners, <strong>Appointments App </strong>will expose self bookable appointments.</p>
      <h5>Lesson appointments</h5>
      <ul>
          <li>Open the <strong>Appointments App</strong> to see all appointments made available to your customers.</li>
          <li>
              Note that the Projection Room resource is used by all theory lessons and if you open this resource from the Configuration / Resources menu, it is shareable, meaning multiple bookings can book a slot. This is obviously not the case
              for vehicles.<br />
              On the other hand, practice lessons rely on instructors assuming each instructor has a vehicle available to provide a lesson.
          </li>
      </ul>
      <h5>Booking a lesson</h5>
      <ul>
          <li>To book an lesson, learner would first have to buy some lessons to have pre-paid lessons on their loyalty cards. Then they can reach the website and click the Schedule an appointment button.</li>
          <li>Click the book now button of one of the A driving license lesson and select a slot prior proceeding to payment.</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">▶️</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>Your account is provided with pre-paid lessons for B license to be able to test the flow.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <ul>
          <li>During the payment stage users can either directly pay for the lesson or use the appropriate claim button to leverage the prepaid lessons associated to their account when they are logged in.</li>
          <li>Once confirmed, the appointment is booked!</li>
      </ul>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>From the portal, learners can access their lesson bookings, their orders and most importantly their balance of lessons and exams!</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/appointments.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Appointments</a></p>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h3>🎓 Instructor management</h3>
      <hr />
      <p>To help you planning lessons without the hurdle of assigning slots to learners, Appointments App will expose self bookable appointments. Let's see how instructors can use <strong>Calendar App </strong>then to know their planning.</p>
      <h5>Planning</h5>
      <ul>
          <li>As any user, including instructors, the calendar App provides a view of booked appointments.</li>
      </ul>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>In order to let instructors adapt their time, the appointments for practice lessons are setup with a pre-booking time of 4 days. Feel free to update this per you needs.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p>You can <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar/google.html">sync your Odoo Calendar</a> with others like Google and Outlook.</p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <h5>Leaves</h5>
      <p>When an instructor takes some time off, you can prevent the booking of appointments during this period.</p>
      <ul>
          <li>Open the Appointments App, and go to the Leaves from the Configuration menu.</li>
          <li>Create a new leave selecting the appropriate resource.</li>
          <li>Save the leave and voila, no more appointments can be booked with this instructor!</li>
      </ul>
      <p>
          <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar.html">🎓 Calendar</a>
          <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/appointments.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Appointments</a>
      </p>
      <p><br /></p>
      <h3>🚙 Fleet management</h3>
      <hr />
      <p>The <strong>Fleet App</strong> is tailored to help you manage your vehicles.</p>
      <ul>
          <li>Open the Fleet App to see all your vehicles.</li>
          <li>You can update the Odometer on a regular basis to better plan you maintenance from the smart button of each vehicle.</li>
          <li>The models; defined from the Configuration menu, allows you typically to capture the different vehicles you have.</li>
          <li>
              Follow up on services planning maintenance and repairs from a vehicle.<br />
              You can as well access the list of services from the Fleet menu.
          </li>
      </ul>
      <p><a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/hr/fleet.html">🎓 Fleet</a></p>
      <p><br /></p>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
          <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
              <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
              <p>
                  Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free to
                  <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!
              </p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <h2><br /></h2>
      <h1><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></h1>
      <hr />
      <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
      <ul>
          <li>
              Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment i<font class="text-o-color-5">n </font><strong><font class="text-o-color-5">Accounting App</font></strong><font class="text-o-color-5">.</font>
          </li>
          <li>Open the door for more custom workflows and actions with the power of <strong>Studio App</strong>.</li>
      </ul>
      <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
      <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
          <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
          <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
              <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
              <p><a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <h1><br /></h1>
      <h1><strong>Final word</strong></h1>
      <hr />
      <p>You might have tested this package with or without demo data.</p>
      <p>In any case, you may have written records in journals which are not deleteable and which might be an issue for your traceability.</p>
      <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
          <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
          <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
              <p><strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then to create a new one for your own usage.</strong></p>
          </div>
      </div>
      <p><br /></p>
      <div
          style="
              box-sizing: border-box;
              color: rgb(55, 65, 81);
              font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Ubuntu, 'Noto Sans', Arial, 'Odoo Unicode Support Noto', sans-serif, 'Apple Color Emoji', 'Segoe UI Emoji', 'Segoe UI Symbol', 'Noto Color Emoji';
              font-size: 14px;
              font-style: normal;
              font-variant-ligatures: normal;
              font-variant-caps: normal;
              font-weight: 400;
              letter-spacing: normal;
              orphans: 2;
              text-align: start;
              text-indent: 0px;
              text-transform: none;
              widows: 2;
              word-spacing: 0px;
              -webkit-text-stroke-width: 0px;
              white-space: normal;
              background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);
              text-decoration-thickness: initial;
              text-decoration-style: initial;
              text-decoration-color: initial;
          "
          class="oe-hint">
          <br />
      </div>      
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Driving School</field>
        <field name="icon">🚙</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="1"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">34.199999999999996</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
