<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Odoo for Photographers</h1>
        <p>
            This industry is designed for small photography studios, including freelancers and small organizations. It is built to cater to both corporate clients (team building events, professional events, product photography) and individual
            clients (weddings, family events, pregnancy shoots, pet shoots, etc.).
        </p>
        <h1>External Events</h1>
        <h2>Lead generation and management</h2>
        <h3>Through the website</h3>
        <p>From the website, a potential client can ask for a quote or simply get in touch. They can fill some extra details about their needs:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>What they're looking for</li>
            <li>Their contact information</li>
            <li>... And other information</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can add as many fields as you want to the contact form. Simply visit the page editor, and click "Add field" after selecting the form.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html">Website documentation</a>
            <a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html">CRM Management</a>
        </p>
        <h3>Email alias</h3>
        <p>
            Leads can also come via email using. You can assign an email alias to your CRM to get a handy overview of all your customer enquiries. Once a lead has been created, you can use it as a central point from where you can reach your
            customer. Any reply they send will directly arrive in the opportunity's page!
        </p>
        <h3>Quote</h3>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            After qualification through a call or meeting, a quote can be generated detailing the services required.
        </p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br /></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            Clients can sign online to confirm the quote. You can use the quotation templates service packages you may sell often. You can also assign template emails, add sections to your quotes, and specific terms and conditions! Don't hesitate
            to customize them to your liking.
        </p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br /></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html">Quotations &amp; Sales</a><br /></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br /></p>
        <h3>Project</h3>
        <p>
            Once a quotation is confirmed, a project is created for the shooting session.
        </p>
        <p>You can modify these template projects to suit your needs, e.g. by adding tasks to them. You don't want to use project management? Feel free to replace the product by their 'no-service' equivalent to avoid the creation of a project.</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html">Project Management</a><br /></p>
        <h2>Studio Shoots</h2>
        <h3>Lead generation</h3>
        <p>From the website or via the email alias, as above.</p>
        <h3>Quote</h3>
        <p>Once qualified (call/meeting), a quote is created for the shooting with details on schedule and expected service etc. Customer can sign online to confirm.</p>
        <h3>Appointment</h3>
        <p>
            Clients get a link to book an appointment in the template emails. This link can be sent from a Sales Order or from a Task. The client can book whatever time slot they would like from there.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Note : Website visitors can also book studio shoots directly, depending on availabilities. Don't hesitate to configure the appointment types, availabilities, and ressources (photographers) in the
                    <strong>Appointments app</strong>.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Project</h3>
        <p>Once the quote is confirmed, a project is created for the shooting session, as above.</p>
        <h2>Session image sharing</h2>
        <p>Need to share pictures with your client? You can use the Odoo "Documents" app for that. You can create new folders for each customer in which you upload your pictures, then share the folder with them.</p>
        <p><img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-02-25 at 10.50.51.png" src="photography/static/src/binary/ir_attachment/2.png" /></p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html?highlight=document">Documents</a><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    Odoo has a fair usage policy for data storage is capped at 10Gb. <br />
                    We advise you to look for alternative solutions for long term image storage.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>Invoicing</h2>
        <p>With Odoo, you get invoicing out-of-the-box! Invoice directly from your order, configure a payment provider and voilà! Your clients can pay their invoice online.</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">Invoicing</a><br /></p>
        <h2>Want to go further?</h2>
        <p>Install new Apps to do even more with Odoo! Here are a few suggestions:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Sign</strong>: send contracts to prospects and get the full traceability of their online signature</li>
            <li><strong>Accounting</strong>: do more than simple invoicing - with Odoo Accounting, you can generate tax reports, manage your invoices and bills and even synchronize payments from your bank account automatically</li>
            <li><strong>Planning</strong>: manage plannings for team members and resources, like a studio room or some hardware</li>
            <li><strong>Surveys</strong>: get your prospect to fill surveys before or after a shoot</li>
            <li><strong>Email Marketing </strong>and <strong>Social Marketing</strong> <span>: reach out to your clients regarding special events or offers, or prospect for new clients​</span><strong>​</strong>​<strong>​</strong></li>
            <li><strong>​and much more!</strong><br /></li>
        </ul>
        <p><br /></p>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Photography - Start here!</field>
        <field name="icon">📷</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_0" />
        <field name="cover_image_position">50.0</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
