<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_cover_attachment" model="ir.attachment">
        <field name="name">knowledge_cover.jpg</field>
        <field name="datas" type="base64" file="photography/static/src/binary/ir_attachment/knowledge_cover.png" />
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_cover_0" model="knowledge.cover">
        <field name="attachment_id" ref="knowledge_cover_attachment" />
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_0" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Photography - Start here!</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_0" />
        <field name="cover_image_position">50.0</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Photography</h1>
            <p>
                This app is designed for small photography studios, including freelancers and small organizations. It is
                built to cater to both corporate clients (team building events, professional events, product photography) and
                individual clients (weddings, family events, pregnancy shoots, pet shoots, etc.).
            </p>
            <h1>External Events</h1>
            <h2>Lead generation and management</h2>
            <h3>Through the website</h3>
            <p>From the website, a potential client can ask for a quote or simply get in touch. They can fill some extra details
                about their needs:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Type of shooting session/event</li>
                <li>Potential date</li>
                <li>Their contact information</li>
            </ul>
            <h3>Email alias</h3>
            <p>Leads can come via email using info@&lt;your_odoo&gt;.odoo.com.</p>
            <p>Once a lead has been created, you can use it as a central point from where you can reach your customer. Any reply
                they send will directly arrive on the lead!</p>
            <h2>Quote</h2>
            <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">After qualification through a call or meeting, a quote is generated detailing the
                event requirements. Clients can sign online to confirm the quote. You can use the quote templates (which will
                customize the emails that get sent to the customer). Don't hesitate to customize them!</p>
            <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br></p>
            <h2>Project</h2>
            <p>Once the quote is confirmed, a project is created for the shooting session. You can modify these template
                projects to suit your needs, e.g. by adding tasks to them. You don't want to use project management? Feel free
                to replace the product by their 'no-service' equivalent to avoid the creation of a project.</p>
            <h1>Studio Shoots</h1>
            <h2>Lead generation</h2>
            <p>From the website or via the email alias, as above.</p>
            <h2>Quote</h2>
            <p>Once qualified (call/meeting), a quote is created for the shooting with details on schedule and expected service
                etc. Customer can sign online to confirm.</p>
            <h2>Appointment</h2>
            <p>Clients get a link to book an appointment - this link can be sent from a Sales Order or from a Task. The link
                directly binds to the correct appointment type and is easy to remember or type manually
                (e.g.&nbsp;https://&lt;your_odoo&gt;.odoo.com/book/studio).&nbsp;The appointment page is not publicly available
                on the website, you can only register an appointment when given the link.</p>
            <p>The client can book whatever time slot they would like from there.</p>
            <h2>Project</h2>
            <p>Once the quote is confirmed, a project is created for the shooting session, as above.</p>
            <h1>Invoicing</h1>
            <p>With Odoo, you get invoicing out-of-the-box! Invoice directly from your order, configure a payment provider and
                voilà! Your clients can pay their invoice online.</p>
            <p><br></p>
            <p><br></p>
            <p><br></p>
            <h1>Want to go further?</h1>
            <p>Install new Apps to do even more with Odoo! Here are a few suggestions:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Sign</strong>:&nbsp;send contracts to prospects and get the full traceability of their online
                    signature</li>
                <li><strong>Accounting</strong>: do more than simple invoicing - with Odoo Accounting, you can generate tax
                    reports, manage your invoices and bills and even synchronize payments from your bank account automatically
                </li>
                <li><strong>Planning</strong>: manage plannings for team members and resources, like a studio room or some
                    hardware</li>
                <li><strong>Surveys</strong>:&nbsp;get your prospect to fill surveys before or after a shoot</li>
                <li data-oe-zws-empty-inline=""><strong data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">Email Marketing </strong>and <strong
                        data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">Social Marketing</strong><span data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">: reach out to
                        your clients regarding special events or offers, or prospect for new clients​</span><strong
                        data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">​</strong>​<strong data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">​</strong></li>
                <li><strong data-oe-zws-empty-inline="">​and much more!</strong><br></li>
            </ul>
            <p><br></p>
        ]]>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="admin_article_membership" model="knowledge.article.member">
        <field name="partner_id" ref="base.partner_admin" />
        <field name="article_id" ref="knowledge_article_0" />
        <field name="permission">write</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
