<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.1">Shoe Maker Services</h1>
        <p>Hello there!</p>
        <p>You just installed the Odoo for Shoe Makers package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of recommended apps to run your services efficiently.</p>
        <p>Discover the basics of this package in this article, and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to make your day-to-day more efficient to run.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <strong>Basics</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>All installed Apps are available on your Odoo homescreen. The main Apps you'll be using in your day-to-day are : </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Use the <strong>Sales App</strong> to record any new ordering.</li>
            <li>The <strong>Project App</strong> and <strong>Field Service App</strong> will ensure a great follow up of every order.</li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Point of Sale</strong> for your sales at the counter. You can also install the Odoo Web Application on your smartphone to take orders on the go. </li>
            <li>Save time managing your stock using the <strong>Inventory App</strong> and <strong>Purchase App</strong>.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h2>
            <strong>How to use this Odoo Industry Package</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>If you've added the demo data upon creating this database, it will be populated with demo products, sales orders, purchase orders, and so on. These are nice to go through the various use cases demonstrated below. </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>You can still import this industry's demo data. In order to do so, go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your "Shoe Maker" package.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>1. Managing orders</h3>
        <p>
        The <strong>Sales App </strong>is designed to help you efficiently manage your sales quotations and sales orders. You are immediately ready to welcome your first customers. To do so, open the Sales App, click "New", and add
        your customer.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>Inserting the customer's email address makes it easy for you to send them emails once their order is ready to be picked up again. </p>
                <p>You can edit the customer's contact details by clicking on the <strong>internal link </strong>(arrow)<b> </b>next to their name. </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong>Scenario 1: </strong>The simplest way to add products to an order is to directly select your services from the <strong>Product Catalog</strong>. Just click the "Product Catalog" button in your sales order lines and select
        the products you wish to sell. Note that you can filter products services by leveraging the filters in the sidebar on the left side of the screen!
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Scenario 2:</strong> Oftentimes, services are bundled together. You can toggle the "Quotation Templates" setting in your <strong>Settings app </strong>in order to create, edit and load quotation templates in your
        sales order.
        </p>
        <p>
        Once you're finished adding products and services to the sales order, all that remains is confirming it. The system then creates the appropriate tasks, that are displayed in the <strong>Smart Buttons </strong>on top of the screen.
        </p>
        <hr />
        <p>In order to get an overview of all your open tasks, just click the <strong>Project App. </strong>
        </p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the project that corresponds to your order to access all related duties.</li>
            <li>
            When working on one of those task, move the tasks in the <strong>In Progress</strong> <strong>Stage</strong>. Opening the task, you can add the product you'll be using to fulfill this task from the Products
                <strong>Smart Button</strong>  at the top - for example "outsoles" in case of outsoles replacement.
            </li>
            <li>When you're done with a task; move it to the <strong>Done Stage</strong>. </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You currently have multiple steps in your projects: New, Planned, In progress, Done and Canceled. You can configure those steps in the template project by adding, removing, renaming columns if necessary.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr />
        <p>
        Next : return to the <strong>Sales App</strong>. You can see that your first order is now ready for pick up, which is indicated by the "<strong>Ready for Pickup</strong>" checkbox. At that point, your customer has been notified by
        email that the order is ready to collect!
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                You can as well configure the process to notify your customers by SMS and Whatsapp! See the <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/studio/automated_actions.html#">automation documentation</a> and
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/whatsapp.html">Whatsapp integration documentation</a>.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
        5. When customers come back to your desk, you can easily find their order by searching in the top search bar, and by toggling the "Group by Customer" filter to display all matching customers you have. You could add
        another filter to only display orders that are ready for pickup.
        </p>
        <p>Next up : billing.</p>
        <h3>2. Billing customers</h3>
        <p>Billing efficiently your customers for their orders is paramount for your business and to help you make this as easy as possible, this Odoo package comes with the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>.
        </p>
        <ol>
            <li>From the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>, open your register.</li>
            <li>Select the <strong>customer order</strong> option to load an existing sales order</li>
            <li>If customers want some additional products, such as laces or innersoles, you can add some to their order in just a few clicks!</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Note that you can easily add services performed which were not initially planned at this stage!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
              4. Introduce the means of payment, pay and you're all done with this order!<br />
              ​5. After billing your orders from the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>, the system marks them as fully invoiced.
        </p>
        <p>Go back to your backend by clicking the "Backend" menu in the right corner, and then go to the orders from the <strong>Sales ​App </strong>to appreciate this change.</p>
        <p>At the end of your service, remember to close your register. To do so, in the Point of Sale App, select "Close Register" in the top-right menu.</p>
        <h3>3. Replenishment</h3>
        <p>
            Having available the necessary products at your fingertips is crucial to deliver orders in best delays and therefore maximize your customer satisfaction. The <strong>Inventory App</strong> and the
            <strong>Purchase App</strong> are your best levers to manage your stock efficiently.
        </p>
        <p>You have two main possibilities in Odoo to ease your replenishment process.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Scenario 1:</strong> Most products need a human assessment as the remaining quantity cannot be automatically computed. For those, a Recurring Task is created in the Project App. This task reappears every week, and you can
            personalize it with a checklist to avoid forgetting anything.
        </p>
        <p>Go to your Purchase App to easily create Requests for Proposal or Purchase Orders for products you miss or getting slim.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Scenario 2:</strong> For products that can be tracked, such as laces and soles, you can use automated purchases. To try it, confirm a new <font class="text-o-color-5">order adding i</font>
            <strong>
                <font class="text-o-color-5">
                    <span style="font-weight: normal;">nsoles with size 40-42</span>
                </font>
            </strong>
            <font class="text-o-color-5">.</font>
        </p>
        <p>
            <font class="text-o-color-5">By doing so, you have only </font>
            <strong>
                <font class="text-o-color-5">
                    <span style="font-weight: normal;">2</span>
                </font>
            </strong>
            <font class="text-o-color-5"></font>
            <strong>
                <font class="text-o-color-5">
                    <span style="font-weight: normal;">insoles</span>
                </font>
            </strong>
            <font class="text-o-color-5"> left wit</font>h that size in your stock.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🔄</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can see that there is a reordering rule configured for this product if you go to Inventory &gt; Products &gt; <font class="text-o-color-5">Insoles</font>
                </p>
                <p>
                    Reordering rules are displayed in the smart buttons on top of your product. You can see a minimum quantity, and a maximum. Each time the forecast stock lowers beneath the minimum stock, it automatically creates a purchase
                    order to replenish to the maximum quantity.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>If you navigate to your Inventory App, and go to the replenishment from the Operations menu, you can see that some products could be reordered based on those rules.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    The automated replenishment rules are triggered once a day to generate a purchase order for those products. Read our
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/warehouses_storage/replenishment.html"> Replenishment documentation </a>for more details.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>You can wait for the rules to apply, but at this stagen, let's trigger the replenishment hitting the <strong>Order</strong> button on the considered products.</p>
        <p>Next, go to your Purchase App to open the created purchase order. You can now email your <strong>Request for Quotation</strong> to your vendor or confirm it manually immediately.</p>
        <p>Once the products are there, you can click the "<strong>Receipt</strong>" smart button to validate your receipt and add these new products to your stock.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>
                    Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free to
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>This is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps and discover new features that can help you manage your shoe maker business!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>
            <strong>Do you want to go further?</strong>
        </h1>
        <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Start receiving orders directly in Odoo or go live with your
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">E-shop</font>
                </strong>
                in a few minutes.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font>
                </strong>
                )
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Marketing Automation</font>
                </strong>
                <font class="text-o-color-1">,                <strong>Email Marketing</strong>,
                </font>
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Social Media Marketing</font>
                </strong>
                , and
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing</font>
                </strong>
                .
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Shoe Maker Services</field>
        <field name="icon">👞</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
