<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.0">Shoe Maker Services</h1>
        <p>Hello there!</p>
        <p>You just installed the Odoo for Shoe Maker package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your services efficiently.</p>
        <p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Demo - Use Case (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h1><strong>Basics:</strong></h1>
        <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Use the <strong>Sales App</strong> to record any new ordering.</li>
            <li>The <strong>Project App</strong> and <strong>Field Service App</strong> will ensure a great follow up of every order.</li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Point of Sale</strong> for your sales at the desk. You can also download the Odoo Mobile App on any phone to take orders.</li>
            <li>Save time managing your stock thanks to<strong> Inventory App</strong> and <strong>Purchase App</strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into an additional cashier (and much more).</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><strong>Use case:</strong></h1>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Bar &amp; Pub package and check the related box</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>1. Managing orders</h3>
        <p>From the <strong>Sales App</strong>, you can manage your orders.</p>
        <p>You are ready to welcome your first customers. To do so, open the Sales App, create a new order and the customer.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Imputing the customer email address enables them to receive an email when their order is collectible.</p>
                <p>You can edit the customer details clicking the arrow next to their names.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Flow 1: </strong>The simplest way to record an order is to directly select services from the catalog. Open the catalog at the bottom of the quote and select as many services as needed. Note that you can easily filter the services leveraging the filters in the left hand side drawer!</p>
        <p><strong>Flow 2:</strong> Most of the time, some services bundle well together. For such use, you can take advantage of the quotation templates. Select a quotation template and fill in the quantity of needed services.</p>
        <p>Whichever the flow, you can confirm the order. The order is on track and you can see the corresponding tasks at the top of the order! </p>
        <p>Now open the <strong>Project App</strong> to see the orders to be worked out.</p>
        <p>1. Open the project corresponding to your order, to access all related duties.</p>
        <p>2. When working on one of those task, move the tasks in the In progress column. Opening the task, you can add the product you consume to fulfill this task from the smart button Products at the top, for example outsoles in case of outsoles replacement.</p>
        <p>3. When you're done with a task; move it to the Done. Do so for all tasks as if you completed the order.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You currently have multiple steps in your projects: New, Planned, In progress, Done and Canceled. You can configure those steps in the template project by adding, removing, renaming columns if necessary.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>4. Come back to the Sales App. You can see that your first order is now ready for pick up, which is indicated by the collectible checkbox. At that point, your customer has been notified by email that the order is ready to collect!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can as well configure the process to notify your customers by SMS and Whatsapp! See the <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/studio/automated_actions.html#">automation documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/whatsapp.html">Whatsapp integration documentation</a>.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>5. When customers come back to your desk, you can easily find back their order by searching in the top search bar, and deploying the By customer arrow to access all matching customers  you have. You can as well directly see all collectible orders with the filters.</p>
        <p>Let's now see how to bill your customers as a last step.</p>
        <h3>2. Billing customers</h3>
        <p>Billing efficiently your customers for their orders is paramount for your business and to help you with this in front of customers, Odoo comes with a <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>.</p>
        <p>1. From the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>, open your register.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Downloading the App allows you to manage this step efficiently from your smartphone in parallel of other activities.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>2. Select the customer order from the register options with a full payment process.</p>
        <p>3. If customers want some additional products, such as laces or innersoles, you can add some to their note in few clicks!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"><i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Note that you can easily add services performed which were not initially planned at this stage!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>4. Introduce the means of payment, pay and you're all done with this order!</p>
        <p>5. After billing your orders from the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong>, they turn out to be fully billed. Go back to your backend by clicking the "Backend" menu in the right corner, and then go to the orders from the <strong>Sales App </strong>to appreciate this change.</p>
        <p>At the end of your service, remember to close your register. To do so, in the Point of Sale App, select "Close Register" in the top-right menu. You can then precise your cash amount and validate the closing.</p>
        <h3>3. Replenishment</h3>
        <p>Having available the necessary sub products at finger tips is crucial to deliver orders in best delays and therefore maximize your customer satisfaction. The <strong>Inventory App</strong> and the <strong>Purchase App</strong> are your best levers to manage your stock efficiently.</p>
        <p>You have two main possibilities in Odoo to ease your replenishment process.</p>
        <p><strong>Flow 1:</strong> Most products need a human assessment as the remaining quantity cannot be automatically computed. For those, a Recurring Task is created in the Project App. This task reappears every week, and you can personalize it with a checklist to avoid forgetting anything.</p>
        <p>Go to your Purchase App to easily create Requests for Proposal or Purchase Orders for products you miss or getting slim.</p>
        <p><strong>Flow 2:</strong> For products that can be tracked, such as laces and soles, you can use automated purchases. To try it, confirm a new <font class="text-o-color-5">order adding i</font><strong><font class="text-o-color-5"><span style="font-weight: normal;">nsoles with size 40-42</span></font></strong><font class="text-o-color-5">.</font></p>
        <p><font class="text-o-color-5">By doing so, you have only </font><strong><font class="text-o-color-5"><span style="font-weight: normal;">2</span></font></strong><font class="text-o-color-5"> </font><strong><font class="text-o-color-5"><span style="font-weight: normal;">insoles</span></font></strong><font class="text-o-color-5"> left wit</font>h that size in your stock.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🔄</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can see that there is a reordering rule configured for this product if you go to Inventory &gt; Products &gt; <font class="text-o-color-5">Insoles</font></p>
                <p>Reordering rules are displayed in the smart buttons on top of your product. You can see a minimum quantity, and a maximum. Each time the forecast stock lowers beneath the minimum stock, it automatically creates a purchase order to replenish to the maximum quantity.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>If you navigate to your Inventory App, and go to the replenishment from the Operations menu, you can see that some products could be reordered based on those rules.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" contenteditable="false">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>The automated replenishment rules are triggered once a day to generate a purchase order for those products. Read our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/warehouses_storage/replenishment.html"> Replenishment documentation </a>for more details.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>You can wait for the rules to apply but at this stage let's trigger the replenishment hitting the Order button on the considered products.</p>
        <p>Go to your Purchase App to open the created purchase order.</p>
        <p>You can now email your Request for Proposal to your vendor or confirm it manually.</p>
        <p>Once the products are there, you can click the "Receipt" smart button to validate your receipt and add these new products to your stock.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></h1>
        <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Start receiving orders directly in Odoo or go live with your <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">E-shop</font></strong> in a few minutes.</li>
            <li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)</li>
            <li>Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Marketing Automation</font></strong><font class="text-o-color-1">, <strong>Email Marketing</strong>, </font><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Social Media Marketing</font></strong>, and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing</font></strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Shoe Maker Services</field>
        <field name="icon">👞</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
