<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="blog_post_7" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">Neighborhood spotlight: The mobile coffee cart animating the civic plaza</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_11\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":0,"background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_3"/>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_9'), ref('blog_tag_10')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>The Warmest Corner in Town</h3>
<p>If you walk past the sun-drenched front plaza of City Hall on any given morning, you are bound to notice a rich, comforting aroma drifting through the air. That smell belongs to <i>The Civic Espresso</i>, an independent mobile coffee triporteur run by local resident and passionate barista, Marcus Vance. It has quickly become the social heart of our neighborhood’s morning routine.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>More Than Just Caffeine</h3>
<p>Marcus’s cart represents exactly what our modern City Hall plaza was built for: fostering spontaneous human connection. On any given day, you will find municipal clerks, construction workers, local business owners, and parents fresh from the school run standing together by the wooden steps, chatting over fresh pastries and lattes.</p>
<blockquote class="">"I don't just sell coffee," Marcus says with a smile.<br>I provide a reason for people to slow down, look up 
from their phones, and say good morning to their neighbors.</blockquote>
<p><br></p>
<h3>An Active Plaza Ecosystem</h3>
<p>The city's economic development desk grants public space permits to micro-entrepreneurs like Marcus to breathe life into our civic areas. This philosophy extends into the weekend: every Saturday morning at 8:30 AM, the lawn adjacent to the coffee cart hosts free, open-attendance Tai-Chi sessions. Why not come down this Saturday, enjoy some gentle movement on the green, and support a fantastic local business?</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_6" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">Saying "I Do" at City Hall: A peek inside weddings at the Horizon Hall</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_12\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":0,"background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_3"/>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_8'), ref('blog_tag_7')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>Love with a Panoramic View</h3>
<p>When we designed the modern Horizon Hall inside our new City Hall, we envisioned a space that wouldn't just host administrative events, but would celebrate life's most beautiful personal milestones. Today, we are opening the doors to show you how our flagship indoor ballroom transforms into a dream wedding venue for local couples.</p>
<blockquote class="">The moment we walked in, we fell in love with the light.
Having the city skyline as our wedding backdrop through
those floor-to-ceiling glass walls was unforgettable.</blockquote>
<p>Sarah &amp; Thomas, married April 2026
</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>Premium Features for Your Special Day:</h3>
<ul><li><p><b>Flawless Acoustics:</b> The venue boasts hidden acoustic ceiling panels, ensuring that whether a string quartet or a live folk band is playing on the raised wooden stage, the sound is crisp, warm, and clear.</p></li><li><p><b>Seamless Catering Integration:</b> The hall features direct, hidden service access to a commercial-grade preparation kitchen, allowing your chosen catering team to serve guests seamlessly without disrupting the aesthetics of the room.</p></li><li><p><b>Flexible Layouts:</b> From a seated dinner banquet for 180 guests to an elegant standing cocktail reception for 250, our facility managers customize the floor plan to fit your exact creative vision.</p></li></ul>
<p>Residents of our municipality receive a <b>25% booking discount</b> on weekend slots. Contact our events coordinator today to take a private tour of the space.</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_5" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">Massive turnout for St. Mary’s primary school celebration!</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_13\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":"0.2","background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_3"/>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_5'), ref('blog_tag_4')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>Smiles, Sunshine, and Strategy Games</h3>
<p>Laughter and competitive spirit filled the air last Sunday as the rear garden space of City Hall hosted the St. Mary’s Primary School Annual Garden Fête. Blessed with perfect sunny weather, over 300 parents, teachers, and children turned our beautifully landscaped "Town Square" into a hub of play and generosity.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>Playing for a Good Cause</h3>
<p>The heart of the garden was dominated by custom wooden skill games. Children and parents formed teams to battle it out in a highly competitive Mölkky tournament, while others tested their coordination on oversized wooden mazes and block-stacking challenges.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the main lawn featured a lively fundraising lottery booth. Thanks to the overwhelming generosity of local business sponsors who donated prizes, the raffle ticket sales completely smashed all historical school records.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>A Heartfelt Thank You</h3>
<p>We are proud to report that the event raised a grand total of <b>€5,400</b>. 100% of these proceeds will be used by St. Mary's to fund extra-curricular museum trips and specialized STEM equipment for the upcoming school year. Thank you to the parent-teacher association and our civic facility team for making this open-air celebration an absolute triumph.</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_4" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">The return of the annual fireworks: your ultimate guide to the big night</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_14\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":"0.2","background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="blog_id" ref="blog_blog_3"/>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_1'), ref('blog_tag_3'), ref('blog_tag_2')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>Light Up the Night Sky!</h3>
<p>The most anticipated social evening of the summer is officially back. On Saturday, July 4th, the expansive Civic Plaza at the front of City Hall will transform into a vibrant community gathering space for our Annual Fireworks Celebration. Gather your family, call your neighbors, and join us for a night of music, food, and community magic under the stars.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>The Evening Schedule:</h3>
<ul><li><p><b>7:00 PM – Plaza Doors &amp; Food Trucks Open:</b> Taste local delicacies from seven independent regional food trucks parked along the promenade.</p></li><li><p><b>8:00 PM – Live Music:</b> The local folk band <i>The Wandering Strings</i> takes the main wood terrace stage to play an acoustic outdoor set.</p></li><li><p><b>9:30 PM – The Main Event:</b> Grab your blankets! A spectacular, synchronized pyrotechnic display will light up the sky directly above the modern architecture of City Hall.</p></li><li><p><br></p></li></ul>
<h3>Logistics &amp; Safety:</h3>
<p>To keep this event safe and accessible for everyone, the main avenue leading to City Hall will close to vehicle traffic starting at 6:00 PM. Free parking is available at the sports park lot, with a continuous electric shuttle bus running every 10 minutes. Due to the loud nature of the fireworks, we kindly ask that you leave domestic pets safely at home.</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_3" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">Municipal budget 2026: Where do your taxes go? Focus on the green transition</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_15\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":0,"background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_12'), ref('blog_tag_13'), ref('blog_tag_11')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>Accountable, Balanced, and Forward-Thinking</h3>
<p>As part of our absolute commitment to municipal transparency, the Finance Directorate has published the simplified annual budget overview for the fiscal year 2026. This year, our primary objective is to balance necessary infrastructure growth with aggressive environmental preservation, ensuring that your local tax dollars directly improve our shared well-being.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>2026 Allocation Overview:</h3>
<table class="table table-bordered o_table"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Department / Initiative</strong></td><td><strong>Percentage of Budget</strong></td><td><strong>Primary Target</strong></td></tr><tr><td><b>Green Infrastructure</b></td><td>35%</td><td>Living green roofs, park expansions, tree planting</td></tr><tr><td><b>Digital Transformation</b></td><td>20%</td><td>Paperless paper administration, citizen portal upgrades</td></tr><tr><td><b>Public Works &amp; Roads</b></td><td>25%</td><td>Pothole eradication, cycle paths, LED streetlighting</td></tr><tr><td><b>Community Culture &amp; Safety</b></td><td>20%</td><td>Local association grants, kermesses, public plaza security</td></tr></tbody></table>
<p><br></p>
<h3>Investing in Sustainability</h3>
<p>Our most notable investment this quarter is the operational integration of the new City Hall’s living green roof. This installation naturally regulates the building's temperature, slashing municipal energy costs by 22% while filtering rainwater runoff. Furthermore, by transitioning 85% of our internal permitting procedures to digital workflows, we have successfully saved over three tons of administrative paper to date.</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_2" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">The community has spoken: Discover the official name of our newest street!</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_16\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":0,"background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_14'), ref('blog_tag_15')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>A Map Shaped by You</h3>
<p>We are thrilled to announce that our community naming survey has officially concluded, yielding a record-breaking participation rate from our residents. When we broke ground on the new housing development next to the sports field, the City Council promised that the people living here would write its history. By casting your votes over the last two weeks, you did exactly that.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>The Vote Breakdown:</h3>
<p>Our urban planning team compiled over 1,200 unique submissions from our online portal. Here is how our democratic shortlist stacked up:</p>
<ul><li><p><b>Olympia Way:</b> 42% (The Winning Choice!)</p></li><li><p><b>Meadowview Drive:</b> 28%</p></li><li><p><b>Fairplay Avenue:</b> 18%</p></li><li><p><b>Founder’s Lane:</b> 12%</p></li><li><p><br></p></li></ul>
<h3>What Happens Next?</h3>
<p>Because <b>Olympia Way</b> resonated so strongly with your desire to celebrate our local athletic spirit and proximity to the sports park, the Council has officially signed the naming decree. Our public works department has already ordered the new high-visibility signage, which will be installed as soon as the first road layer is paved next month.</p>
<p>Thank you to everyone who took three minutes to make their voice heard in our digital town square!</p>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
  <record id="blog_post_1" model="blog.post">
    <field name="name">May 12th council recap: Green light for the sports field &amp; residential extension</field>
    <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(\"/web/image/public_institution.ir_attachment_17\")","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover","text_align_class":"","opacity":0,"background_color_class":"o_cc o_cc3","background_color_style":""}]]></field>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="published_date" eval="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d %H:%M:%S')"/>
    <field name="author_id" ref="base.partner_admin"/>
    <field name="tag_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('blog_tag_16'), ref('blog_tag_18'), ref('blog_tag_17')])]"/>
    <field name="content"><![CDATA[<h3>Transforming Vision into Infrastructure</h3>
<p>During our monthly public session on May 12th, 2026, the City Council officially voted to approve the structural zoning amendment for the <b>Pine Creek District</b>. This critical milestone clears the path for a modern, eco-responsible residential extension located immediately adjacent to our Municipal Sports Field.</p>
<p>The project aims to address the growing demand for local housing while strictly preserving the surrounding natural ecosystem.</p>
<p><br></p>
<h3>Key Decisions Made:</h3>
<ul><li><p><b>Access infrastructure:</b> A budget of €340,000 was approved to construct a low-impact permeable roadway, complete with dedicated bicycle lanes and underground smart utility lines.</p></li><li><p><b>Eco-friendly guidelines:</b> The Council mandated that all new homes built within this perimeter must adhere to modern bioclimatic standards, utilizing sustainable timber framing and rainwater harvesting systems.</p></li><li><p><b>Public consultation:</b> The official public inquiry phase is now open. Residents can review the full scale-model architectural blueprints on display in the City Hall lobby.</p></li></ul>
<blockquote class=""><p><b>Citizen action item:</b> We believe transparent governance requires active collaboration. The Council invites all direct neighbors to review the infrastructure timelines and voice any environmental inquiries.</p></blockquote>
<p><br></p>]]></field>
  </record>
</odoo>
