<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <p data-oe-version="1.0">
            <span style="font-size: 36px;"><strong>Bakery </strong></span></p>
            <p>Welcome to the <strong>Odoo Bakery Package!</strong></p>
            <p>This set up is ideal for bakeries specializing in bread, pastries, cakes, and custom orders, such as corporate breakfasts. It suits businesses serving walk-in customers, managing larger orders for cafes and restaurants, or delivering to multiple points of sale.</p><p>The package features the <strong>Point of Sale (POS)</strong> app for seamless in-store sales and the <strong>Sales</strong> app for managing orders. For bakeries looking to expand online, the <strong>Website</strong> and <strong>E-commerce</strong> apps allow you to showcase products and offer <strong>Pick up at Store</strong> options.</p>
            <p>Ensure your customers can enjoy freshly baked croissants—even on busy sunny Sunday mornings when stock is quickly running low!🌞</p>
            <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
            <h2>Basics</h2>
            <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
            <ul>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase App</font></strong> manages raw material orders and vendors.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale App</font></strong> manages in-store orders and payments.</li>
            <li>The<strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> streamlines customer orders and quotations, such as managing company events or coffee shop orders.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website &amp; E-commerce App</font></strong> enables online sales and offer Pick up at Store options.</li>
            </ul>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2>Use Case</h2>
            <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
            <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
            <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Bakery Package</strong> and check the related box.</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h3>Purchase raw materials</h3>
            <p>Maintain stock of fresh ingredients.</p>
            <ol>
            <li><strong>Create a purchase order</strong>: Select the materials you need for your breads and pastries.</li>
            <li><strong>Choose the best vendor</strong>: Pick the vendor offering the best deal for the requested materials.</li>
            </ol>
            <h3>Manage orders and payments</h3>
            <p>Streamline in-store order processing and offer flexible payment options.</p>
            <ol>
            <li><strong>Take orders in Point of Sale</strong>: Process in-store bread, loaf and pastries orders quickly using the Point of Sale system.</li>
            <li><strong>Accept flexible payments</strong>: Provide multiple payment options (cash, card, mobile).</li>
            </ol>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Use the Reporting in the Sales app to analyze trends such as higher order volumes on sunny days, weekends, or holidays, helping you plan better for peak times.</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h3>Grow your business with e-commerce</h3>
            <p>Expand sales online and offer convenience for customers.</p>
            <ol>
            <li><strong>Bulk orders for events</strong>: Allow customers to place large orders for events like company breakfasts, ensuring they can select from a variety of breads, pastries, and baked goods with flexible delivery or pickup options.</li>
            <li><strong>Pre-order system</strong>: Enable customers to place orders in advance, ensuring product availability and timely preparation, especially during busy times like Sunday mornings or holidays.</li>
            </ol>
            <h2>Do you want to go further?</h2>
            <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your bakery:</p>
            <ul>
            <li>Track stock in real-time, manage multiple storage locations, automate restocking, and monitor expiration dates to ensure ingredient freshness and avoid shortages, with our<strong> Inventory app</strong>.</li>
            <li>Craft your perfect breads, loaves, and pastries with ease, on our <strong>Manufacturing app</strong>, by creating manufacturing orders based on customer demand and linking the necessary ingredients to each product.</li>
            <li><strong>Restaurant mode</strong>: Manage tables, orders, and payments with the Point of Sale system if you offer an "eat-in" option.</li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Quality App</strong> to perform product checks upon receipt to ensure they meet your standards.</li>
            <li><strong>Employee scheduling:</strong> Use the <strong>Planning App</strong> to create and manage employee schedules, ensuring you have the right staff at the right times for busy days and specific orders.</li>
            <li>Manage your <strong>team</strong> efficiently and integrate them into all processes with the <em>Employees App</em>.</li>
            <li>Easily handle your <strong>accounting</strong> with the integrated <em>Accounting App</em>.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                    <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
                </div>
            </div>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Bakery</field>
        <field name="icon">🥐</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">65.0</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
