<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <p>
            <strong><span class="h1-fs">Odoo for Law Firms</span></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            Welcome to the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Odoo Law Firm package</font></strong>!
        </p>
        <p>
            This module provides a comprehensive suite of tools designed specifically for law firms, enabling efficient management of time, appointments, deadlines, cases, and client relationships. Lawyers represent their clients and protect their
            interests during legal proceedings.
        </p>
        <p>
            By using this module, you’ll gain access to essential features such as case management, invoicing, and time tracking. These tools streamline the workflow from initial consultations to billing, allowing law firms to focus on delivering
            high-quality legal services.
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Calendar App</font></strong> manages your schedule and appointments.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage client assessment with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM App</font></strong> and handle quotations and contracts with <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Sales App</strong></font>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Centralize case files and tasks with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Project &amp; Documents App</font>.</strong>
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Timesheet App</font></strong> tracks billable hours and time spent.
            </li>
            <li>
                Use the<strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Sign App</font></strong> to securely sign engagement letters and legal documents, ensuring clear agreements before or after legal work.
            </li>
            <li>
                Ease your invoicing process with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoice App</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Showcase your services and client testimonials seamlessly on your professional website using the
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Website App</font><font style="color: rgb(66, 66, 66);"><span style="font-weight: normal;">.</span></font>
                </strong>
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>
                    <font style="color: rgb(66, 66, 66);"><span style="font-weight: normal;">Manage your firm’s internal expenses tracking with the</span> </font><font class="text-o-color-1">Expenses App</font>
                    <font style="color: rgb(66, 66, 66);"><span style="font-weight: normal;"> to keep spending transparent and under control.</span></font><font class="text-o-color-1"></font>
                </strong>
                <br />
            </li>
            <li>
                Streamline legal research and collaboration with the<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Knowledge App</font> </strong>by centralizing case law, legal texts, and internal guides for efficient retrieval, collaboration, and
                compliance.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage your entire business in it.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h2-fs"><strong>Use Case</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo. This is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to modify it however you want!</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Law Firm package and check the <strong>"Include Demo Data"</strong> checkbox.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><strong>📅 Manage your agenda with the calendar app</strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Stay organized by keeping track of all appointments, deadlines, and internal tasks using the Calendar app. Legal assistants can easily assign meetings by accessing the calendars of individual lawyers.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>Calendar</strong> app.
            </li>
            <li>Schedule your meetings, deadlines, or court appearances by clicking on an empty time slot.</li>
            <li>Check other lawyers’ availability by selecting their calendars to coordinate meetings.</li>
        </ol>
        <p><strong>Synchronizing external calendars:</strong> If lawyers or secretaries use tools like Google Calendar or Outlook, follow these steps to sync them with Odoo:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <strong>👉 </strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar/google.html">Google Calendar Integration</a>
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>👉 </strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar/outlook.html">Outlook Integration</a>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <p>This ensures that appointments made outside of Odoo automatically appear in the Odoo calendar.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    With the <strong>Appointment app</strong>, you can easily schedule client meetings by sharing a booking link. Clients can select a time directly from your calendar that works for both of you, saving time and avoiding
                    back-and-forth communication.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Use the <strong>Website App</strong> to enhance your law firm’s online visibility and make it easy for clients to contact you.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><strong>🎯 Create a new client case</strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Easily create and manage a new case for your client using Odoo’s streamlined workflow.</p>
        <p><strong>Steps to create a new case:</strong></p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                Use the <strong>CRM app</strong> to manage client interactions and conduct the required
                <strong>Know Your Customer (KYC) assessment</strong> before accepting a case.
            </li>
            <li>Create a Sale Order from scratch or use the<strong> Standard Lawyer Service Quotation</strong> template.</li>
            <li>
                Adapt your <strong>Terms &amp; Conditions</strong> directly on the quotation, and the customers will be able to
                sign it through their Odoo portal, or create or use the template of the <strong>Engagement Letter</strong> in
                the <strong>Sign App</strong>, and request the client's signature for the agreement.
            </li>
            <li>
                Confirm the Sale Order, which will automatically generate the related <strong>Project</strong> and
                <strong>Tasks</strong>.
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status"
        >
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Link Knowledge articles or notes with practical info (e.g., KYC assessment).</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                    
                        Save key info like KYC details, risk level, or client background in the
                        <strong>Knowledge App</strong>’s clipboard.
                        
                    </li>
                    <li>
                    
                        Click the <strong>Knowledge app icon</strong>in any CRM opportunity, choose the
                        <strong>KYC article</strong>, then click<strong>Use as Notes</strong>to attach it
                        directly where you need it.
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>Quickly access all essential data when reviewing a case or preparing a proposal.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
            data-oe-role="status"
        >
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Using down payment for provision:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        By creating an invoice for the quotation, you can record the down payment based on a percentage of the
                        total or a fixed amount (e.g., €1000, upfront for the Legal Services).
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Final payment: Once the case is closed, invoice the client for the remaining balance based on the time
                        tracked in the timesheets.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-primary">CRM Documentation</a></strong>
        </p>
        <p><strong>Customer identity management</strong></p>
        <p>
            Identity management is a must have activity in your business. The contacts app encompasses all the
            necessary options.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Contacts App</strong> and reach your new customer form.</li>
            <li>Easily request identity document from the gear icon (⚙️) in the bread crumb.</li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status"
        >
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Sending a document request creates an activity for you to follow up without mental load!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>When the document is available, reach the contact ID tab to fill in the contact details.</li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
            data-oe-role="status"
        >
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    When filling in the identity document expiration date, you can leverage the contacts filter "Expired IDs" to
                    efficiently find the IDs to update!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🔃</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    An automation runs daily to request expiring and expired identity documents to your contacts. Make sure to
                    check the open document request from Documents App.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/essentials/contacts.html" class="btn btn-primary" rel="noreferrer">Contacts Documentation</a> 
        </p>
        <h3><strong>📄 Organize case files in projects and documents</strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Centralize all case activities and documents using the <strong>Project</strong> and <strong>Documents</strong> apps.</p>
        <p>
            <strong><span class="h4-fs">Managing projects:</span></strong>
        </p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the related <strong>Project</strong>.</li>
            <li>Assign <strong>responsible users</strong>.</li>
            <li><strong>Manage tasks</strong> by organizing them into stages such as 'To Do,' 'In Progress,' and 'Done' to keep track of progress.</li>
            <li><strong>Log your time</strong> directly in the 'Timesheet' tab of a specific task, or use the timer to track the time spent on that task.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Organize tasks by Milestones and assign specific dates to key stages in the case.</p>
                <p><em>Example:</em></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <em><strong>Milestone: </strong>First Hearing</em>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <em><strong>Tasks</strong>: Prepare Legal Arguments, Review Submissions and Arguments from Opposing Counsel</em>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong>
                <span class="h4-fs">
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html" class="btn btn-primary">
                        <span class="o_small-fs">Projects Documentation</span>
                    </a>
                </span>
            </strong>
        </p>
        <h3><br />⏲️ Time management</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Some of your services might be time sheet invoiced. You can proceed by different ways to record your time.</p>
        <p><strong>From a task</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>Project App</strong> or navigate to the sale order associated tasks with the smart button at
                the top.
            </li>
            <li>Open the task you were working on, go to the Timesheets tab and add a new line.</li>
            <li>Saving the task will report this time in the sale order for billing.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>From a project</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the the project you worked on.</li>
            <li>Click the project shortcut for Timesheets and add a line.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>From the Timesheets App</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the Timesheets App, add a line selecting the project and task you worked on, and inputing the time spent
                today.
            </li>
            <li>You can as well change view for the list view for example, and click the New button to report some time.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Leveraging Services &amp; Materials</strong></p>
        <p>
            Timesheets work well but you may want to capture more on the fly some work you do and expense it to the customer.
            Here is how to proceed.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>Sales App</strong> and navigate from the menu to <strong>To Invoice</strong>,
                <strong>Services &amp; Materials</strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Hit the New button, select the order it applies to, the product you worked on, adjust the quantity, leave a note
                and save the line.
            </li>
            <li>Navigate to the sale order you just pointed out, the delivered quantity is now updated accordingly.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    Note that to use products in the Services &amp; Materials view, you need to define their re-invoicing cost
                    from the product form, sales tab, expense section.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Leveraging the activity tracker</strong></p>
        <p>
            The <strong>Odoo Timesheets Assistant</strong> takes the pain out of answering “What should I timesheet today?” by
            tracking work activity in the background and turning it into smart, context-aware timesheet suggestions.
        </p>
        <p>
            Instead of making users reconstruct their day from memory, Odoo helps them log billable hours accurately by
            suggesting entries based on what they actually worked on.
        </p>
        <p>
            To activate it, open the Timesheets App, hit the "Want to track your activities" suggestion and follow
            recommendations!
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    Not all you time might be billable even when working on a customer projects. In such case, just leave the
                    sale order item field blank.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    If you wish you can introduce sections in your sale order to structure it by year of follow up or simply add
                    a note to the product line for example.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    You can set up a <strong>Billing Time Target per month</strong> per employee to keep track of billable hours
                    and ensure targets are met.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong>
                <span class="h4-fs">
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/timesheets.html" class="btn btn-primary">
                        <span class="o_small-fs">Timesheets Documentation</span>
                    </a>
                </span>
            </strong>
        </p>
        <h3>🗂️ Document management</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>
            Since a tedious part of the job is to request and organise documents for reference and traceability, a good document
            management system is required!
        </p>
        <p>
            Documents create a dedicated space for each of your projects to prevent you to mix documents between your customers.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                When sending a message in the chatter, you can easily attach files from the Documents app as attachment.
            </li>
            <li>Chatter documents can easily be saved in the Documents App folders.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Setting up the project folder email alias</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>To setup the project folder email alias, display the project top bar and add the Documents shortcut.</li>
            <li>
                Click the Document shortcut to open the Documents folder of this particular project, and deploy the information
                panel (top right corner <span class="fa fa-info"></span> icon).
            </li>
            <li>
                Input the email alias for this customer and select the Inbox activity type and the assignee of the activities
                which will be triggered when receiving new documents.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            The documents sent to the email alias of this project will arrive in the root folder of the project. This can be
            considered as an inbox while sub folders contain treated documents in an organized fashion.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    Note that only direct email capture the attached documents. Be clear with your customers to send a new email
                    for any new documents they wish you to process from the email alias.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Requesting a document</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>To request a document, click New and then Request.</li>
            <li>
                Input the name of the document you seek for, set the contact the request needs to reach (making sure their email
                is configured), and adjust the Due Date if necessary before finally hitting the Request button.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    This creates an empty document in your project to be filled by your customer by uploading a file from the
                    email they receive. You could do so for all required documents by the task.
                </p>
                <p>
                    On upload of a document, you receive an activity which is visible in the notification for the Documents app.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    Don't forget to check as done the activity when your done with a document to have clear visibility of your
                    workload from the activity list.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>How to build your court bundle:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Mark your essential documents as favorites.</li>
                    <li>Select all your favorite documents.</li>
                    <li>Merge them into a single document, ready to be submitted to the judge.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>
            <strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html" class="btn btn-primary">Documents Documentation</a></strong>
        </h3>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h4>🤖 Use AI to organize, explain, summarize and more</h4>
        <hr />
        <p>
            Odoo AI is built into the apps you already use. It helps your team handle the repetitive parts of legal work such as
            filing documents, summarizing long PDFs, drafting routine replies, and looking up information across cases.
        </p>
        <p>
            There are three ways AI shows up in your day-to-day work: <strong>AI assistants</strong> (in-context help inside any
            app), <strong>AI agents</strong> (a custom assistant configured for a specific role or task), and
            <strong>automated document handling</strong> (in the Documents app).
        </p>
        <p><strong>AI assistants in any record</strong></p>
        <p>
            The AI icon is visible anywhere in Odoo, in the top-right corner of your screen. Pressing it opens up your AI
            assistant that is aware of everything that's on your screen.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                In a task description, ask the AI to <em>summarize the latest deposition</em> attached to the case, or to
                <em>draft a status update for the client based on the last three chatter entries</em>.
            </li>
            <li>
                In the chatter of a client opportunity, ask the AI to
                <em>draft a polite follow-up requesting the missing KYC documents</em>.
            </li>
            <li>
                In a Knowledge article, ask the AI to <em>rewrite this clause in plain English</em> or
                <em>translate this paragraph into French</em>.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Automated document handling</strong></p>
        <p>
            Each case project has a Documents folder. When a new file lands there, whether dragged in, emailed via the project
            alias, or uploaded by a client, Odoo AI can <strong>Auto-sort</strong> the file into the right sub-folder
            (Pleadings, Correspondence, Evidence, Invoices, Client IDs).
        </p>
        <p><strong>Ask Odoo questions in plain language</strong></p>
        <p>
            You can ask Odoo questions about your own data without writing a filter or a report. From the AI app or the global
            search, type questions like:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li><em>Which cases have hearings in the next 30 days?</em></li>
            <li><em>Show me unbilled hours for the Smith matter.</em></li>
            <li><em>What's our average time-to-invoice this quarter?</em></li>
            <li><em>Which clients have expired ID documents?</em></li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Create agents with expertise</strong></p>
        <p>
            Build your own AI specialists by uploading the source material they should rely on. An agent with documents attached
            only answers from those sources, with citations.
        </p>
        <p><strong>Examples for a law firm:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                A <strong>case law agent</strong> loaded with judgments, statutes, and commentary for your practice area. Ask
                <em>"What's the leading case on force majeure in commercial leases?"</em> and get an answer that cites the
                rulings you uploaded.
            </li>
            <li>
                A <strong>firm playbook agent</strong> loaded with your internal procedures, clause libraries, and precedent
                contracts. New hires can ask <em>"How do we draft a limitation of liability for a software vendor?"</em> and get
                the firm's standard approach.
            </li>
            <li>
                A <strong>client-specific agent</strong> loaded with everything from a long-running matter — pleadings,
                correspondence, expert reports, prior advice. Useful when a partner picks up a file they haven't touched in
                months and needs to get up to speed in five minutes.
            </li>
            <li>
                A <strong>regulatory agent</strong> loaded with the regulations, circulars, and guidance notes that govern a
                sector your firm advises in (banking, data protection, employment).
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h3><strong>Invoice Clients</strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Ensure every billable hour and expense is accurately accounted for and invoiced.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Confirm the quotation to generate an invoice automatically.</li>
            <li>Send the invoice directly to the client from Odoo.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Use the <strong>Sign App</strong> to request a signature from the partner to approve the completed legal documents before delivery and invoicing the client.</p>
                <p>The Sign App offers <strong>three levels of signatures</strong>, allowing you to choose the appropriate level based on the document’s importance and legal requirements.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Use the <strong>Expenses App</strong> to keep track of all firm-related costs in one place, such as a restaurant with a client or office supplies. This ensures internal expenses remain transparent and easy to manage.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html" class="btn btn-primary">Invoicing Documentation</a></strong>
        </p>
        <p><strong>Workflow Example</strong></p>
        <hr />
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Schedule the first consultation</strong>: Add a consultation with John Doe to your calendar.</li>
            <li><strong>Open the case</strong>: Create a new project for the case.</li>
            <li><strong>Organize tasks</strong>: Set up tasks for the case, such as "Document Drafting" and "Legal Research."</li>
            <li><strong>Manage documents</strong>: Upload and organize case documents in the project’s document folder.</li>
            <li><strong>Log your time</strong>: Track hours spent on each task in the Timesheet tab.</li>
            <li><strong>Invoice the client</strong>: Compile logged hours, document preparation costs, and travel expenses into the invoice.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>
                    Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>
            <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></span>
        </h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                A free, personalized, integrated<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Website </font></strong>in a few clicks. Get new clients or direct appointment online in a few clicks.
            </li>
            <li>
                Make and receive calls, and send SMS or WhatsApp messages directly through Odoo by adding our <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>VoIP and WhatsApp module</strong></font>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage your team's and integrate them in all processes by adding the<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Employees App</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment thanks to our <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Law Firm</field>
        <field name="icon">⚖️</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_10"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
