<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Lawyer firms</h1>
        <p>This setup is for lawyers firms. They represent their clients and defend their interest during juridical procedures.</p>
        <p>Lawyers have open / public consultations for people to reach out and get advice on their situation.</p>
        <p>When a case he opened and a contract is signed between them and their clients, they will typically execute a certain amount of tasks related to the case, and invoice their services on a given rate.</p>
        <h1>Business Flows</h1>
        <h2>Flow 1: Get an appointment on the website</h2>
        <p>On the Website:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Visit the Appointment page where the open consultations slots for all the lawyers are accessible.</li>
            <li>Select the domain, then the lawyer, and select an available slot.</li>
        </ol>
        <p>In the Backend:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Check the created appointment.</li>
            <li>Check the user agenda, a meeting is created.</li>
        </ol>
        <h2>Flow 2: Open a new file, start registering Timesheets.</h2>
        <p>From the Sales app:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Create a Sale Order using the Standard Lawyer service Quotation template.</li>
            <li>Complete the Customer information.</li>
            <li>Add another Sale Order line using the Administration fees product.</li>
            <li>Confirm the Sale Order which will create the related Project and Tasks</li>
        </ol>
        <p>Open the related Project:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Assign the responsible user.</li>
            <li>Look at the available tasks, select the Lawyer Services task.</li>
            <li>Put it In Progress, open it.</li>
            <li>Go in the Timesheets tab, register a new Timesheet manually.</li>
        </ol>
        <p>Open the Timesheet app:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Use the quick Timesheet functionality to start counting time on the Lawyer Services Task of the project.</li>
            <li>Add a new line to register a new Timesheet on the Administration Task of the project manually.</li>
        </ol>
        <h2>Flow 3: Create an invoice of</h2>
        <p>From the Sales app:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Select the project SO.</li>
            <li>Input the amount of delivered dactylographied pages and travel expenses incurred.</li>
            <li>Create a Regular Invoice.</li>
        </ol>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Law Firm</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">50.0</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
