<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="sale_order_template_1" model="sale.order.template">
        <field name="name">Standard Lawyer service</field>
        <field name="note"><![CDATA[<p data-oe-version="1.0">GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF ENGAGEMENT</p><ol>
<li>SCOPE OF ENGAGEMENT
The Client engages the Attorney to provide legal counsel and/or court representation. The Attorney commits to implementing all necessary means to best defend the Client's interests.</li>
<li>FEES AND EXPENSES
2.1. Calculation Basis
Fees are calculated according to the following terms:</li>
</ol><ul>
<li>Base hourly rate for a Junior Lawyer: 120€/hour</li><li>Base hourly rate for a Senior&nbsp;Lawyer: 200€/hour</li>
<li>Administrative costs:&nbsp;80€/hour</li>
<li>Travel expenses: 80€/hour</li>
</ul><p>2.2. Retainer
A retainer of [amount]€ is required upon signing this agreement. This amount will be deducted from the final billing.</p><ol>
<li>ATTORNEY'S OBLIGATIONS
The Attorney commits to:</li>
</ol><ul>
<li>Maintain attorney-client privilege</li>
<li>Regularly inform the Client of case developments</li>
<li>Implement best expertise</li>
<li>Avoid any conflicts of interest</li>
</ul><ol>
<li>CLIENT'S OBLIGATIONS
The Client commits to:</li>
</ol><ul>
<li>Provide all necessary information and documents</li>
<li>Cooperate in good faith</li>
<li>Pay fees within agreed timeframes</li>
<li>Inform the Attorney of any relevant changes</li>
</ul><ol>
<li>FILE RETENTION AND DOCUMENT STORAGE
Files will be retained for 5 years after the end of the engagement. Beyond this period, they may be destroyed unless expressly requested otherwise by the Client.</li>
<li>DATA PROTECTION
Personal data processing is conducted in accordance with GDPR and the firm's privacy policy.</li>
<li>TERMINATION
Either party may terminate the engagement with 15 days written notice, subject to payment for services already rendered.</li>
<li>LIABILITY
The Attorney maintains professional liability insurance with [insurance company name].</li>
<li>APPLICABLE LAW AND JURISDICTION
This agreement is governed by Belgian law. Any disputes will be submitted to the courts of [city].</li>
<li>MEDIATION
In case of dispute, parties commit to attempting mediation before any legal action.</li></ol>]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
