<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Surveyor</h1>
        <p>This setup is for surveyors that sell services like land measurement  &amp; mapping, planning permission, mediation counsel, etc to private customers as well as companies (architect, notary, real estate, …).</p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <p>They need a website to collect new leads and give access to produced documents.</p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <p>They also need subscriptions for long term relationships with larger companies that require several services per year.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Basics</h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Project App</b>: Manage complex surveying sites as distinct projects, tracking tasks like initial
                measurements, data processing, and report generation.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Planning App</b>: Optimize your field operations by visually scheduling surveyors and equipment to specific
                locations and times.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Documents App</b>: Securely store, organize, and share heavy files such as topographic maps, CAD drawings,
                and compliance reports.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Knowledge App</b>: Create a central repository for internal procedures, safety guidelines, and technical
                standards accessible to all staff.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>CRM App</b>: Track potential projects and manage relationships with developers, construction firms, and
                private property owners.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Sales App</b>: Generate detailed proposals and contracts for surveying services, ensuring clear scope and
                pricing agreements.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Invoicing App</b>: Bill clients accurately based on project milestones or time spent on site, maintaining
                healthy cash flow.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h1>Business flows</h1>
        <h2>Flow 1: Request a Quote</h2>
        <h3>From the website</h3>
        <p><br /></p>
        <p>Visit the Contact us page: This form will create an opportunity in the CRM, with the right information.</p>
        <h3>Surveyor meets the client</h3>
        <p>From the CRM, schedule a call or a meeting. Based on the client’s need, you can create a quotation using the quotation templates.</p>
        <h3>(From a phone call)</h3>
        <p>Quicker flow where the surveyor can directly create and send a quote to the lead.</p>
        <h2>Flow 2: Buy  &amp; deliver services</h2>
        <p>When the quote is signed by the customer, a dedicated project is created with all the services listed in the quotation as a task.</p>
        <p>In Planning, the surveyor can allocate the task to each employee (himself, topographer or drawer).</p>
        <p>
            In all cases, a surveyor will deliver documents. Therefore an integration with Documents is enabled to easily share the created documents and gather them if needed. To this intent a share link (share  &amp; upload) can be generated for
            each project sub-workspace so that the customer has direct access to it.
        </p>
        <p>Once the final documents are delivered to the customer, the surveyor can send the final invoice potentially adapting the hours spent on each service.<br /></p>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="cover_image_position">92.01000000000006</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_8"/>
        <field name="parent_path">3/</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="sequence">3</field>
        <field name="name">Surveying &amp; Mapping</field>
        <field name="icon">📐</field>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
