<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Odoo for DIY Workshops</h1>
        <p>This setup is perfect for DIY sewing studios offering group classes, private sessions, memberships, and creative events in fields such as sewing, woodworking, pottery, painting, jewelry-making, and beyond. Odoo helps you manage your schedule, supplies, instructors, and customer specific requests, all from one place.</p>
        <p>Use the <strong>Events App</strong> to organize your classes and the <strong>Purchase App</strong> to keep your workshop stocked with the right materials. With the <strong>Website App</strong>, you can showcase your studio, promote workshops, and let participants book their spots online.</p>
        <p>Create, craft, and connect, Odoo takes care of the business side, so you can focus on creativity. 🎨</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><strong>Basics</strong></h2>
        <p>You can access every installed app in your Odoo database from your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Events App</font></strong> organizes creative workshops like sewing, painting, and woodworking to engage your community.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website App</font></strong> promotes your studio, explains your creative offerings, and enables online class bookings.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> simplifies private workshop requests, material sales, and manages memberships.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase App</font></strong> manages your supplies by tracking and ordering fabrics, clay, tools, paints, and more.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing App</font></strong> automates payments and keeps your finances organized.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2><strong>Use Case</strong></h2>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <div><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your DIY Workshops Package </strong>and check the related box.</div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr/>
        <h3><strong>Defining Your DIY Workshop Offer</strong></h3>
        <h4>Create Your Products</h4>
        <p>Design flexible options for your clients based on how they want to engage with your workshops studio:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Single workshop registration</strong> (e.g., “Pottery for Beginners” or “Build a Wooden Shelf”)</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Workshop pass</strong> (e.g., “5-Class Sewing Pass” or “DIY Essentials Card”)</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Monthly memberships</strong> (e.g., “Unlimited DIY Access – Studio Time”)</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Set Up Membership Pricing with Pricelists</h4>
        <p>Create a pricelist for each membership or class pack, then link it to a membership level:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Set the product type to <strong>Service – Membership</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Link the product to a <strong>Membership Level</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Associate that level with a specific <strong>Pricelist</strong></p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>When someone purchases a membership, they’re automatically assigned the level and see the correct class pricing (e.g., free or discounted) directly on the website.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Use Loyalty Cards for Class Packs</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create a product: “5-Class Creative Pass”</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Go to <strong>Discount &amp; Loyalty</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add a rule: 5 points earned per purchase</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add a reward: 1 point = 100% discount on one class</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>As users book classes, they can use their points. When all points are used, regular prices apply.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr/>
        <h3><strong>Organize Your Class Schedule</strong></h3>
        <p>Use the <strong>Events App</strong> to manage all your DIY workshops—like sewing, pottery, or open studio time.</p>
        <h4>Set Up Your Event</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Click <strong>Create</strong> in the Events App.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add your workshop details (name, date, location, capacity).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add a <strong>ticket product</strong> for online booking and payment.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Enable Multiple Sessions</h4>
        <p>Perfect for offering a single class at different times:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Activate <strong>Multiple Slots</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Click <strong>Slots</strong> to add specific time options (e.g., Wednesday 6 PM, Saturday 11 AM).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Adjust seat limits and pricing per slot if needed.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Publish on Your Website</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>Website App</strong> to design your event page.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add images, class info, and booking options.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Customers choose a time slot, book online, and pay securely online.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <hr/>
        <h3><strong>Manage Purchases</strong></h3>
        <p>Keep your workshop stocked with materials like fabrics, tools, and supplies.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create a <strong>Purchase Order</strong>: Order the materials you need for upcoming workshops.</li>
            <li>Choose the best vendor: Select the supplier offering the best price and delivery terms.</li>
            <li>Once the purchase is confirmed, send the <strong>Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> via email or confirm it manually.</li>
            <li>When the goods arrive, click the <strong>“Receipt” </strong>smart button to validate the incoming shipment</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you want to go further, manage your workshop materials with the Inventory app. Track stock levels in real time, automate restocking, and monitor supplies to avoid shortages; ensuring your DIY projects always have the materials they need.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr/>
        <h3><strong>Manage Specific Requests and Tailor-Made Orders</strong></h3>
        <h4>Manage Customer Requests</h4>
        <p>
        Track inquiries from your Website (like custom team-building or private DIY sessions). When a group fills the “Contact Us” form, an opportunity is created in the CRM to follow up and convert leads.
        </p>
        <h4>Create Tailored Quotations</h4>
        <p>
        Generate customized Sales Quotations for corporate workshops, birthdays, or group events directly in the Sales app.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Create Quotation Templates for common requests like team-building packages or birthday workshops, to streamline sending offers.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><strong>Workflow Example</strong></h3>
        <ol>
            <li>Organize multi-session classes using the <strong>Events App</strong>, setting capacity and pricing per slot.</li>
            <li>Promote workshops and bookings on your website with the <strong>Website App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Track custom requests from the “Contact Us” form in the <strong>CRM App</strong> to follow up and convert leads.</li>
            <li>Create tailored quotes for groups and corporate events in the <strong>Sales App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Order materials through the <strong>Purchase App</strong>, managing vendors and orders.</li>
            <li>Manage invoicing and payments seamlessly via the <strong>Invoicing App</strong>.</li>
        </ol>
        <h2><span class="h2-fs"><strong>Do You Want to Go Further?</strong></span></h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your flower business:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Track fabrics, threads, paints, and tools and automate stock replenishment using the <strong>Inventory</strong> <strong>app</strong>.</li>
            <li>Define instructor roles like “Beginner Sewing” or “Advanced Woodworking” and schedule them automatically with the <strong>Employees</strong> and <strong>Planning apps</strong>.</li>
            <li>Log and monitor maintenance of studio equipment; sewing machines, looms, kilns, using the <strong>Maintenance app</strong> to keep everything workshop-ready.</li>
            <li>Sell DIY kits, patterns, or craft supplies directly from your website alongside workshop bookings with the <strong>eCommerce </strong>add-on.</li>
            <li>Collect valuable visitor feedback after workshops using the <strong>Surveys app.</strong></li>
            <li>Promote new classes on social media and automate client communication using <strong>Social Marketing</strong> and <strong>WhatsApp</strong> integration.</li>
            <li>Easily handle your accounting with the integrated <strong>Accounting App</strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>
    
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for DIY Workshops</field>
        <field name="icon">🧵</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_12"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
