<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="sale_order_template_1" model="sale.order.template">
    <field name="name">Group Workshop – Team Building Activity</field>
    <field name="note"><![CDATA[
        <h3 data-oe-version="2.0"> <strong>Terms &amp; Conditions</strong></h3>
        <ol>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Booking Confirmation</strong></p>
              <p>
                The booking is confirmed upon acceptance of this quotation and payment of the full amount (or as per agreed payment terms). Early confirmation ensures workshop date availability.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Payment Terms</strong></p>
              <p>
                Payment is due within 7 days of invoice date, and no later than 48 hours before the scheduled workshop. For late bookings, payment is required immediately upon acceptance.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Cancellation Policy</strong></p>
              <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>Cancellations made more than 7 days before the event will be refunded in full.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>Cancellations made within 7 days of the event will incur a 50% fee.</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>No-shows or cancellations within 48 hours of the workshop are non-refundable.</p>
                </li>
              </ul>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Rescheduling</strong></p>
              <p>
                One free reschedule is permitted up to 72 hours before the scheduled date, subject to availability.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Liability &amp; Safety</strong></p>
              <p>
                DIY Atelier is not responsible for any injuries or damages resulting from misuse of equipment during the workshop. All participants are expected to follow safety instructions and behave respectfully in the space.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Apéro Add-On</strong></p>
              <p>
                The apéro includes healthy&nbsp;snacks and non-alcoholic beverages.&nbsp;
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Allergies &amp; Dietary Requirements</strong></p>
              <p>
                Please inform us of any dietary restrictions at least 72 hours before the workshop if an apéro is included.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Materials &amp; Tools</strong></p>
              <p>
                All essential materials and tools will be provided unless otherwise specified. Damaged or lost equipment may be charged at cost.
              </p>
          </li>
          <li>
              <p><strong>Photos &amp; Social Media</strong></p>
              <p>
                We occasionally take photos during workshops to share on our website and social media. Please inform us in advance if any participants prefer not to be photographed.
              </p>
          </li>
        </ol>
    ]]></field>
    <field name="mail_template_id" ref="sale.mail_template_sale_confirmation"/>
    <field name="require_signature" eval="True"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
