<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0">Odoo for Concert Halls</h1>
        <p>Odoo empowers concert halls with a suite of integrated tools that simplify event planning, streamline operations, and enhance the audience experience.</p>
        <p>From organizing concerts to managing ticket sales and backstage logistics, Odoo offers an all-in-one solution tailored for live event venues.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><span class="h1-fs">Basics</span></h2>
        <hr />
        <p><strong>Apps &amp; What They Do:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Events</strong>: Plan, publish, and manage concerts with registrations and attendance tracking.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website</strong>: Create a public page with all event info and enable online bookings.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Point of Sale</strong>: Sell tickets and refreshments on-site with real-time sync.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>CRM</strong>: Track leads and partnerships with sponsors, agencies, and groups.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Projects</strong>: Coordinate all behind-the-scenes tasks for smooth show execution.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Social Marketing</strong>: Boost event visibility through scheduled social media campaigns.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every feature of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr />
        <h2>Event Management 🎟️</h2>
        <p>Plan your concert from A to Z: define times, artists, ticket tiers, and automate follow-ups. Publish event details on your website and track every registration up to the entrance scan.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Events</strong>: Create event details, schedule, tickets, pricing, and reminders.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website</strong>: Design a beautiful event page for online bookings.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Attendance</strong>: Monitor registrations and scan tickets at the entrance.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>Organize events, publish online, sell tickets, and manage attendees all from one place.</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/marketing/events.html">Events Documentation</a></p>
        <hr />
        <h2>Point of Sale 🏧</h2>
        <p>Sell tickets or refreshments directly from your bar or ticket desk. Easy to use, fast, and integrated.</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Sell entrances </strong>: See available tickets for each of the concerts</li>
            <li><strong>Sell drinks &amp; Snacks: </strong>Sell drinks &amp; snacks before the concerts</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>It's easy to add new categories, for merchandise for example, to the Point of Sale. If it's a separate point of sale, creating a new one and restricting its categories to the desired category can be done in the settings app.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Point of Sale Documentation</a></p>
        <hr />
        <h2>CRM 🌟</h2>
        <p>Manage your B2B and internal relationships. Use CRM to track incoming leads (e.g. companies, sponsors, artists, indie bookings, etc).</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Track potential bookings, partner discussions, and promotional inquiries</li>
            <li>Centralize all discussion relating to the opportunity, and obtain detailed reporting</li>
            <li>Create quotes on the go, and generate invoices when needed</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>With Odoo Studio, you can also directly link tags to the radio button menu on the website contact form.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html">CRM Documentation</a></p>
        <hr />
        <h2>Project Management 🌄</h2>
        <p>From artist logistics to stage setup, use projects and tasks to coordinate all activities across departments.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Projects</strong>: Plan and assign tasks for transportation, accommodation, tech setup, and more.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Project and Task Templates: </strong>Recurring tasks &amp; Projects can be managed easily through the templates feature.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Get an instant overview </strong>: need to understand what needs to be done? The Project Stages and Status icons give you an instant overview of where things are at, and what needs to be prioritized.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>It's also possible to automatically create a project when a sale is concluded for maximum automation.</p>
                <p>Tip: on a product, define the "create on order" settings.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html">Project Documentation</a></p>
        <hr />
        <h2>Social Marketing 📣</h2>
        <p>Keep your fans updated with promotional posts. Schedule social media campaigns to boost event awareness.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Social Marketing</strong>: Plan and post across Instagram, Facebook, and more.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Link Tracker</strong>: Measure performance of your campaigns.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Don't forget to check out our email marketing tool for newsletter management.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/marketing/social_marketing.html">Social Marketing Documentation</a></p>
        <hr />
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <div>
                    <strong>
                        <span class="h2-fs">
                            Tips for Success<br />
                            <br />
                        </span>
                    </strong>
                </div>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <strong><span class="h2-fs"></span></strong><span class="h5-fs">Create your events in advance and use early-bird tickets to generate interest.</span>
                    </li>
                    <li class="h5-fs">Link your POS with inventory to never run out of popular items at the bar.</li>
                    <li class="h5-fs">Use the chatter feature in CRM and Projects to centralize communication.</li>
                    <li class="h5-fs">Automate reminders and email confirmations to reduce no-shows.</li>
                    <li>
                        <span class="h5-fs">Analyze attendance and sales data post-event to improve your next one.</span><strong><span class="h2-fs"></span></strong><br />
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><br /></h1>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Once your core operations are running smoothly, consider expanding your toolset:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Email Marketing</strong>: Send newsletters and pre-sales to loyal fans.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting</strong>: Keep track of income from sales, donations, and sponsors.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Dashboards</strong>: Visualize performance with real-time KPIs.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Planning</strong>: Coordinate volunteers, bar staff, and sound engineers.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Purchase</strong>: Reorder supplies, drinks, and gear ahead of events.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Inventory</strong>: Stay on top of merch and bar stock levels.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>eCommerce</strong>: Sell merchandise online to your audience.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sign</strong>: Send and sign artist contracts or venue agreements digitally.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>Curious about what else Odoo can do for your tour business? Let’s explore it together.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><br /></h1>
        <p><br /></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Concert Halls</field>
        <field name="icon">🎸</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
