<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="event_event_1" model="event.event">
        <field name="name">Wine Tasting - Bordeaux</field>
        <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(/web/image/wine_merchant.ir_attachment_1161)","background_color_class":"o_cc3 o_cc","opacity":"0.4","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover"}]]></field>
        <field name="description"><![CDATA[<section class="s_text_block o_colored_level" data-name="Text">
                <h5>Join us for this exclusive event</h5>
                <p>Join us for an enchanting evening of wine exploration at our Bordeaux Bliss wine tasting event! Immerse yourself in the rich heritage and exquisite flavors of one of the world’s most celebrated wine regions. </p><p>On April 8, from 17:30pm, we invite wine enthusiasts and novices alike to gather at our winery for a delightful experience that will transport you straight to the sun-drenched vineyards of Bordeaux, France. </p><p>As you sip on a carefully curated selection of Bordeaux wines, ranging from the robust reds of the Left Bank to the elegant whites of the Right Bank, our expert sommelier will guide you through the unique characteristics and stories behind each bottle. Learn about the renowned grape varieties, the art of blending, and the influence of terroir that make Bordeaux wines so exceptional.</p><p>The evening will feature:</p><ul><li>A tasting of [insert number] exquisite Bordeaux wines, including iconic châteaux and hidden gems.</li><li>Pairing of artisanal cheeses and gourmet bites that complement the wines perfectly.</li><li>Engaging discussions and insights into the history and culture of Bordeaux winemaking.</li><li>A chance to mingle with fellow wine lovers and share your own experiences.</li></ul><p>Whether you’re a seasoned connoisseur or just beginning your wine journey, Bordeaux Bliss promises to be an unforgettable evening filled with flavor, knowledge, and camaraderie. </p><p>Reserve your spot today and raise a glass to the timeless elegance of Bordeaux!</p><p>We look forward to sharing this exquisite experience with you! Cheers!</p>
            </section>]]></field>
        <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
        <field name="stage_id" ref="event.event_stage_done"/>
        <field name="date_tz">Europe/Brussels</field>
        <field name="date_begin" model="res.users" eval="
            pytz.timezone(obj().env.user.tz or 'UTC').localize(
                DateTime.now().replace(hour=15, minute=30) + relativedelta(months=4, weekday=2)
            ).astimezone(pytz.UTC).replace(tzinfo=None)
        "/>
        <field name="date_end" model="res.users" eval="
            pytz.timezone(obj().env.user.tz or 'UTC').localize(
                DateTime.now().replace(hour=19, minute=30) + relativedelta(months=4, weekday=2)
            ).astimezone(pytz.UTC).replace(tzinfo=None)
        "/>
        <field name="country_id" ref="base.be"/>
        <field name="image_1024" type="base64" file="wine_merchant/static/src/binary/event_event/1-image_1024"/>
    </record>
    <record id="event_event_2" model="event.event">
        <field name="name">Oenology Class</field>
        <field name="cover_properties"><![CDATA[{"background-image":"url(/web/image/wine_merchant.ir_attachment_1161)","background_color_class":"o_cc3 o_cc","opacity":"0.4","resize_class":"o_half_screen_height o_record_has_cover"}]]></field>
        <field name="description"><![CDATA[<section class="s_text_block o_colored_level" data-name="Text">
                <h5>Join us for this brand new class!</h5><p>Unlock the secrets of wine with our comprehensive 6-month Oenology class! Designed for both beginners and enthusiasts, this immersive program will take you on a journey through the fascinating world of wine production, tasting, and appreciation.</p><p>**Course Highlights:**</p><ul><li>**In-Depth Curriculum:** Explore the science of viticulture, fermentation processes, and the art of blending. Each module is crafted to provide a thorough understanding of the wine-making journey from grape to glass.</li><li>**Hands-On Experience:** Participate in practical workshops, vineyard visits, and tastings that will enhance your sensory skills and deepen your appreciation for different wine styles and regions.</li><li>**Expert Instructors:** Learn from seasoned professionals in the field, including winemakers, sommeliers, and viticulturists, who will share their knowledge and passion for wine.</li><li>**Networking Opportunities:** Connect with fellow wine lovers and industry professionals, expanding your network and enhancing your learning experience.</li></ul><p>**Who Should Enroll:**</p><p>This class is perfect for anyone interested in wine, whether you’re a novice looking to learn the basics or a seasoned enthusiast wanting to deepen your knowledge. No prior experience is necessary!</p><p>Don’t miss this opportunity to elevate your wine knowledge and skills! Secure your spot today and embark on a flavorful journey through the world of oenology. For more information and to register, please visit [Insert Website] or contact us at [Insert Contact Information]. Cheers to your wine education!artners' case studies, methodology or developments. Be there and see directly from the source the features of the new version!</p>
            </section>]]></field>
        <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
        <field name="date_tz">Europe/Brussels</field>
        <field name="date_begin" model="res.users" eval="
            pytz.timezone(obj().env.user.tz or 'UTC').localize(
                DateTime.now().replace(hour=16, minute=30) + relativedelta(months=1, weekday=2)
            ).astimezone(pytz.UTC).replace(tzinfo=None)
        "/>
        <field name="date_end" model="res.users" eval="
            pytz.timezone(obj().env.user.tz or 'UTC').localize(
                DateTime.now().replace(hour=15, minute=30) + relativedelta(months=6, weekday=1)
            ).astimezone(pytz.UTC).replace(tzinfo=None)
        "/>
        <field name="country_id" ref="base.be"/>
        <field name="image_1024" type="base64" file="wine_merchant/static/src/binary/event_event/1-image_1024"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
