<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.1">
        <span class="display-4-fs"><strong>🍷Wine Shop</strong></span><br />
    </h1>
    <p>
        This package is designed to help wine shop owners structure their product offerings, streamline sales, and enhance customer engagement—all within a single, intuitive platform. With Odoo, your catalog will be clear and well-organized,
        making it easy to manage wines, spirits, and exclusive selections effortlessly.
    </p>
    <p>With this module, you can structure your product offer, manage opportunities, sell in your shop and online, organize engaging events and have a clear overview of your purchase as well as your stock levels.</p>
    <p>Ready to embark on this wine journey? Let’s raise a glass to success! 🥂</p>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
    <h2><span class="h1-fs">Basics</span></h2>
    <hr />
    <ul>
        <li>
            The <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>CRM App</strong></font> helps you manage client interactions and track potential leads
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> streamlines quotations
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale App</font></strong> allows you to easily sell wine in your store
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Ecommerce App </font></strong>showcases your different wines and allow customers to buy them online
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Event App</font></strong> will allow your clients to participate in different events around wine
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Inventory App</font></strong> help you manage your stock levels
        </li>
        <li>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase App</font></strong> gathers all the different purchase orders you have made
        </li>
    </ul>
    <h2><span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span></h2>
    <hr />
    <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few demo data.</p>
    <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
    <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable"><p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Wine Shop package and check the related box.</p></div>
    </div>
    <h2><span class="h1-fs">Flows</span></h2>
    <hr />
    <h3>Flow 1: Create your products database in a clear and structured way</h3>
    <p>Create your products and use <strong>attributes and attribute values</strong> to structure and classify them</p>
    <ol>
        <li>Open the products menu (from the sales or inventory application) and create a new product. Choose well your name to keep a good structure among all products; Ex: name of the bottle - domain - vintage</li>
        <li>Assign <strong>attributes and attribute values</strong> to this product</li>
        <li>Give it a <strong>sales price </strong></li>
        <li>Choose the right<strong> Unit of Measure</strong> (bottle) and create different<strong> packagings</strong> (case)</li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>Demo attributes and attribute values have been added but feel free to add as many attributes and attribute values as you would like!</p>
            <p>
                Find here documentation about product packagings:
                <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/fr/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/product_management/configure/packaging.html">Configure Product Packagings</a>
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Flow 2: Manage leads and client relationship with the CRM App and create your first sale order with the Sales App</h3>
    <p>Track potential clients and manage interactions effectively.</p>
    <ol>
        <li>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong>, create a new lead for a particular wishing to order a large quantity of different wines and assign the lead to a team member</li>
        <li>Log meetings, calls, and emails directly in the CRM. Use the pipeline to<strong> track the progress of each lead</strong> (e.g., New → Qualified → Proposition → Won)</li>
        <li>Once your lead has shown interest, generate a <strong>quotation in the Sales App</strong> offering your different wines</li>
        <li>Add the products to the quotation and send it by email to your customer</li>
        <li>Once your customer confirmed the quotation, you can transfor it into a sale order and...voila!</li>
        <li class="oe-nested"><br /></li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>To speed up the creation of the quotation use a quotation template.</p>
            <p><a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales/send_quotations/quote_template.html">Configure quotation templates</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Flow 3: Sell your products online...</h3>
    <ol>
        <li>Open your website, add different blocks to build the perfect website. Get your clients to know you, your offer and the events you organize</li>
        <li>The shop page will automatically showcase your different products</li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>The Ecommerce categories will help you structure and organize your online catalog making it easier for customers to browse and find what they need.</p>
            <p>The attributes defined on the products will allow your customers to filter on different attribute values to refine their search.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p>2. Add products to your cart, choose your favorite <strong>payment provider</strong> and <strong>delivery method</strong></p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>Activate payment and delivery methods.</p>
            <p>
                <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/ecommerce/checkout_payment_shipping/payments.html">Configure payment providers</a> and
                <a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/fr/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/shipping_receiving/setup_configuration.html">Configure delivery methods</a>
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Flow 4: ... or in your shop with the Point of Sale App</h3>
    <p>From the POS app</p>
    <ol>
        <li>Select the customer</li>
        <li>Add the products to the cart</li>
        <li>Select any of the payment methods and proceed to payment</li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>For a more structured point of sale catalog, create different Point of Sale categories. These can be defined on your product forms.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Flow 5: Organize events around wine with our Events App</h3>
    <p>Organize sparkling events in your shop!</p>
    <ol>
        <li>Open the Events App</li>
        <li>Configure your next event. Wheter it's an oenology class, a wine tasting or a special event, configure the <strong>tickets, pricing, communication</strong> around it,...</li>
        <li>Write an attracting <strong>description</strong></li>
        <li>Publish it on your website</li>
        <li>On your website, your customers will now be able to buy tickets for your different events and you will be able to manage the participants from the Events App</li>
    </ol>
    <h3>Flow 6: Manage the replenishment of your products with the Purchase App and your stock levels with the Inventory App</h3>
    <p>Track your purchases and manage your stock levels</p>
    <ol>
        <li>You recently did a tour of the vineyards in France or in Italy and you wish to keep a trace of your recent purchases? Record them in the<strong> purchase app</strong></li>
        <li>This will allow you to<strong> plan your receptions</strong> and know when your stock will be replenished with your novelties or best sellers</li>
        <li>Once you have received your products <strong>store</strong> them in your shop or warehouse</li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
            <p>Want to make sure you never run out of stock? Check our different replenishment strategies</p>
            <p><a class="btn btn-fill-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/warehouses_storage/replenishment.html">Replenishment strategies</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p><br /></p>
    <hr />
    <p><br /></p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3">
            <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p><br /></p>
  </template>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Wine Shop</field>
    <field name="icon">🍷</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_8"/>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
  </record>
  </odoo>
