<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>
            <strong><span class="display-4-fs">Catering</span></strong><br/>
        </h1>
        <p>
            Welcome to the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Odoo Catering package.</font></strong>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            This module helps you manage every step of the process, from initial customer relationships to event planning and execution. With it, you can effortlessly prepare and validate events, purchase the necessary raw materials, and
            efficiently track your entire operation.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Boost your team's efficiency and improve customer satisfaction across all your catering services with this powerful tool.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">​</span><br/></p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    <font class="text-o-color-1"><b>The CRM &amp; Sales Apps:</b></font> Manage all your client contacts and quotations.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">The Project &amp; planning Apps:</font></b> Manage event-related tasks and track their progress through customizable stages.
            </li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">The Purchase App:</font></b> Accurately track all purchased and rented products.
            </li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">The Invoice App:</font></b> Keep a clear record of all your invoices.
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    <font class="text-o-color-1"><b>The Website App:</b></font> Use this app as a virtual showroom and a powerful tool for generating new leads.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to <b>manage your entire business from your phone</b>.<s><br/></s>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Activities</strong></span><br/>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">To get a rapid understanding of the processes this Odoo package offers, you can execute the following flows and configure the settings to suit your catering business.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Catering package and select the relevant checkbox</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <h3><br/></h3>
        </ul>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage Quotation and Sales Order 🤝</span></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            Customers can submit a quote request directly from your website. You can then use the <b>CRM app</b> to communicate with them via the chatter feature to clarify their needs and validate pre-sales steps like a menu tasting.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p style="text-align: justify;">You can also use a contact's email to automatically create an opportunity in your CRM pipeline.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Once everything is clear, you can generate the final quote.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            To speed up your sales process, use <b>Quotation Templates</b> for rapid quote creation. Additionally, the <b>Catalog</b> feature is an excellent tool for quickly adding all required products to each section of your quote.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">After the quote is approved, a new <b>project</b> will be created automatically to manage all event-related tasks.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <strong><u>Quotation process: (Follow the Sarah Davis Opportunity from the Demo Data)</u></strong>
        </p>
        <ol>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">Manually create an opportunity only if it hasn't been automatically generated by Odoo.</li>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">
            Use the chat feature to communicate with the client and understand their specific needs.
            <ol>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                To speed up the sending process, use an <b>email template</b> in the chatter when sharing your <b>Catalog</b>.
            </li>
            </ol>
        </li>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">
            Schedule a food tasting by creating a meeting directly from the task.
            <ol>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                Starting with version 19.1, you can use predefined meeting templates to automatically fill in details like location and email reminders.
            </li>
            </ol>
        </li>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">
            Once the client's needs are clear, generate a quote using a quotation template for efficiency.
            <ol>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">
                Use the section settings to hide detailed prices or the composition of your items.
            </li>
            </ol>
        </li>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">
            The Section feature allows you to mark products as optional. This lets the customer choose, directly from the live quotation signature, whether to add those products to the final sales order.
        </li>
        <li style="text-align: justify;">
            Wait for client approval. They can sign the quotation online.
        </li>
        </ol>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h2-fs">
                <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html">🎓 CRM</a>
                <span class="h2-fs"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html">🎓 Sales</a></span>
            </span>
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To prevent Odoo from automatically creating a delivery, <b>set all products on the quotation as service products.</b></p>
                <p>
                    Want to create a stunning quotation? Explore the <strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Quote Builder</a></strong> feature. <b></b>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><br/></h3>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Project Management 🥗</span></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">For better project management, <b>use predefined templates</b> to ensure all necessary tasks are already created.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Create a Project Template</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Go to the <b>Project app</b> and <b>create a project</b>. This project will become your reusable template.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
                    <li>Define the template's timeline by setting the <b>Plan Date</b>. (For example December 1st–31st).</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
                    <li><b>Adapt the stages and tasks</b> to match your standard workflow.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
                    <li>Set a specific <b>Plan Date</b> on each individual task.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>The dates you set establish automated, relative deadlines:</p>
                <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
                    <p>
                        If the template's overall plan is December 1st–31st and a critical task is set for December 1st–2nd, <b>any new project</b> generated from this template will automatically schedule that task to occur one month
                        <i>before</i> the new project's completion date. This mechanism ensures key deadlines are set automatically.
                    </p>
                </blockquote>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Once the structure and dates are finalized, use the <b>⚙️ icon</b> on the project and select the option to <b>Convert to Template</b>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Use the <b>Properties</b> feature to ensure you capture all necessary data by clicking on the <b>⚙️ icon</b> from the project or a task and choose <b>Edit Properties</b>.</p>
                        <ul>
                            <li>
                                <p>This allows you to add custom fields—such as <b>text areas, images, or documents</b>—to collect specific information exactly where it's needed within the template.</p>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">To effectively automate your <b>Quotation / Project</b> workflow, follow this process. For a simple example, use the <b>Sarah Davis Sales order</b> found in the <b>Demo Data</b>.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Catering package and select the relevant checkbox</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            The <b>"1 Day Wedding" service product</b> is configured to trigger automatic project creation. When the sales order is confirmed, a new project is instantly generated from the <b>"1 Day B2C Project" template </b>(thanks to the product
            settings).
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">To ensure correct date calculation across all tasks, the <b>Sales Order delivery date</b> is automatically set to match the <b>last date of the generated project</b>.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Furthermore, specific services listed on the quotation, such as <b>"Custom Menu Design,"</b> are set to <b>"Create Task,"</b> which adds a corresponding task with the same name to the new project.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            Once the <b>Sales Order is confirmed</b>, the project is automatically created. The <b>project's top bar</b> then becomes your central hub, giving you quick access to essential management tools like
            <b>invoices, purchase orders, time tracking, planning,</b> and other resources.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">The dashboard also provides an immediate view of your <b>project's profitability</b>.</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html">🎓 Project</a></p>
        <h3><br/></h3>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage Purchases and Deliveries 🚚</span><b></b><br/></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            For large catering events, different types of logistics are required to get all the products and materials where they need to go. By registering these movements in Odoo, you can ensure every item is accounted for. Here's how to manage
            each type of purchase and delivery.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h4-fs">
                <b><u>Supplier to Workshop</u></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Use this process for items that need to be delivered to your workshop for food preparation or storage.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Create a <b>Purchase Order</b> directly from the project.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Add all necessary products (we recommend using goods without tracking to avoid complexity).</p></li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Validate the purchase order.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Once validated, a <b>receipt</b> will be automatically generated at your workshop, ready for the delivery.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h4-fs">
                <b><u>Supplier to Event Location</u></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">For items like beverages or rented materials that are delivered directly to the event, use a dropship operation. Before you begin, be sure the event location is registered in your contacts.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Create a <b>Purchase Order</b> directly from the project.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Add the necessary products.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Select <b>Dropship Delivery</b> and choose the correct event location.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Validate the purchase order.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">This will generate a dropship operation that goes directly to the event location.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h4-fs">
                <b><u>Workshop to Event Location</u></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Use this process for food and materials that have been prepared at your workshop and need to be delivered to the event venue.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">From the project's top bar, click <b>"From WH"</b> to create a new delivery.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Select the destination location (the event venue).</p></li>
            <li><p style="text-align: justify;">Add the products to be delivered.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Mark the delivery as <b>"To Do."</b></p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">By following these steps, all of your receipts and deliveries will be registered in Odoo, creating a clear checklist and reminders for every necessary stock operation linked to the event.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Currently, we only use products as a checklist to ensure nothing is forgotten, meaning we don't track stock of each item. If your business scales and requires accurate inventory tracking, you'll need to activate product tracking
                    and refer to the Inventory app documentation.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Inventory</a></p>
        <h3><br/></h3>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Staff Planning &amp; Scheduling 🗓️</span><b></b><br/></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">The planning application facilitates <b>increased efficiency</b> in project planning by enabling the <b>prior configuration of all necessary settings</b>.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><b>In the Planning App</b><br/></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Input all <b>employees</b> into the configuration. (Note: These employees are for planning purposes, are <b>not Odoo users</b>, and <b>do not generate extra Odoo costs</b>.)</p>
                        <ul>
                            <li>
                                <p>Set an <b>hourly cost</b> for each employee if you plan to track labor costs.</p>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create <b>specific roles</b> for your project (e.g., Waiter, Maître d'hôtel, Kitchen Porter).</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Assign employees to one or more of these specific roles.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create <b>"Shift Templates"</b> to easily build the planning schedule for your project. (This streamlines the creation of recurring or common shift patterns.)</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            You can access the <b>Planning tool</b> via a button in the <b>top bar</b> of the Project app. This tool allows you to <b>efficiently prepare and schedule</b> the necessary workers for your event. Simply
            <b>select the desired shift</b> on the corresponding dates to create it.
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To see the pre-existing plan and the shifts that still require scheduling, please select an additional 40 days, now that the demo data is uploaded.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You need to duplicate several time the same shift? press Ctrl and move the shift, it will duplicate it automatically.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">After creating the shifts, <b>assign them to the appropriate employees</b> to guarantee that every shift is covered and to <b>prevent any double booking</b> across simultaneous events.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Once shifts are assigned, <b>publish and send them</b> to ensure every employee receives a confirmation email detailing their schedule.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To take your project planning to the next level, explore these powerful features:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Service Product Integration:</b> Automatically generate shifts in your planning schedule directly from your service products.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Resource-Based Auto-Planning:</b> Use the auto-plan feature to schedule shifts efficiently based on your available resources.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Material Tracking:</b> Track specific materials within your planning to ensure you have everything needed for the project.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/planning.html">🎓 Planning</a></p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Invoicing Clients 💵</span><b></b><br/></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;">You can easily invoice clients directly from a <b>Sales Order</b>. Each order allows you to set specific <b>payment terms and conditions</b> tailored to that client or project.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            When you're ready, you have the flexibility to create an invoice for either a full or a partial payment, such as a down payment. All invoices generated are tracked and can be managed through the <b>Invoices app</b>.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting/customer_invoices.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Invoicing</a></p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Manage your website 🌐</span></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>You can easily tailor your website to provide the information you want for potential leads. When a client contacts you through the contact page, their submission will automatically create a new opportunity in your CRM pipeline.</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html">🎓 Website</a></p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h1 style="text-align: justify;">Do you want to go further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Accounting made easy 🧮</strong></p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Use the <strong>Accounting</strong> app to easily handle:</p>
        <ul>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">The customer reminders.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">The vendor bills payment.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">The synchronization with the banks.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">The financial reporting.</li>
        </ul>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">🎓 Accounting</a></p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs"><b>Survey ⁉️</b></span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs"><b></b>Use the Survey App to send survey to your customer after the events.</span><br/>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <b><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/marketing/surveys.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Survey</a></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <b>️<span class="h6-fs">Centralize document 📄</span></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">Use the <b>Document</b> app to manage all your internal and external documents and use the Sign App for automated customer signature</span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <b>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Document</a>
                    <span class="h6-fs"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/sign.html">🎓 Sign</a> </span>
                </b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs"><b>Follow your meal Production 🍳</b></span><br/>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs"><b></b>Use the Manufacturing App to create recipes and follow the stock of your raw material</span><br/>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <b><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/quality.html">🎓 Manufacturing</a></b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <span class="h6-fs"><b></b></span>
            </span>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Catering</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">🍢</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
  </odoo>
