<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_team_meetings" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Team meetings</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="welcome_article"/>
        <field name="icon">📆</field>
        <field name="full_width" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="article_properties_definition" eval="[
            {'name': 'note_taker', 'type': 'many2one',  'domain': False,'string': 'Note taker','comodel': 'hr.employee','default': False},
            {'name': 'care_workers', 'type': 'many2many', 'domain': '[(&quot;planning_role_ids&quot;, &quot;in&quot;, [1])]',  'string': 'Care Workers',  'comodel': 'hr.employee',  'default': False},
            {'name': 'resident_focus', 'type': 'many2many', 'domain': '[(&quot;x_is_resident&quot;, &quot;!=&quot;, False)]',    'string': 'Resident focus', 'comodel': 'res.partner', 'default': False}
        ]"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_team_meetings" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="body" type="html">
            <h1 class="oe-hint">Team meetings</h1>
            <div data-embedded="view" data-oe-protected="true" data-embedded-props="{
                &quot;viewProps&quot;: {
                    &quot;actionXmlId&quot;: &quot;knowledge.knowledge_article_item_action&quot;,
                    &quot;displayName&quot;: &quot;Team meeting&quot;,
                    &quot;viewType&quot;: &quot;list&quot;,
                    &quot;context&quot;: {
                        &quot;active_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_team_meetings)d,
                        &quot;default_parent_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_team_meetings)d,
                        &quot;default_is_article_item&quot;: true
                    }
                }
            }"></div>
            <p>
                <br/>
            </p>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_team_meeting_1" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Team meeting 2026-03-18</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_team_meetings"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="article_properties" eval="{'resident_focus': [ref('community_care.res_partner_42'), ref('community_care.res_partner_24'), ref('community_care.res_partner_36'), ref('community_care.res_partner_27'), ref('community_care.res_partner_31'), ref('community_care.res_partner_13'), ref('community_care.res_partner_21'), ref('community_care.res_partner_39'), ref('community_care.res_partner_42'), ref('community_care.res_partner_42'), ref('community_care.res_partner_42')],
        'care_workers':[ref('community_care.hr_employee_1'), ref('community_care.hr_employee_5'), ref('community_care.hr_employee_4'), ref('community_care.hr_employee_3')],
        'note_taker':ref('community_care.hr_employee_4')
        }"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Team meeting 2026-03-18</h1>
        <h2>Items Discussed</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Review of Success Stories (Positive Care Highlights):</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Karen presented on Willa Good's successful first month. Her adjustment to the center has been exceptionally positive, and her daily hygiene routines are well-established.</li>
                    <li>Ed highlighted Story Turner's latest vocational project; they completed their portfolio cover, which is now in the <b>Scholar &amp; Future</b> section.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Behavioral Strategy Workshop (Herb Choke):</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Will B. Kind led a discussion on refining de-escalation protocols for Herb Choke. The focus was on identifying environmental triggers and standardizing staff responses during transition times.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Legal Compliance Update (Admin &amp; Legal):</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Abe noted a need for urgent review regarding Link Wire's legal representation network map. A core legal document in his folder is outdated and needs re-signing.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Mental Health Observation (Health &amp; Medical):</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Karen raised concerns regarding Hope Case. A change in dietary habits and social withdrawal has been observed.</li>
                    <li>Will discussed strategies to encourage Sony Sunshine's participation in group therapies without adding pressure.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Goal Setting and Life Paths:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Penny Save's upcoming personal financial literacy course assignment was finalized.</li>
                    <li>A review of Margie Up's transition plan (Life Path &amp; Logs) was delayed due to lack of mentorship input.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Consistency in Behavior Plans:</b> Consistency from <i>all</i> staff members is the critical missing component for Herb Choke's behavioral stability. A written plan is useless if not followed uniformly.</li>
            <li><b>Early Intervention on Health:</b> Hope Case's change in behavior requires immediate medical consultation and proactive emotional support before the situation escalates.</li>
            <li><b>Documentation Urgency:</b> The Legal Network mapping for Link Wire must take absolute priority to ensure compliance before next month's court date review.</li>
            <li><b>Mentorship Bridge Needed:</b> Despite the mentorship coordinator's absence, mentorship targets (specifically for Margie Up) must still move forward.</li>
        </ol>
        <h2>Actions</h2>
        <ul class="o_checklist">
            <li class="o_checked"><strong>Abe: </strong>Coordinate a priority video conference between the legal team, Link Wire, and his legal guardian to finalize updated representation documents.</li>
            <li class="o_checked"><strong>Will: </strong>Formalize the agreed de-escalation plan for Herb Choke and conduct a 15-minute training brief for the night shift staff.</li>
            <li><strong>Karen: </strong>Schedule a Health &amp; Medical check-up appointment for Hope Case and begin a daily detailed observation log on her mood and intake changes.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_team_meeting_template" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Template - Team meeting</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_team_meetings"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_listed_in_templates_gallery" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Team meeting YYYY-MM-DD</h1>
        <h2>Items Discussed</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ol>
        <h2>Actions</h2>
        <ul class="o_checklist">
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_logs" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Handover logs</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="welcome_article"/>
        <field name="icon">✍️</field>
        <field name="full_width" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="article_properties_definition" eval="[
            {'name': 'dcfe776bed332994', 'type': 'many2one',  'domain': '[(&quot;planning_role_ids&quot;, &quot;in&quot;, [1])]',  'string': 'Outgoing Care Worker', 'comodel': 'hr.employee',  'default': False, 'view_in_cards': True},
            {'name': '8fe9a8428916b08b', 'type': 'many2many', 'domain': '[(&quot;x_is_resident&quot;, &quot;!=&quot;, False)]',    'string': 'Resident focus',       'comodel': 'res.partner', 'default': False}
        ]"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_logs" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="body" type="html">
            <h1 class="oe-hint">Handover logs</h1>
            <div data-embedded="view" data-oe-protected="true" data-embedded-props="{
                &quot;viewProps&quot;: {
                    &quot;actionXmlId&quot;: &quot;knowledge.knowledge_article_item_action&quot;,
                    &quot;displayName&quot;: &quot;Handover log&quot;,
                    &quot;viewType&quot;: &quot;list&quot;,
                    &quot;context&quot;: {
                        &quot;active_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_handover_logs)d,
                        &quot;default_parent_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_handover_logs)d,
                        &quot;default_is_article_item&quot;: true
                    }
                }
            }"></div>
            <p>
                <br/>
            </p>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_log_1" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Handover log</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_handover_logs"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Handover log</h1>
        <h2>Shift Overview &amp; Atmosphere</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Overall Mood:</b> High energy in the afternoon, specifically during the transition from outdoor play to indoor study. We had a brief "volume spike" in the common area, but it did not escalate into a full incident.</li>
            <li><b>Safety/Site Check:</b> All sensory "cool-down" kits were restocked at 16:00. Weighted blankets in the "Reset Space" have been sanitized. Emergency exit paths are clear.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Resident Detailed Anecdotes &amp; Status</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Herb Choke</b> (Behavioral/Sensory focus): Herb had a successful afternoon. We practiced the "Lowering Palms" signal during a high-volume moment in the gym; he responded immediately without a verbal reminder. He spent 20 minutes in "Heavy Work" (helping move the gym mats), which significantly grounded him before dinner. No outbursts recorded.</li>
            <li><b>Addy Ding</b> (Transition/Focus focus): Addy was deep into a Blender render. I provided the 10-minute and 5-minute warnings as per protocol. She saved her work and joined the group for the evening briefing without resistance. She noted that the "noise level" from the younger kids was a bit much today, so I authorized her to use her noise-canceling headphones during the last hour of shift.</li>
            <li><b>Hope Case</b> (Observation/Mental Health focus): Continued monitoring for social withdrawal. She did not join the main table for the afternoon snack but did accept a 1-on-1 check-in. She mentioned feeling "crowded." I moved her study spot to the corner of the library (lower traffic), and she seemed more settled. Watch for any "shut-down" behaviors tonight.</li>
            <li><b>Story Turner</b> (Vocational/Engagement focus): Story is very high on "Achievement Energy" right now because of the portfolio success. They were almost too focused, skipping their water break. I had to prompt them twice to hydrate. They are a great "positive anchor" for the house right now—try to tap into their mood to help lift the atmosphere if things get tense.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Urgent Actions &amp; Follow-ups</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Herb Choke Volume Check (Immediate):</b> If he gets loud during the evening wind-down, use <i>only</i> the hand signals first. Keep verbal interaction low-key.</li>
            <li><b>Hope Case Meal Check (Dinner):</b> See if she will join the table if she is seated at the end/edge. Do not force, but offer the option.</li>
            <li><b>Addy Ding Project Save (21:00):</b> Remind her to back up her 3D files to the cloud. She gets anxious if she thinks her work is "unsaved."</li>
            <li><b>Sensory Room Audit (EOD):</b> Ensure the weighted blanket is returned to the rack if Herb uses it before bed.</li>
        </ol>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_log_2" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Handover log</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_handover_logs"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Handover log</h1>
        <h2>Shift Overview &amp; Atmosphere</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Overall Mood:</b> The house was relatively quiet this evening. Most residents were engaged in individual projects or low-energy social activities. There was a slight tension during dinner prep, but it was managed through one-on-one check-ins.</li>
            <li><b>Safety/Site Check:</b> Perimeter check completed at 21:30. All window locks in the common area verified. The night staff should ensure the kitchen pantry is double-locked before 23:00.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Resident Detailed Anecdotes &amp; Status</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Link Wire</b> (Legal/Admin focus): Spent 45 minutes with Link working on his legal representation network map. He was initially resistant ("It's just more paperwork"), but once we started drawing it out visually, he became much more engaged. He expressed some frustration with the delay in his court date. He needs a calm, listening ear tomorrow morning regarding his "right to be heard."</li>
            <li><b>Dawn View</b> (Developmental/Emotional focus): Dawn was very proud of her "Big Kid" job of organizing the board game shelf. She was wearing her yellow cap throughout the evening. She mentioned missing her parents after a brief phone call; we did 15 minutes of "Feeling Cards" drawing to help her process. She went to bed calmly after the full 20-minute reading routine.</li>
            <li><b>Margie Up</b> (Life Path focus): Margie and I discussed her transition plan. She is feeling "excited-scared" about her projected exit. We focused on her goal of independent living. She requested more information on local vocational workshops. She is in a very reflective headspace—great time for a mentor check-in if <b>Guy Dance</b> is back.</li>
            <li><b>Sony Sunshine</b> (Behavioral/Mental Health focus): Significant win this evening—Sony chose to eat dinner at the main table with the group instead of her room. She didn't initiate much conversation, but her physical presence in the shared space for 30 minutes is a major milestone. Please maintain "Parallel Presence" during the night shift checks—don't force talk, just let her know you're there.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Urgent Actions &amp; Follow-ups</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Link Wire Legal Prep (Priority):</b> Ensure the updated network map is scanned into his <b>Admin &amp; Legal</b> section before the EOW meeting.</li>
            <li><b>Dawn View Morning Check (07:30):</b> Check her mood immediately upon waking. If she mentions the phone call again, steer her toward her "important morning job" to ground her.</li>
            <li><b>Margie Up Resource Search (EOD):</b> Find the brochures for the "Step-Up" vocational workshop for Margie to review tomorrow afternoon.</li>
            <li><b>Sony Sunshine Positive Reinforcement:</b> If she is up for it, give her a specific, low-pressure "thumbs up" for joining the group at dinner.</li>
        </ol>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_log_3" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Handover log</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_handover_logs"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Handover log</h1>
        <h2>Shift Overview &amp; Atmosphere</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Overall Mood:</b> General atmosphere was calm and productive throughout the day. Residents engaged well during study time, but required closer monitoring during free time in the common area after 16:30.</li>
            <li><b>Safety/Site Check:</b> All entry points were secure at 19:00. Fire alarm panel is clear. The night shift check-in with security is due at 23:00.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Resident Detailed Anecdotes &amp; Status</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Herb Choke</b> (Behavioral Strategy focus): Agitated around 15:30. Instead of escalating, I used the proactive 5-minute pre-warning strategy Will suggested for the quiet study transition. He initially huffed but complied and went to his desk without needing further intervention. He is responding well when given clear boundaries and warnings. He did well, but needs positive reinforcement for this successful transition.</li>
            <li><b>Story Turner</b> (Vocational/Scholar focus): Was incredibly focused on their portfolio work for over two hours. They asked for specific assistance on their cover design. They were genuinely proud of the final product. I praised their effort and focus. We need to ensure <b>Ed U. Cator</b> makes a point of seeing it first thing tomorrow morning.</li>
            <li><b>Sony Sunshine</b> (Behavioral/Mental Health focus): Sony was more withdrawn today. Checked on her every 30 minutes. Around 16:00, she consented to sit on the porch for 10 minutes with brief conversation. It wasn't a huge step, but she engaged slightly. Please continue to offer gentle encouragement without pressure during the night shift.</li>
            <li><b>Willa Good</b> (Routine/Positive focus): Willa volunteered to help set the table for dinner and was observed encouraging Penny during study hall. Her routines are well-established. She requested extra quiet time at 21:00 for reading, which is typical for her positive adjustment. Everything is going well.</li>
            <li><b>Penny Save</b> (Task/Goal focus): Penny was visibly struggling with the budget section of her financial literacy assignment. She mentioned wanting help tomorrow morning. She did finish the second module but is feeling overwhelmed. Please encourage her to break the task down and assure her help is scheduled.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Urgent Actions &amp; Follow-ups</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Monitor Herb Choke (Immediate):</b> Verify he has finalized his room setup by 21:00. Confirm the Night Shift has read Will's behavior plan draft.</li>
            <li><strong>Sony Sunshine Observation (Immediate):</strong> Pay extra attention to her mood. If withdrawn, continue gentle checks. Note if there is any change in appetite.</li>
            <li><b>Link Wire Documentation Prep (EOD):</b> Abe, remember that legal mapping is urgent. Double-check if you need to prepare any specific printouts or coordinate logistics for the EOW video conference.</li>
            <li><b>Morning Prep (08:00):</b> Verify that Ed U. Cator has been notified to check Story Turner's portfolio first thing.</li>
        </ol>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_handover_log_template" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Template - Handover log</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_handover_logs"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_listed_in_templates_gallery" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Handover log</h1>
        <h2>Shift Overview &amp; Atmosphere</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Resident Detailed Anecdotes &amp; Status</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Urgent Actions &amp; Follow-ups</h2>
        <ol>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ol>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_residents" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Residents</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="welcome_article"/>
        <field name="icon">🧒</field>
        <field name="full_width" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_residents" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="body" type="html">
            <h1 class="oe-hint">Residents</h1>
            <div data-embedded="view" data-oe-protected="true" data-embedded-props="{
                &quot;viewProps&quot;: {
                    &quot;actionXmlId&quot;: &quot;knowledge.knowledge_article_item_action&quot;,
                    &quot;displayName&quot;: &quot;Resident&quot;,
                    &quot;viewType&quot;: &quot;list&quot;,
                    &quot;context&quot;: {
                        &quot;active_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_residents)d,
                        &quot;default_parent_id&quot;: %(community_care.knowledge_article_residents)d,
                        &quot;default_is_article_item&quot;: true
                    }
                }
            }"></div>
            <p>
                <br/>
            </p>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_herb_choke" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Herb Choke</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_residents"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Herb Choke</h1>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>👤 General</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how to interact and build rapport.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Language Mirroring:</b> Herb is bilingual (English/Spanish). When he is excited or playing, he often mixes the two. Staff are encouraged to use basic Spanish phrases of encouragement to build a sense of "home" and safety.</li>
            <li><b>Volume Control:</b> Herb has a naturally high volume. He isn't always "yelling" out of anger; he simply lacks a baseline for "indoor voice." <b>Strategy:</b> Use visual hand signals (lowering palms) to remind him to adjust his volume rather than verbal shushing, which he can perceive as a challenge.</li>
            <li><b>Trust through Activity:</b> He bonds best through high-energy play. If you need to have a serious conversation, try doing it while playing catch or walking outside; he processes information better when his body is moving.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>⚖️ Admin &amp; Legal</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how Herb perceives and reacts to his legal status.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Stability Sensitivity:</b> Because of his "Ward of the State" status, Herb is hyper-sensitive to staff changes or absences. If a primary worker like <b>Karen Forr</b> is going on leave, Herb needs to be told several days in advance to prevent "abandonment" outbursts.</li>
            <li><b>Parental Context:</b> While Rose Mary and Artie are listed as parents, his legal status implies limited or supervised contact. Check the <i>Daily Supervisor Briefing</i> for the current "Contact allowed" status before mentioning his parents to him.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🏥 Health &amp; Medical</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on the psychological impact of medical conditions, not the list of shots.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Trigger Identification:</b> Loud, sudden noises or crowded rooms can trigger immediate agitation.</li>
            <li><b>The "Reset" Space:</b> Herb has a designated "Calm Down Corner" with heavy blankets. He should be encouraged to go there <i>before</i> an outburst happens. Watch for his "tells": jaw clenching and pacing.</li>
            <li><b>Sensory Diet:</b> Responds well to "heavy work" (carrying books, moving chairs) to help ground his nervous system when he feels a "high energy" spike coming on.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🎓 Scholar &amp; Future</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on what drives him, rather than just his grades.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Task Frustration:</b> Herb has a low threshold for academic frustration, especially with reading. He will often act out (loudly) to avoid admitting he doesn't understand a task.</li>
            <li><b>Strategy:</b> Break schoolwork into "micro-tasks" (5 minutes of work = 2 minutes of movement). <b>Ed U. Cator</b> suggests "gamifying" his learning to keep his competitive nature engaged in a positive way.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>📈 Life Path &amp; Log</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how he moves through the facility and interacts with peers.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>The Mandatory 5-Minute Rule:</b> As established by <b>Will B. Kind</b>, Herb <i>must</i> have a proactive 5-minute warning before any transition (leaving for school, stopping play, bedtime).
                <ul>
                    <li><i>Success Marker:</i> He has recently shown he can comply without agitation if the boundary is clear and the warning is given calmly.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Peer Impact:</b> Herb's outbursts are a major trigger for <b>Addy Ding</b>.
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Action:</b> If Herb begins to escalate, prioritize moving him to a separate room immediately to protect the sensory environment of the other residents.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Positive Reinforcement:</b> He thrives on "Public Praise." Complimenting his successful transitions in front of the group (within reason) builds his pride and reinforces the desired behavior.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_dawn_view" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Dawn View</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_residents"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Dawn View</h1>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>👤 General</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on rapport building with a younger resident.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>The "Big Kid" Approach:</b> Despite being the youngest in the group, Dawn strives for independence. She responds well when given "important" small jobs (e.g., holding the clipboard or picking the fruit for the table).</li>
            <li><b>Tactile Comfort:</b> Dawn is highly attached to her yellow cap (seen in her profile). If she loses it or it's in the wash, her anxiety levels spike. Always ensure she knows where her "comfort items" are before transitions.</li>
            <li><b>Communication:</b> At 8, she can struggle to name complex emotions. Use "Feeling Cards" or drawing as a medium when she is upset rather than asking her to explain "why" verbally.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>⚖️ Admin &amp; Legal</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how Dawn perceives and reacts to her legal status.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Placement Awareness:</b> Dawn often asks when she is "going home." Because her admission is recent (Aug 2024), she is still in the "honeymoon/protest" cycle of adjustment.</li>
            <li><b>Contact Management:</b> While Claire and Misty (parents) are listed, check the daily log for the specific <b>Contact Protocol</b>. She often experiences "re-entry" distress after phone calls. <b>Strategy:</b> Plan a high-engagement activity (like a game or drawing) immediately following any parental contact to help her transition back to the facility routine.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🏥 Health &amp; Medical</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on the psychological impact of medical conditions, not the list of shots.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Bedtime Routine (The Golden Hour):</b> This is her most vulnerable time. She requires a strict "wind-down" sequence: 20 minutes of reading, a nightlight check, and a verbal "Plan for Tomorrow." Skipping these steps often leads to night terrors or sleepwalking.</li>
            <li><b>Physical Activity:</b> She has a high "sensory diet" need. If she starts "fidgeting" or jumping on furniture, it's a sign she needs 15 minutes of outdoor play or a heavy-work task (like carrying a laundry basket) to regulate her system.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🎓 Scholar &amp; Future</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on what drives her, rather than just her grades.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Literacy Spark:</b> She is currently at a 2nd-grade reading level. She is very self-conscious about "hard words." <b>Action:</b> Use "Paired Reading" where you read a paragraph and she reads a sentence. This builds her confidence without the pressure of failure.</li>
            <li><b>Creative Play:</b> Unlike Addy's technical 3D modeling, Dawn is in the "Imaginative Play" stage. She loves building forts and "office" scenarios. This is where she processes her life events; observe her play themes to understand her current emotional state.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>📈 Life Path &amp; Log</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how she moves through the facility and interacts with peers.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Peer Dynamics (The Little Sister):</b>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>With Addy Ding:</b> Dawn looks up to Addy. While Addy likes her space, she is surprisingly patient with Dawn. Use this bond sparingly to help Dawn mirror Addy's focus during study times.</li>
                    <li><b>With Older Residents:</b> Monitor for "people-pleasing." Dawn will sometimes try to act older or use slang she doesn't understand to fit in. Remind her that she is allowed to just "be a kid."</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Transition Fatigue:</b> Because she is younger, she tires faster than the teens. By 19:00, her ability to follow complex instructions drops. Keep evening requests simple and one-step only.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_addy_ding" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Addy Ding</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_residents"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Addy Ding</h1>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>👤 General</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how to interact and build rapport.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Communication Style:</b> Addy is highly logical. She values being told the "Why" behind a rule or a change in schedule. Avoid "Because I said so" or overly emotional appeals.</li>
            <li><b>The "Adding" Nickname:</b> This is a high-trust marker. If you are new or haven't established a bond, stick to "Addy." If she invites you to use her nickname, it's a sign she feels safe in your presence.</li>
            <li><b>Language Nuance:</b> While her record lists her as bilingual, she switches to Arabic primarily when stressed or "shutting down." In these moments, do not force her back into English; allow her to process in her native tongue to de-escalate.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>⚖️ Admin &amp; Legal</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how Addy perceives and reacts to her legal status.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Social Worker Visits:</b> These are high-anxiety events for her. She often feels "prodded." <b>Strategy:</b> Allow her 15 minutes of quiet time immediately after a legal or social worker visit to "reset" before asking her to join group activities.</li>
            <li><b>Autonomy:</b> Because her life is heavily governed by court mandates, she responds exceptionally well to small choices. (e.g., "Would you like to do your paperwork in the study hall or the common area?") Giving her back small pieces of control reduces friction.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🏥 Health &amp; Medical</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on the psychological impact of medical conditions, not the list of shots.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Nut Allergy:</b> Beyond just "no nuts," Addy has a fear of cross-contamination. She may become hyper-vigilant at the dining table. <b>Action:</b> If a new resident is present, quietly reassure Addy that the kitchen has been briefed. Visual confirmation (showing her the label of a "safe" snack) calms her significantly.</li>
            <li><b>Physical Space:</b> She is sensitive to crowded medical environments. If she needs a check-up, try to book the first appointment of the day or wait in a quiet area to prevent sensory overload.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🎓 Scholar &amp; Future</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on what drives her, rather than just her grades.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Blender &amp; 3D Modeling:</b> This is her "Special Interest." If she is having a difficult day, asking her a technical question about her latest 3D render is the fastest way to get her talking and out of a "mood."</li>
            <li><b>Writing as an Incentive:</b> Her sci-fi graphic novel is her most prized project. Using "uninterrupted writing time" is a far more effective reward for completed chores than screen time or sweets.</li>
            <li><b>The "Hard Surface" Focus:</b> She likes things that are "fixable" and "logical." Vocational paths in engineering or coding should be encouraged over more "abstract" arts.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>📈 Life Path &amp; Log</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how she moves through the facility and interacts with peers.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>The 5-Minute Transition Rule:</b> Transitioning between tasks is her primary trigger. Always provide a 10-minute and 5-minute verbal warning before she needs to stop a creative task.</li>
            <li><b>Peer Influence:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>With Penny Save:</b> Addy enjoys the "mentor" role. If she is feeling low, asking her to help Penny with a task can boost her self-esteem.</li>
                    <li><b>With Herb Choke:</b> High friction potential. Addy finds loud, unpredictable noise overstimulating. Proactively offer her noise-canceling headphones if the common area becomes chaotic.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Parallel Play:</b> She doesn't always want to "talk" to be social. She is perfectly happy sitting in the same room as a staff member while both do their own work. This "Quiet Company" is her preferred way to bond.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_resident_template" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Template - Resident</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="knowledge_article_residents"/>
        <field name="is_article_item" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_listed_in_templates_gallery" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Resident Name</h1>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>👤 General</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how to interact and build rapport.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>⚖️ Admin &amp; Legal</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how the resident perceives and reacts to their legal status.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🏥 Health &amp; Medical</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on the psychological impact of medical conditions, not the list of shots.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>🎓 Scholar &amp; Future</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on what drives the resident, rather than just their grades.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        <h2>📈 Life Path &amp; Log</h2>
        <p><i>Focuses on how the resident moves through the facility and interacts with peers.</i></p>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>

    <record id="knowledge_article_policies" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Policies</field>
        <field name="parent_id" ref="welcome_article"/>
        <field name="icon">▶️</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Policies</h1>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"/>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Resident Rights Policy</h2>
        <p><b>Policy Statement:</b> [Facility Name] is committed to ensuring that every resident is treated with dignity, respect, and fairness. This policy outlines the fundamental rights guaranteed to all residents under our care, aligned with national standards and human rights conventions.</p>
        <p><b>1. General Principles</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Dignity and Respect:</b> Every resident has the right to be treated with consideration and respect for their personal dignity, independence, and individuality. This includes the right to be addressed by their preferred name.</li>
            <li><b>Non-Discrimination:</b> Access to care, services, and participation in programs will not be denied based on race, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, religion, disability, or age.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>2. Core Resident Rights</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Safety and Freedom from Abuse:</b> The right to live in a safe environment and to be free from physical, emotional, sexual, and verbal abuse, neglect, and financial exploitation.</li>
            <li><b>Privacy:</b> The right to personal privacy, including:
                <ul>
                    <li>Privacy during medical examinations and treatment.</li>
                    <li>Privacy in written, telephone, and electronic communications.</li>
                    <li>Privacy of personal records (aligned with our Confidentiality SOP).</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li><b>Informed Choice and Participation:</b> The right to be fully informed about their care plan, health status, and life goals. They have the right to participate in making decisions regarding their care and life choices (e.g., contributing to their Life Goals Plan).</li>
            <li><b>Communication:</b> The right to free, private, and uncensored communication with persons outside the facility (social workers, guardians, family, legal counsel) within reasonable guidelines set for safety and wellbeing.</li>
            <li><b>Personal Property:</b> The right to retain and use personal property, clothing, and possessions within reasonable limits established for safety and hygiene.</li>
            <li><b>Complaint and Grievance:</b> The right to file a complaint or grievance without fear of retaliation or discrimination. Residents must be informed of the formal procedure to submit such grievances and to receive a timely, respectful response.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>3. Care Worker Responsibility</b><br/>
        It is the mandatory responsibility of <i>all</i> care workers, mentors, and administrators to understand, uphold, and actively protect these rights in all daily interactions and interventions.</p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Incident Reporting Procedure</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><br/></li>
            <li>Unauthorized absence (AWOL).</li>
            <li>Accidental injury (falls, cuts) requiring first aid or medical attention.</li>
            <li>Medical emergencies.</li>
            <li>Medication errors (e.g., incorrect dosage).</li>
            <li>Property damage or theft.</li>
            <li>Disclosure of safe-guarding concerns (e.g., abuse).</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>2. The 3-Step Reporting Procedure</b></p>
        <p><b>Step 1: Immediate Action (First 15 Minutes)</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Secure Safety:</b> Ensure the immediate safety and stabilization of all individuals involved.</li>
            <li><b>First Aid/Medical:</b> Administer immediate first aid if necessary. Call emergency services (911/112) for life-threatening situations.</li>
            <li><b>Stabilize Scene:</b> Isolate the area if needed to maintain safety.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>Step 2: Notification (First Hour)</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Internal Notification:</b> Immediately notify the Shift Supervisor or on-call Care Manager.</li>
            <li><b>Family/Guardian/Social Worker:</b> The Care Manager will coordinate notification of external parties (guardian, social worker, family) if the resident's safety or medical status is significantly affected.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>Step 3: Documentation (Before Shift End)</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Access the Form:</b> Retrieve a <i>blank Incident Report Form</i> (Link: [Insert link to printable/digital form in the Resource Center Folder 6]).</li>
            <li><b>Completion:</b> Complete the form <i>before the end of the current shift</i>.</li>
            <li><b>Content:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>State the <b>facts only</b>: What was observed, who was involved, where, and when.</li>
                    <li>Do <b>not</b> include opinions, blame, assumptions, or judgments.</li>
                    <li>Describe immediate actions taken and notifications made.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>3. Post-Incident Review</b><br/>
        All submitted incident reports will be reviewed by senior leadership within 72 hours to identify patterns, evaluate SOP compliance, and determine necessary follow-up support or interventions.</p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Medical Administration</h2>
        <p><b>Purpose:</b> This procedure establishes a standardized, safe, and compliant method for the storage, handling, and administration of medication, minimizing error and prioritizing resident safety.</p>
        <p><b>1. Mandatory Principles</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Staff Authorization:</b        
        > Only care workers who have received specific, documented medical administration training and authorization are permitted to handle or administer medication.</li>
            <li><b>The "Six Rights" of Administration:</b> Every dose <i>must</i> verify the:
                <ol>
                    <li><b>Right Resident</b> (Confirmed by photo ID/questioning).</li>
                    <li><b>Right Drug</b> (Matching label to order).</li>
                    <li><b>Right Dose</b> (Correct amount).</li>
                    <li><b>Right Route</b> (Method: oral, topical, etc.).</li>
                    <li><b>Right Time</b> (Scheduled slot).</li>
                    <li><b>Right Documentation</b> (Immediate sign-off).</li>
                </ol>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>2. Medication Storage &amp; Security</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Locked Storage:</b> All medication must be kept in a double-locked, access-controlled cabinet or refrigerator.</li>
            <li><b>Access:</b> Keys or access codes are only for authorized medical staff. No other individuals may access storage areas.</li>
            <li><b>Labeling:</b> All medication containers must be clearly labeled with the resident's full name, drug name, dosage, route, frequency, and expiration date.</li>
            <li><b>Storage Conditions:</b> Store medicines under appropriate temperature, light, and humidity conditions as specified by the manufacturer.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>3. Administration Procedure</b></p>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Preparation:</b> Wash hands and prepare a clean surface. Retrieve the correct medication and MAR (Medication Administration Record).</li>
            <li><b>Verify:</b> Check the medication label against the MAR using the "Six Rights."</li>
            <li><b>Resident Check:</b> Verify the resident's identity.</li>
            <li><b>Administration:</b> Observe the resident taking the medication. Stay with them until fully consumed.</li>
            <li><b>Documentation (Mandatory):</b> Immediately sign and date the MAR entry for that specific dose. <b>Do not pre-sign.</b> <b>Do not sign for others.</b></li>
        </ol>
        <p><b>4. Errors, Refusals, and Waste</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Errors:</b> In case of a medication error (e.g., wrong drug/dose), follow the <i>Incident Reporting Procedure SOP</i> (Article 3.2) immediately. Monitor the resident and notify medical leadership.</li>
            <li><b>Refusals:</b> If a resident refuses medication, encourage them gently, but do not force. Document the refusal on the MAR (e.g., circle and note "Refused") and notify the supervisor/physician.</li>
            <li><b>Waste:</b> Dispose of unused, expired, or contaminated medication according to the specific facility disposal SOP and regulatory guidelines.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>Confidentiality &amp; Data Protection (GDPR)</h2>
        <p><b>Policy Purpose:</b> This policy defines strict standards for handling personal and sensitive information in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and local data protection laws of [Insert e.g., Wallonia/Belgium]. Protection of resident and staff data is a mandatory condition of employment.</p>
        <p><b>1. Scope &amp; Definition of Data</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Resident Data (Sensitive):</b> Medical history, behavioral logs, educational records, case files, Life Goals Plans, photos.</li>
            <li><b>Staff Data (Personal):</b> Payroll info, contact details, HR records, background checks.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>2. Core Principle: "Need to Know" Basis</b><br/>
        Access to personal and sensitive data is granted only to staff members who <i>require</i> that information to perform their specific job functions effectively. Viewing records for curiosity, gossip, or unauthorized personal gain is a severe breach of policy.</p>
        <p><b>3. Mandatory Data Handling Procedures</b></p>
        <p><b>Physical (Paper) Records:</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Storage:</b> Securely locked in cabinets within access-controlled offices.</li>
            <li><b>Use:</b> Never leave files unattended on desks, in common areas, or viewable to unauthorized individuals.</li>
            <li><b>Transfer:</b> Files must remain on-site unless authorized in writing by the Data Protection Officer for specific, necessary travel.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>Digital Records:</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Access:</b> Accessible only via authorized, password-protected facility platforms (not personal accounts).</li>
            <li><b>Security:</b> Passwords must not be shared. Lock screens (Windows Key + L) when stepping away.</li>
            <li><b>Sharing:</b> Secure links within our internal platform are preferred. If emailing, data must be encrypted/password protected. Never share sensitive resident data via personal email or unsecured messaging apps.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>Handover Logs &amp; Shift Notes:</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Focus:</b> Must focus on professional observations relevant to care (Behavioral Logs, Handover Notes).</li>
            <li><b>Anonymity (if required):</b> When used outside direct care (e.g., training), all data must be fully anonymized.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>4. Data Breach &amp; Rights</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Reporting Breaches:</b> Any suspected data breach (lost files, unauthorized access, shared passwords) must be reported <i>immediately</i> to the facility Data Protection Officer (DPO) and follow the Incident SOP (Article 3.2). GDPR requirements necessitate reporting of major breaches within 72 hours.</li>
            <li><b>Resident Rights:</b> Residents (or their guardians) have rights under GDPR, including the right to access their data, correct errors, and in some cases, request deletion. All such requests must be formally routed to the administration for review.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
