<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <p>
            <strong>
                <span style="font-size: 36px;">The Grocery Shop</span>
            </strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            Setting up a Point of Sale (POS) system for a grocery store which is essential for efficiently managing various product categories, handling transactions, and providing excellent customer service. Grocery stores are businesses that
            carry a large selection of products like Food Grains, Oil &amp; Clarified Butter, Dry Fruits, Chocolates, Snacks &amp; Packaged Food with multiple variants etc… Here's a step-by-step guide to setting up a POS system for a grocery
            store or a supermarket:
        </p>
        <p>In the retail store, we set up the POS module for B2C customers and sales for B2B customers. They use the Sales, Purchase, Inventory, Accounting modules.</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc">
            <div class="o_knowledge_toc_content">
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Flow 1 : Purchase Flow.</a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Flow 2: Point of sale - Regular flow with Buy one get one free product</a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Flow 3: Point of sale - Customer Account </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Flow 4: Point of Sale - Ship Later &amp; Global discount @10% </a>
                <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Flow 5: Sale Flow – B2B Customer</a>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2><strong>Flow 1: Purchase Flow</strong></h2>
        <ul>
            <li>Create an RFQ for "Grocery outlet"</li>
            <li>Select a product (e.g toothpaste)</li>
            <li>Confirm the RFQ</li>
            <li>Validate the reception for all quantities at once.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2><strong>Flow 2: Point of sale - Regular flow with Buy one get one free product</strong></h2>
        <p>For the Small Products, orders &amp; payments are made at the shop itself, and the customer picks up the products directly.</p>
        <br />
        <p><strong>To do that, open the Point of Sale application:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create a POS order with the required product (i.e. ‘Daawat Traditional Basmati Rice)and (Colgate Maxfresh with cooling crystals Toothpaste — 600g – Pack of 4)</li>
            <li>Click on the “Reward” Button then after automatic Free product add “‘Toothbrush Ultrasoft[Pack of 4].</li>
            <li>Then pay the order.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2><strong>Flow 3: Point of sale - Customer Account</strong></h2>
        <p>
            The concept is simple from the POS screen itself, When a customer purchases a product on credit, it means they take the product without making an immediate payment. Instead, they owe a certain amount to the shop. The customer
            returns to the shop at a later date to pay the remaining amount they owe for the product, settling the debt.
        </p>
        <br />
        <p><strong>To do that, open the Point of Sale application:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create a POS order with the required product (i.e.Maggie Mega Pack” – 70g - Pack of 4, Sunfeast Dark Fantasy Choco Fills Cream – 600g - Pack of 4)</li>
            <li>Then click on Payment, we can add a “customer account” i.e put in some money as the credit balance.</li>
            <li>Validate your order.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2><strong>Flow 4: Point of Sale - Ship Later &amp; Global discount @10%</strong></h2>
        <p>For large or Bulk products, the order &amp; payment is done at the shop, but the delivery is sometimes scheduled later.</p>
        <br />
        <p><strong>To do that, open the Point of Sale application:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create a POS order with heavy products (i.e. Almonds(American), Cadbury Oreo Biscuit Vanilla Flavour Cream)</li>
            <li>​Give the Global Discount @ 10%</li>
            <li>Set the customer to define the shipping address</li>
            <li>As it's set an invoice and mark "Ship Later"</li>
            <li>Then pay the order</li>
        </ul>
        <h2><strong>Flow 5: Sale Flow – B2B Customer</strong></h2>
        <p>Customers can book the order, or ask for a quote, on the phone at the shop, but the customer picks up and pays for the products at the store when they are available.</p>
        <br />
        <p><strong>To do that, start with a Quotation order:</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create a quotation and send it by email</li>
            <li>Optionally: the customer might confirm the order, but it's not necessary</li>
            <li>When the customer goes to the store, from the POS Order, use the button "Quotation / Order" to load the related Sales order</li>
            <li>Settle the order from the POS screen to record the payment and give products to the customer.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>​<strong>Flow 6: Product with multiple barcode packaging</strong></h2>
        <p>If customers opt to disassemble packages within the shop, the packaging feature becomes essential. For instance, when selecting a Monster Energy drink bottles are in packs of 5 and 10 in the shelves:</p>
        <p><strong>To do that, open the Point of sale application:</strong></p>
        <ul style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            <li>Scanning the pack's barcode is necessary to determine the accurate price and decrease the inventory by six units.</li>
        </ul>
        <ul>
            <li>If a customer chooses a single bottle from the pack, the barcode of that bottle must be scanned instead.<br /></li>
        </ul>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Grocery Shop</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_4"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
