<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_34" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="name">Condominium</field>
        <field name="sequence">16</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">26.8</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_11"/>
        <field name="icon">🏢</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[
            <h1>Condominium</h1>
            <p>
                This industry is tailor-made for condominium businesses that aim to manage the co-ownership properties. Such a business is complex because it implies to manage all the aspects of the properties while&nbsp;fairly splitting the charges.
                Moreover, the business is legally regulated in lots of countries under different names: condo in US, co-ownership in Canada, joint domination in UK, property syndicate in France, syndic in Belgium, etc.
            </p>
            <p>Odoo empowers you to effortlessly and efficiently manage every aspect of the condominiums under your responsibility, ensuring homeowners satisfaction thanks to its suite of integrated applications.<br /></p>
            <div tabindex="-1" class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc" data-oe-protected="true">
                <div class="o_knowledge_toc_content">
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Condominium</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Business Flows</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Easily convert the homeowner associations 🖋️</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Never forget a task&nbsp;⚡</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Quickly set up a condominium&nbsp; 🚀</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="5" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Know the&nbsp;stakeholders&nbsp;🔎</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="6" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Provide the best customer service&nbsp;🆘</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="7" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Fairly split the costs&nbsp;⚖️</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="8" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Book&nbsp;the right numbers 🧾</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="9" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Schedule the meetings&nbsp;📅</a>
                    <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="10" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">Efficiently count the votes&nbsp;🧮</a>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
                    <p>
                        Click on the&nbsp;&nbsp;<a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="#">🎓Buttons</a>&nbsp; to get access to the related documentation<br />
                        <br />
                        Double click on the <font class="text-o-color-1">Purple Links</font> to be redirected in the corresponding&nbsp;Odoo screen
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h1>Business Flows</h1>
            <h2>Easily convert the homeowner associations 🖋️</h2>
            <p>
                As soon as the&nbsp;homeowner association reaches you to get a quote, quickly send them an overview of your services and fees by creating&nbsp;
                <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Quotations</span>&nbsp;in the Sales application where you can directly use the
                "Kick-Off Quote" quotation template.&nbsp;This will automatically fill the quote by adding the kick-off fees and also the price of all the extra services such as the recurring contribution, the hourly rate, etc. Don't forget to attach
                the terms &amp; conditions as well. Of course, the price of each service and the content of the
                <span class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link" data-oe-protected="true" tabindex="-1">Quotation Templates</span>&nbsp;can be adapted accordingly.
            </p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Sales</a></p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/sales/sales/send_quotations/quote_template.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Quotation Template</a><br /></p>
            <h2>Never forget a task&nbsp;⚡</h2>
            <p>
                Once&nbsp;the quotation is confirmed, it automatically creates
                <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Projects</span>&nbsp;including several tasks to properly start the collaboration.
                This is based on the&nbsp;<span class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link" data-oe-protected="true" tabindex="-1">Kick-Off Template</span>&nbsp;project:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>Contracts establishment<br /></li>
                <li>Condominium creation in Odoo (see&nbsp;<em>Quickly Set Up a Condominium&nbsp; 🚀 </em>section)</li>
                <li>Properties&nbsp;creation in Odoo (see&nbsp;<em>Know the&nbsp;stakeholders&nbsp;🔎</em> section)</li>
                <li>Helpdesk creation in Odoo (see&nbsp;<em>Provide the best customer service&nbsp;🆘</em> section)</li>
                <li>Accounting opening/handover<br /></li>
                <li>Audit</li>
                <li>Meters reading</li>
                <li>Act analysis</li>
                <li>Insurances analysis</li>
                <li>Kick-off meeting</li>
                <li>Call for working and reserve funds</li>
                <li>...</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Again, feel free to edit and/or create new tasks to never forget a step&nbsp;during the kick-off process.</p>
            <h2 class="null">Quickly set up a condominium&nbsp; 🚀</h2>
            <p>Once the quotation is confirmed, the condominium should be created in Odoo. Basically,&nbsp;a<strong>&nbsp;</strong>condominium is like a&nbsp;company that is funded by the owners and that has to pay for operating costs.</p>
            <p>
                From the Settings, create a new company in&nbsp;<span class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link" data-oe-protected="true" tabindex="-1">Companies</span>&nbsp;to manage
                the Once done, it will appear on the top right of all screens with the aim to quickly switch between your company and the different condominiums:
            </p>
            <p>
                <span style="width: 40px;" class="oe-tabs"> </span>​<img style="width: 50%;" src="/web/image/809-55bc4303/image.png?access_token=a81739d9-09ae-4ab9-ae66-fa7b6a7efd46" data-file-name="image.png" class="img-fluid img-thumbnail" /><br />
            </p>
            <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/general/users/companies.html">🎓 Companies</a><br /></p>
            <h2>Know the&nbsp;stakeholders&nbsp;🔎</h2>
            <p>
                In&nbsp;the <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Contacts</span>&nbsp;application, easily create an address book
                containing all the owners, tenants, suppliers, etc.&nbsp;It is useful to fill the following information:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>The contact name.</li>
                <li>The postal address.</li>
                <li>The phone numbers.</li>
                <li>The email address.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                Once done, create all the <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Properties</span>&nbsp;belonging to the Each
                property&nbsp;corresponds to an apartment, a studio, a flat, a house, etc. that is characterized by:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>A name to identify the property, for example the post box or the identification code.</li>
                <li>The condominium to which the property&nbsp;belongs.</li>
                <li>The owner of the property.</li>
                <li>The tenant.</li>
                <li>
                    The area from which the ownership percentage&nbsp;will be computed. This defines the proportion of the property&nbsp;in the condominium and it will be useful to split the costs (see&nbsp;
                    <em>Fairly split the costs&nbsp;⚖️</em> section) and to weight the votes of the owners when decisions must be taken during the general meetings.
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>In the contact form, the information about the related properties&nbsp; are summarized.</p>
            <h2>Provide the best customer service&nbsp;🆘</h2>
            <p>
                Since the requests from the&nbsp;homeowner association could come from several owners, it would be easier to centralize them all.&nbsp;Create&nbsp;
                <span class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link" data-oe-protected="true" tabindex="-1">Helpdesk Teams</span>&nbsp;for each condominium under your responsibility. Don't
                forget to define an email alias and share it with the owners. Thereby, they will easily send requests that will be centralized in a single point as tickets.&nbsp;This eases the follow-up and the invoicing in case the time spent is not
                covered by the service fees.
            </p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/17.0/applications/services/helpdesk/overview/getting_started.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Helpdesk</a><br /></p>
            <h2>Fairly split the costs&nbsp;⚖️</h2>
            <p>Each owner has to pay recurring fees:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>The working fund that is used to pay the common charges&nbsp;such as monthly expenses (water, electricity, gas, etc.), insurances, maintenance, repairs, cleaning of common areas, etc.&nbsp;</li>
                <li>The reserve fund that is a savings account used in case of exceptional expenses such as a severe&nbsp;repair, an investment in equipment, etc.</li>
                <li>The&nbsp;services provided by the condominium management company.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>On the one hand, the funds requests are sent by&nbsp;the condominium to the owners. On the other hand, the service fees can be invoiced by "My Condominium Management" to the owners. Here are the steps to follow:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Select the right company from which the fees will be invoiced (see&nbsp;<em>Quickly set up a condominium&nbsp; 🚀</em> section to see how to switch the company).</li>
                <li>In the Sales application, create a quotation and set the condominium as customer.</li>
                <li>In case of recurring fees:</li>
                <li class="oe-nested">
                    <ol>
                        <li>Define a recurring plan, monthly or yearly.</li>
                        <li>Set the recurring plan start date.</li>
                        <li>Make sure that the products added are recurring.</li>
                    </ol>
                </li>
                <li>Add the corresponding product(s): "Working Fund", "Reserve Fund",&nbsp;"Service Fees", etc.</li>
                <li>Set the right (recurring) price.</li>
                <li>Click on "Split per Property" button: this will cancel the current quotation and will recreate as many quotations as properties&nbsp;in the condominium for which the costs&nbsp;are shared.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
                <li>Click on the "Sales Orders" buttons to access all the generated quotations.</li>
                <li>Check if everything is correct. If yes, select all the quotations and, under the "Actions" button, click on "Confirm".</li>
                <li>In case of recurring fees, the invoices will be automatically generated by Odoo at the right date. If not, you can manually post them in mass. Then just send them using your preferred way!</li>
            </ol>
            <p>
                For example, to collect the cotisations, the selected company must be the condominium and the customer must be the condominium too. If you want to invoice your services, the selected company must be yours and the customer must be the
                condominium&nbsp;to be invoiced.
            </p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/sales/subscriptions.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Subscription</a><br /></p>
            <h2>Book&nbsp;the right numbers 🧾</h2>
            <p>A condominium works like a company. It gets revenues from the owners. These are collected in two bank accounts that can be directly integrated with the bank:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Working Fund: to collect all the money that will be used to pay the recurring&nbsp;fees.</li>
                <li>Reserve Fund: to collect all the money that will be used in case of exceptional expense.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>These will be used to pay the Vendor Bills that can be uploaded and automatically booked thanks to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/app/invoice-automation">Artificial Intelligence</a>.</p>
            <p>By the end of the period, easily generate the legal reporting such as Balance Sheet and Profit &amp; Loss for each</p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/finance/accounting.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Accounting</a><br /></p>
            <h2 class="null">Schedule the meetings&nbsp;📅</h2>
            <p>
                Every year, a general meeting is scheduled to talk about the financial statements, to take important decisions and so on. This event can easily be scheduled in the Calendar app by creating&nbsp;
                <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Meetings</span>. To invite all the owners of a condominium, use the "Search More"
                on "Attendees" and type the name of the Condominium in... "Condominiums":
            </p>
            <p><span style="width: 40px;" class="oe-tabs"> </span>​<img src="/web/image/876-e73e7024/image.png?access_token=910cf09a-09f3-4ab9-badb-7f8fb51ee37e" data-file-name="image.png" class="img-fluid" /><br /></p>
            <h2>Efficiently count the votes&nbsp;🧮</h2>
            <p>
                During the general meetings, counting the votes depending on the ownership percentage&nbsp;could be painful. From the&nbsp;
                <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Properties</span>&nbsp;screen, select all the properties&nbsp;of the corresponding
                condominium and insert them in a spreadsheet:
            </p>
            <p><img src="/web/image/877-7f5d381c/image.png?access_token=6f50585a-94f7-4e10-8378-641ff17fcdc8" data-file-name="image.png" class="img-fluid" /></p>
            <p>
                Use the power of formulas to quickly count the votes. See an example of spreadsheet in&nbsp;
                <span tabindex="-1" data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_view_link text-o-color-1 o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_view_link">Documents</span>.&nbsp;
            </p>
            <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/master/applications/finance/spreadsheet.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Spreadsheet</a></p>
            ]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
