<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 data-oe-version="1.2">Property Owner Association</h1>
        <p>
            Managing property owner associations involves multiple stakeholders, recurring tasks, and detailed records. Odoo empowers associations by streamlining processes—from handling new prospects to managing shared expenses—through a fully
            integrated suite of applications. Whether you're organizing general meetings, tracking owner history, or handling complex expense distributions, Odoo provides the tools to stay efficient and transparent.
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Basics</h1>
        <hr />
        <h2>Apps Overview</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>CRM:</strong> Track and manage incoming leads and communications with potential new condominiums.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sales:</strong> Send quotations, confirm orders, and invoice shared expenses to owners.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Contacts:</strong> Manage contacts turning prospects into condominiums, as well as owners, tenants and suppliers.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Condominium:</strong> Define buildings, properties, owner and tenant histories, meter readings and distribution keys.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting:</strong> Manage shared expenses, distribute costs by owner, and maintain owner-specific balance sheets.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Calendar:</strong> Schedule and organize association meetings, collecting votes during general assemblies and share the report.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Easily convert the condominiums 🖋️</h2>
        <p>
            As soon as a condominium reaches out to you to get a quote, quickly send them an overview of your services and fees by creating Quotations in the <strong>Sales App</strong> where you can directly use the "Kick-Off Quote"
            quotation template. This will automatically fill the quote by adding the kick-off fees and also the price of all the extra services such as the recurring contribution, the hourly rate, etc. Don't forget to attach the terms &amp;
            conditions as well. Of course, the price of each service and the content of the Quotation Templates can be adapted accordingly.
        </p>
        <p>When the quote is confirmed for a new condominium, you can convert the prospect contact into a condominium in a click from the contact form, in the <strong>Contact App</strong>. </p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html">🎓 Sales</a></p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales/send_quotations/quote_template.html">🎓 Quotation Template</a></p>
        <h2><br /></h2>
        <h2>Never forget a task 📑</h2>
        <p>Once the quotation is confirmed, it automatically creates Projects including several tasks to properly start the collaboration. This is based on the Kick-Off Template Template project:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Contracts establishment<br /></li>
            <li>Condominium creation in Odoo (see <em>Quickly Set Up a Condominium 🚀 </em>section)</li>
            <li>Properties creation in Odoo (see <em>Know the stakeholders 🔎</em> section)</li>
            <li>Accounting opening/handover<br /></li>
            <li>Audit</li>
            <li>Meters reading</li>
            <li>Act analysis</li>
            <li>Insurances analysis</li>
            <li>Kick-off meeting</li>
            <li>Call for working and reserve funds</li>
            <li>...</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Again, feel free to edit and/or create new tasks to never forget a step during the kick-off process.</p>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Project</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2 class="null">Set up a condominium 🚀</h2>
        <p>Once the quotation is confirmed, the condominium should be created in Odoo. Basically, a<strong> </strong>condominium is like a company that is funded by the owners and that has to pay for operating costs.</p>
        <p>
            From the Settings, create a new company in <font style="font-weight: bolder;" class="text-o-color-1">Companies</font>. Once done, it will appear on the top right of all screens with the aim to quickly switch between your company and the
            different condominiums.
        </p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            Once done, it is time to create the composition of the condominium by selecting the right one on the top right of the screen. 
        </p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><br /></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            Open the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Condominium</font></strong> App where you can:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>See the information of the condominium and fill the vendors to build an address book.</li>
            <li>Create the buildings that compounds the</li>
            <li>Create the properties that compounds the buildings: apartment, studio, flat, penthouse, garage, etc.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Each property is characterized by:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>A name to identify the property, for example the post box or the identification code.</li>
            <li>The building to which the property belongs.</li>
            <li>The type to easily classify it.</li>
            <li>The owner history.</li>
            <li>The tenant history if relevant.</li>
            <li>Some tags to add extra visual information.</li>
            <li>The parent property, for example to indicate that a garage is linked with an apartment.</li>
            <li>The floor.</li>
            <li>
                The area.
            </li>
            <li>The meter readings history, leveraged to split bills based on consumption.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Finally, you can also define the distribution keys. The goal is to assign a ratio for each property that will be used for splitting the fees per owner and for distributing the costs:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Distribution keys based on shares can be populated with all properties from the condominium and the ratios computed based on properties' surface. You can still edit the ratios as you need and includes only a sub selection of the
                properties when relevant.
            </li>
            <li>Distribution keys based on meter readings only refer to a meter. When used to split costs, the recorded meter readings for the corresponding period will be used. </li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    A distribution key is needed for several actions.<br />
                    Defining a distribution key is efficient by populating defined properties in a click.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/general/users/companies.html">🎓 Companies</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Fairly split the costs ⚖️</h2>
        <p>Each owner has to pay recurring fees:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>The working fund that is used to pay the common charges such as monthly expenses (water, electricity, gas, etc.), insurances, maintenance, repairs, cleaning of common areas, etc.</li>
            <li>The reserve fund that is a savings account used in case of exceptional expenses such as a severe repair, an investment in equipment, etc.</li>
            <li>The services provided by the condominium management company.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>On the one hand, the funds requests are sent by the condominium to the owners. On the other hand, the service fees can be invoiced by "My Condominium Management" to the owners. </p>
        <h5>Requesting funds</h5>
        <p>Here are the steps to follow:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Select the right company from which the fees will be invoiced (see <em>Set up a condominium 🚀</em> section to see how to switch the company).</li>
            <li>In the <strong>Sales App</strong>, create a quotation and set the condominium as customer.</li>
            <li>Set the right distribution key.</li>
            <li>In case of recurring fees:</li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>Define a recurring plan, monthly or yearly.</li>
                    <li>Set the recurring plan start date.</li>
                    <li>Make sure that the products added are recurring.</li>
                </ol>
            </li>
            <li>Add the corresponding product(s): "Working Fund", "Reserve Fund", "Service Fees", etc.</li>
            <li>Set the right (recurring) price.</li>
            <li>
                Click on "Split by Property" button: this will cancel the current quotation and will create as many quotations as there are ongoing owners in the condominium for which the costs are shared, with a line by property they
                own.
            </li>
            <li>Click on the "Sales Orders" buttons to access all the generated quotations.</li>
            <li>Check if everything is correct. If yes, select all the quotations and, under the "Actions" button, click on "Confirm".</li>
            <li>In case of recurring fees, the invoices will be automatically generated by Odoo at the right date. If not, you can manually post them in mass. Then just send them using your preferred way!</li>
        </ol>
        <p>
            For example, to collect the cotisations, the selected company must be the condominium and the customer must be the condominium too. If you want to invoice your services, the selected company must be yours and the customer must be the
            condominium to be invoiced.
        </p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/subscriptions.html">🎓 Subscription</a><br /></p>
        <h5>Distributing costs</h5>
        <p>Record invoices from from supplier from <strong>Accounting App</strong>, by assigning supplier and listing products.</p>
        <p>Then, on a regular basis or at invoice confirmation, distribute the costs of each expenses:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the<strong> Condominium App</strong> and reach the Distributions from the Purchase menu.</li>
            <li>Assign the appropriate distribution key and if relevant the distribution period..</li>
        </ol>
        <p>The cost distribution inputs are available on each invoice in the distribution tab.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Expenses regarding a single owner can be assigned setting the analytic distribution of the corresponding invoice lines to the corresponding account, from the invoice form.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Examples</p>
        <ul>
            <li>To distribute costs related to an annual services, such as condominium insurance fees, the distribution based on shares over a period is relevant to expense each owner in proportion of their ownership and share.</li>
            <li>To distribute costs which only impact current owners, a distribution key based on shares without period inputs is required.</li>
            <li>
                Finally, for condominiums organised with a general meter for the condominium to be expenses and then with meters for each owners to split the expenses, the distribution key based on meter is relevant and requires period inputs and
                associated meter readings for each property to be representative.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Distribution keys based on meter reading require the period start and end inputs.<br />
                    When distributing costs, for each property, the closest meter readings to period boundaries are used to compute the consumption over the period, and in case of owner change, the consumption by owner is captured if a meter
                    reading is near the owner change date.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Distribution keys based on shares directly use the ratios.<br />
                    Without period inputs, the distribution is handled between the current owners.<br />
                    With period inputs, the distribution is computed between owners over the corresponding period, in proportion to the ownership.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Book the right numbers 🧮</h2>
        <p>A condominium works like a company. It gets revenues from the owners. These are collected in two bank accounts that can be directly integrated with the bank:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Working Fund: to collect all the money that will be used to pay the recurring fees.</li>
            <li>Reserve Fund: to collect all the money that will be used in case of exceptional expense.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            These will be used to pay the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Vendor Bills</font></strong> that can be uploaded and automatically filled thanks to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/app/invoice-automation">Artificial Intelligence</a>.
            As soon as a bill is booked, you can use the button "Distribute Cost" to automatically reflect the cost per property according to the distribution key.
        </p>
        <p>By the end of the period, easily generate the legal reporting such as Balance Sheet and Profit &amp; Loss for each</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>The chart of account and relationships with products and product categories is not setup in this module.</p>
                <p>We recommend your accountants to setup the appropriate chart of account based on your localization to generate the appropriate balance sheet and other needed accounting documents through Odoo.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">🎓 Accounting</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Provide access to the owners 🔑</h2>
        <p>In many cases, direct access to the condominium accounting shall be provided to some owners. This is the case for example when some are given review duties.</p>
        <p>To setup such access, you shall create users for such owners and restrict rights to the level which suite your needs so that they can access in read only most likely.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Be aware that additional users lead to additional Odoo subscription costs. We therefore recommend you :</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>To maintain the number of users to the minimum needed, creating and deleting them when relevant.</li>
                    <li>To account for this additional cost in your pricing. </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/general/users/access_rights.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Access Rights</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2 class="null">Organize and lead general meetings 📅</h2>
        <p>
            Every year, a general meeting is scheduled to talk about the financial statements, to take important decisions and so on. This event can easily be scheduled in the Calendar app by creating
            <font style="font-weight: bolder;" class="text-o-color-1">Meetings</font>. To invite all the owners of a condominium, use the "Search More" on "Attendees" and type the name of the condominium in... "Condominiums" and set the condominium
            field.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Plan you general meeting agenda with motions to vote in the Motions tab.</li>
            <li>Send the meeting agenda upfront to all expected attendees</li>
            <li>Select the relevant distribution key to account for owner ratios.</li>
            <li>Create the relevant motions in advance to efficiently drive the meeting.</li>
            <li>For each motion, assign the relevant motion criteria, take notes while discussion goes on and record the owners votes.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>At the end of the meeting, you can preview the meeting report and send it to the owners.</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can find all past meeting for a condominium from the Condominium App, by the Owners menu.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Connect your calendar to your Odoo database to never miss any meeting!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><a class="btn btn-outline-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar.html">🎓 Calendar</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Provide the best customer service 🆘</h2>
        <p>
            In their day to day, the owners and the tenants can face some issues. In order to collect and centralize them, use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Helpdesk</font></strong> application. Thereby, each member can send an email
            that will be caught in the right helpdesk team. This eases the follow-up and the invoicing in case the time spent is not covered by the service fees.
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/helpdesk/overview/getting_started.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Helpdesk</a></p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <h2>Tips for Success</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Use quotation templates</strong> in the Sales app to standardize quotes and reduce manual errors.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Keep contact data up-to-date</strong> to ensure seamless communication during meetings, billing and accounting.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Automate recurring tasks</strong>, like meter reading imports or expense allocation.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Leverage tags and filters</strong> in Contacts and CRM to segment your audience (owners, tenants, suppliers, condominiums...).</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Define condominium your charts of account template</strong> to save time setting up accounting aspects. Don't hesitate to contact us if needed!</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <hr />
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <p>Odoo offers additional possibilities to enhance your business:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Sign</strong> <strong>App: </strong>Send digital property reservation contracts.</li>
            <li><strong>Documents App: </strong>Request and share documents.</li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website Builder:</strong> Build a professional website with lead capture forms and member areas.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>VoIP Integration:</strong> Organize online meetings directly from Odoo with integrated call capabilities.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Explore <strong>automations</strong>, <strong>community portals</strong>, and <strong>custom dashboards</strong> tailored to your needs.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>These features can be added to your current subscription. Feel free to explore and expand your Odoo experience!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Final word</h1>
        <p>
            You might have tested this package with or without demo data.<br />
            In any case, you may have written records in journals which are not deletable and which might be an issue for your traceability.
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p><strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then to create a new one for your own usage.</strong></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="oe-hint"><br /></div>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Property Owner Association</field>
        <field name="sequence">16</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">26.8</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_11"/>
        <field name="icon">🏢</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
