<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0">
            <span class="display-4-fs"><strong>Odoo for Takeaway Restaurants</strong></span>
        </h1>
        <p>
            Running a takeaway restaurant means juggling a fast-paced mix of online orders, in-store customers, kitchen prep, and supplier management. Odoo empowers takeaway businesses with a fully integrated suite of applications - covering
            everything from your menu to your deliveries - so you can focus on flavor, not friction.
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><span class="h1-fs">Basics</span></h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Website 🌐</strong>: Build up your digital presence on the web using our convenient website &amp; SEO tools, as well as an online menu that works without friction.</li>
            <li><strong>Point of Sale 📒 </strong>: Register in-store orders, assign orders to tables, connect to the kitchen display, collect payments and more</li>
            <li><strong>Kitchen display 🧑‍🍳 </strong>: All orders, online and offline, appear on the kitchen display. Chefs can easily move orders from one readiness status to the next by simply tapping the order.</li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Purchase &amp; Inventory 📦 </strong>: Purchase &amp; receive supplier deliveries, track ingredient stocks.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><br /></h3>
        <h3>From Menu to Door, in a few clicks 🌐</h3>
        <p>Customers browse your menu on your Odoo website, selecting dishes and extras (like toppings, or side dishes). During checkout, they can choose delivery or pickup. A delivery fee can be applied before validating the order.</p>
        <p><strong>Odoo ensures every order is registered, traceable, and ready to prepare or deliver without delay.</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create &amp; manage your products in Odoo - from single dishes, to combo meals, and more.</li>
            <li>Customers order through your online menu, choose pickup times, delivery address, and specify special requests if applicable.</li>
            <li>Orders arrive in your kitchen display, and are easily trackable, updateable, in a single tap</li>
            <li>Once your order is ready to be delivered, it gets out of the way, and you're ready for the next order.</li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Apps &amp; features</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website </strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Design a rich, mobile-friendly website for your customers.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Give access to your interactive menu for easy ordering</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-fill-primary">Website documentation</a><br />
            <br />
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Point of Sale</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create dishes, sides, drinks, and <strong>combo products</strong><br /></p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Add <strong>product variants</strong> for toppings, size, and special requests</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Let customers choose between pickup and delivery options</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-fill-primary">Point of Sale documentation</a><br />
            <br />
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Kitchen display</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Your kitchen has an easy overview of what's going on at all times</p></li>
                    <li><p>The easy to use interface allows you to know what's going on in a glance, and update orders in a tap.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3>From Kitchen to Table, in a few minutes 🍽️</h3>
        <p><strong>Take orders, manage tables, and keep the kitchen running smoothly.</strong></p>
        <p>
            The Point of Sale app allows you to manage multiple order sources, including in-restaurant orders. All your products are ready from the get go, and can be added to a table in just a few taps. Create customized floor plans, add
            discounts, and more if needed.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Assign orders to tables in just a tap</li>
            <li>Split the bill, add discounts, or apply special promotions on the go</li>
            <li>Complicated customer requests? No problem - serve any item in any order, take notes, and more.</li>
            <li>Follow-up on orders in the kitchen display, never get lost in your to-do's.</li>
        </ul>
        <h4>Apps &amp; features</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Point of Sale</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create dishes, sides, drinks, and <strong>combo products</strong><br /></p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Add <strong>product variants</strong> for toppings, size, and special requests</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create a beautiful <strong>floor plan, add tables &amp; seats</strong></p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Assign orders to tables, follow-up on customer requests, and always deliver on time.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-fill-primary">Point of Sale documentation</a><br />
            <br />
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Kitchen display</strong></p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Your kitchen has an easy overview of what's going on at all times</p></li>
                    <li><p>The easy to use interface allows you to know what's going on in a glance, and update orders in a tap.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Need to manage many simultaneous customers? No problem, configure your appointment app to manage table bookings in just a few clicks.</p>
                <p>You can then get an overview of your bookings, including preferences, allergies, and more with appointment questions.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Purchasing &amp; Stock Management 📦</h3>
        <p><strong>Keep your pantry stocked and your costs under control.</strong></p>
        <p>
            Behind every great restaurant is great inventory control. With Odoo, you can manage your ingredient stocks, track vendor deliveries, and automate reordering. When supplies run low, the <strong>Purchase</strong> app can trigger requests
            to your vendors, which get received into the <strong>Inventory</strong> app and validated upon delivery.
        </p>
        <p>This means you avoid ingredient shortages and never over-order.</p>
        <h4>Key Apps Involved</h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Purchase</strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create one-off or recurring <strong>RFQs</strong> to vendors</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Automate purchases when stock drops below threshold</p></li>
                    <li><p>Link items to cost structures for margin control</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Inventory</strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Receive and validate deliveries</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Track stock levels of <strong>ingredients and packaging</strong></p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Sync with <strong>Sales</strong> and <strong>PoS</strong> to update availability</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Run inventory adjustments and see real-time data</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <hr />
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    <strong><span class="h2-fs">Tips for Success</span></strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Start small, iterate.</strong> Configure your website and products first, then consider discounts and promotions.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Monitor your <strong>top-selling products</strong> to refine purchasing and promotions</p>
                    </li>

                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Visit our E-Learning platform </strong>on <strong><a href="http://Odoo.com/slides">Odoo.com/slides</a></strong>
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Experiment ! </strong>Did you know you can create a copy of your database to try things out ? Simply go to <a href="http://Odoo.com">Odoo.com</a>, go to My Databases, then click the <strong>gear icon </strong>to
                            duplicate your database.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Your restaurant's growth can be fueled with more Odoo apps and integrations:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>WhatsApp Integration</strong>: Let customers message you for updates, feedback, or special requests</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Loyalty Programs in the Point of Sale</strong>: Reward repeat customers with discounts, points, or free items</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting</strong>: Handle daily revenue tracking, taxes, and end-of-month reports</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Marketing</strong>: Send newsletters or discount codes to customers who've opted in<br />
                    <br />
                </p>
            </li>
            <p>Hungry for more? Let’s tailor your system to fit your kitchen’s rhythm. 🔥</p>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Takeaway Restaurants</field>
        <field name="icon">🍕</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
