<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1 data-oe-version="2.0">
        <span style="font-size: 45px;"><strong>Odoo for Event Management</strong></span><br />
    </h1>
    <p>Welcome to the <strong>Odoo Event Management</strong> package!</p>
    <p>
        This suite of applications is designed specifically for businesses in the events industry; whether you're organizing corporate retreats, outdoor team-buildings, workshops &amp; seminars or sports challenges. Odoo brings together everything
        you need to manage your business in one place: from receiving client requests and sending attractive quotations, to scheduling staff, handling logistics, and invoicing clients.
    </p>
    <p>
        By using this solution, you’ll gain access to essential tools like CRM, Sales, Projects, Rentals, Planning, and more. These apps work seamlessly together to streamline your operations, save time, and improve coordination across your
        entire team.
    </p>
    <p>Focus on delivering unforgettable events while Odoo takes care of the behind-the-scenes tasks.🎤</p>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
    <h2>
        <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
    </h2>
    <hr />
    <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>Capture leads directly from your <strong>website</strong> and track them in <strong>CRM</strong>, where you can follow up, plan meetings, and qualify opportunities.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Send attractive proposals and service offers using <strong>Sales</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Organize your network of venues, suppliers, and partners with detailed profiles in <strong>Contacts</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Turn confirmed bookings into structured event plans with <strong>Project.</strong></p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Set up and manage event registrations, tickets, and attendee lists using the <strong>Events</strong> app</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Manage logistics and equipment rentals smoothly with <strong>Rental</strong> and <strong>Inventory</strong>, ensuring item availability.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Ensure all event equipment stays in top condition by scheduling repairs and maintenance using the <strong>Maintenance app</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Use <strong>Planning</strong> to assign staff for each event and publish new job offers through <strong>Recruitment</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Keep your team aligned with shared calendars using <strong>Calendar</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Create and send invoices quickly from <strong>Invoicing.</strong></p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Collect digital signatures on quotes or agreements with <strong>Sign</strong> for faster client approval.</p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
            <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage your entire business in it.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h2>
        <span class="display-4-fs">
            <strong>
                <font class="text-800"><span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span></font>
            </strong>
        </span>
    </h2>
    <hr />
    <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
    <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
    <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
        <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
            <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Event Management package and check the related box.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Organize your contacts database</h3>
    <hr/>
    <p>Create a centralized, searchable database of your vendors, venues, and event partners.</p>
    <ul>
        <li><p>Open the <strong>Contact</strong> app:</p></li>
        <li class="oe-nested">
            <ul>
                <li><p>Add all business contacts: food trucks, venues, entertainers, caterers.</p></li>
                <li><p>Enter generic info: emails, phone number, specific point of contact for each business, address...</p></li>
                <li><p>Take detailed notes on each contact, including their price ranges and any other important info to remember.</p></li>
                <li><p>Log internal reviews or feedback for future events to help evaluate vendor or venue performance, in the chatter of the corresponding contact via the "Log notes" button.</p></li>
                <li><p>Use <strong>tags</strong> to organize your contact database efficiently (e.g., Catering, Venue, Photographer).</p></li>
                <li><p>Add specific tags like <strong>“Catering Free: YES”</strong> if the venue allows you to choose your own catering service, or <strong>“NO”</strong> if you must use the venue’s catering.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Link <strong>Knowledge</strong> articles or notes with practical info (e.g., parking capacity).</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Save a list of practical info, such as parking details, seating capacity, or available outdoor space, in the Knowledge app’s clipboard.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Attach this information directly to the relevant contact’s notes and complete all essential information to have a comprehensive overview of each venue when planning events.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
    <h3>Manage your business opportunities</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Convert incoming requests into event opportunities.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>Create a form on your <strong>Website</strong> allowing clients to request a quotation for their event (e.g., activity type, participants, ideal period and duration, budget,...).</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>When submitted, the form generates a new opportunity in the <strong>CRM</strong> module.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>In <strong>CRM</strong>:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Plan activities like a discovery call, task to check venue availability, or meeting.</p></li>
                <li><p>Assign a priority level to your opportunity and responsible employee.</p></li>
                <li><p>Use the chatter to communicate and keep track of updates.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li><p>Ask your contacts that could fit the needs of your opportunity to make sure that logistics could be available for the time request, the place and the food.</p></li>
        <li class="oe-nested"><br /></li>
        <li class="oe-nested">--> Once the event feasibility is confirmed, create a detailed <strong>Quotation</strong>.</li>
    </ul>
    <h3>Create quotations</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Send clear, detailed offers that reflect agreed services, supplier availability, and timing.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>From the CRM opportunity, generate a <strong>Sales</strong> quotation.</p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>If you offer logistics rental services, create a "new rental quotation", instead of a "new quotation", from the CRM opportunity and specify the rental period.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <ul>
        <li>Add products and services based on the request (e.g., venue rental, photographer service, catering,...).</li>
        <li>
            <p>Use a <strong>Quotation Template</strong> (e.g., "Outdoor Team Building") to save time.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>You can also include <strong>Terms and Conditions</strong> on your quotation based on your company’s policies to clearly communicate rules and protect your business.</p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🎬</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>Want to create an attractive quotation? Watch the “Outstanding Quotations” to help you building nice quotation to make your offer even more attractive<br /></p>
            <p>➡️ <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N4zw-2t6spk">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N4zw-2t6spk</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Organize event management into projects</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Structure each event with tasks, stages, deadlines, files, and responsibilities after a quotation is confirmed.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>Once the quotation is confirmed, a templated project with predefined tasks for that event will be automatically created.</li>
        <li>Open the <strong>Project </strong>via the button at the top of the quotation:</li>
        <li class="oe-nested">
            <ul>
                <li><p>Manage deadlines, assignees, notes, subtasks, and more for each task.</p></li>
                <li><p>Customize project and tasks stages to align with your team’s workflow and processes.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>A <strong>document</strong> folder is also created for the project, allowing you to store all event-related files, such as a ZIP of event photos for example.</li>
        <li>
            You can easily access these documents through a button that can be added directly to your project interface.
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>If you want to track project profitability, use the same filter button as above to display a dashboard on your Project page. This gives you a clear view of costs and revenues to see how profitable each event is.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Invoice clients</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Ensure every billable item is invoiced and nothing gets missed.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>Confirm the quotation to generate an invoice automatically.</li>
        <li>Send the invoice directly to the client from Odoo.</li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>Using down payments for Event Booking:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>When generating an invoice from the quotation, you can request a <strong>down payment</strong>, either as a fixed amount or a percentage of the total (e.g., €1000 upfront to secure the venue and catering services).</p>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <p>
                        <strong>Final Payment:</strong> After the event is completed, invoice the client for the remaining balance, which can include additional services or time tracked (e.g., extra hours, added logistics, or last-minute
                        requests).
                    </p>
                </li>
            </ul>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Manage logistics &amp; rentals</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Coordinate stock, rentals, repairs, and availability for your event inventory</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>Go to the <strong>Inventory</strong> app.</p>
        </li>
        <li class="oe-nested">
            <ul>
                <li><p>Use the search bar or filters to check availability of items like tents, chairs, tables, lighting, and decorations.</p></li>
                <li><p>Review stock levels and locations (e.g., “Room 2 – Shelf 3”) to know where items are stored.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Use <strong>Rental</strong> to:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Create a new rental order.</p></li>
                <li><p>Add the required items from your inventory (e.g., 100 folding chairs, 2 large tents, 10 round tables).</p></li>
                <li>
                    <p>Define the <strong>Rental Period</strong> by setting the <strong>pickup/delivery date</strong> and the <strong>return date</strong>.</p>
                </li>
                <li><p>Assign the rental to the corresponding event/project to keep things traceable.</p></li>
                <li><p>Validate the rental to lock in the reservation and prevent double-booking.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li><p>Before the event, inspect rented items:</p></li>
        <li class="oe-nested">
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>If any equipment requires attention (e.g., a torn tent or broken table), create a <strong>Maintenance Order</strong> via the <strong>Maintenance</strong> app.</p>
                </li>
                <li><p>Assign it to your technician, explain the problem, set the deadline, and track the status until the item is marked as ready.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>You can use <strong>Security Time</strong> to add extra hours before or after a rental. For example, if you need time to clean a tent before renting it again. Just set it in the <strong>"Rental"</strong> tab for each product.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <ul>
                <li>Before confirming an order, check the <strong>Rental app schedule</strong>.</li>
                <li>Remove the <strong>"Confirmed Orders"</strong> filter to see <strong>all pending and confirmed bookings</strong>.</li>
                <li>This helps you spot <strong>conflicts</strong> if multiple clients request the same item for overlapping times.</li>
            </ul>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>If you want to evaluate whether it's time to invest in an additional tent, go to the <strong>Reporting tab</strong> if the <strong>Rental app</strong>.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <p>Open the <strong>Pivot view</strong> and <strong>group by Product</strong>.</p>
                </li>
                <li><p>You’ll see how often each tent has been rented, the total revenue generated (based on the sales price), and compare it with the product’s cost.</p></li>
                <li><p>This helps you assess if the tent has already paid for itself and whether it’s worth purchasing another one.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <div>Use <strong>sub-locations</strong> like Room 1/ Shelf A to show exactly where items are stored in the warehouse.</div>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Manage purchases and supplier orders</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Request quotes, compare prices, and manage supplier orders efficiently.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>Create a <strong>Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> and add alternative products or vendors to compare prices and options.</p>
        </li>
        <li><p>When you choose the best quote, Odoo cancels the other quotes automatically.</p></li>
        <li>
            <p>Confirm the RFQ to make a <strong>Purchase Order (PO)</strong> you can track and invoice.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Add a <strong>delivery address</strong> like the event venue if the supplier ships there.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>Use <strong>Purchase Agreements</strong> to set fixed prices and terms with suppliers for regular items like chairs or lighting kits. This makes ordering faster and easier.</p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>You can add a <strong>warnings</strong> for your vendors to remind your team of important constraints. For example, “Vendor requires 2 weeks’ notice for large orders” helps ensure timely planning and smooth deliveries.</p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h3>Manage purchases and supplier orders</h3>
    <hr/>
    <p>Request quotes, compare prices, and manage supplier orders efficiently.</p>
    <ul>
        <li><p>Create a <strong>Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> and add alternative products or vendors to compare prices and options.</p></li>
        <li><p>When you choose the best quote, Odoo cancels the other quotes automatically.</p></li>
        <li><p>Confirm the RFQ to make a <strong>Purchase Order (PO)</strong> you can track and invoice.</p></li>
        <li><p>Add a <strong>delivery address</strong> like the event venue if the supplier ships there.</p></li>
        <li><p>Use <strong>Purchase Agreements</strong> to set fixed prices and terms with suppliers for regular items like chairs or lighting kits. This makes ordering faster and easier.</p></li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3"><p>You can add a <strong>warnings</strong> for your vendors to remind your team of important constraints. For example, “Vendor requires 2 weeks’ notice for large orders” helps ensure timely planning and smooth deliveries.</p></div>
    </div>
    <h3>Manage your agenda with the calendar app</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Stay organized by tracking all meetings, deadlines, reminders, and internal tasks using the Calendar app.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>Open the <strong>Calendar app</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                Schedule client meetings, vendor calls, deadlines, or event reminders by clicking on an empty time slot.<br />
                Example: “Set up tent for TechCorp team building in Namur.”
            </p>
        </li>
        <li><p>Check team members’ availability by selecting their calendars to coordinate meetings efficiently.</p></li>
    </ul>
    <p><strong>Synchronizing external calendars:</strong> If event managers use tools like Google Calendar or Outlook, follow these steps to sync them with Odoo:</p>
    <ol>
        <li>
            <p>Navigate to <strong>Settings > Calendar > Sync External Calendar</strong>.</p>
        </li>
        <li><p>Link each user’s external calendar to the Odoo Calendar app.</p></li>
    </ol>
    <p>This ensures that appointments made outside of Odoo automatically appear in the Odoo calendar.</p>
    <p>Refer to the following guides for detailed steps:</p>
    <p><strong>👉 </strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar/google.html">Google Calendar Integration</a></p>
    <p><strong>👉 </strong><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/calendar/outlook.html">Outlook Integration</a></p>
    <h3>Manage recruitment and employee planning</h3>
    <hr />
    <p>Hire event staff and assign them to shifts seamlessly</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>In <strong>Recruitment</strong>:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Create job offers for interim positions (e.g., Host, Cloakroom manager, Activity Instructor).</p></li>
                <li><p>Publish them on the website.</p></li>
                <li><p>Collect applications and manage hiring process.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>In <strong>Employee</strong>:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Add job position under "Roles" in the planning part of the "Work Information" tab once hired.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>In <strong>Planning</strong>:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><p>Create shifts by event.</p></li>
                <li><p>Assign employees manually or use "Auto-Assign" button to assign them automatically based on their roles and their availability.</p></li>
            </ul>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
            <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
            <p>
                Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h2>
        <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></span>
    </h2>
    <hr />
    <ul>
        <li>
            Want to handle ticket sales at the entrance? Install the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale</font></strong> app, add your tickets to it, and you're ready to go"
        </li>
        <li>
            Activate the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Quality Check</font></strong> setting in Inventory to easily track and ensure the quality of your event logistics items.
        </li>
        <li>
            Enhance on-site communication with vendors by making calls and sending SMS or WhatsApp messages directly through Odoo, using our integrated <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">VoIP and WhatsApp</font></strong> modules.
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                Use the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Social Media app</font></strong> to manage and schedule social media posts related to your events if it's requested by the clients.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment thanks to our
            <strong>
                <font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Accounting App</font><font class="text-o-color-2"><span style="font-weight: normal;">.</span></font>
            </strong>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
        <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
            <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
            <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Schedule a demo</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <h1><br /></h1>    
  </template>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Event Management</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2"/>
    <field name="icon">🎆</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
