<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>Accounting Firm</strong>
            </span>
            <br/>
        </h1>
        <p>Welcome to the Odoo Accounting Firm package! This guide will help you manage your missions efficiently from opportunity management to billing, as well as requesting documents. </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent" data-oe-protected="true"/>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Basics</span>
        </h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>Your Odoo Accounting Firm package includes essential apps to streamline your operations:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Manage opportunities with the <strong>CRM App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Generate quote and manage sale order from the <strong>Sales App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Follow up on missions leveraging the <strong>Project App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Bill easily and manage your accounts with the <strong>Accounting App</strong>.</li>
            <li>Have a central repository for requested documents in<strong> Documents App</strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on &#xFEFF;<a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">&#xFEFF;Odoo.com/trial&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>A crucial part of the business is to transform prospects into customers, then to follow up efficiently on the mission and finally to bill customers in for your work. We got you covered all along this journey!</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Use case</span>
        </h2>
        <hr/>
        <h3>👋 Welcoming prospects</h3>
        <p>You just got a all and a customer wants to know more about your rates and services. Rather than sending him an email on the side, leverage the centralised chatter capability and most of all, do not lose this lead!</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong>.</li>
            <li> Create a new lead typing the customer name and augment the contact by clicking the create and edit. Specify email address for that contact so that you can communicate within Odoo.</li>
            <li> Add any extra information relevant such as expected revenues and notes.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Now that your lead is in the system, you can directly correspond with the associated contact leveraging the opportunity chatter!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>For such typical request, you can leverage email templates for ask recurrent questions and save time exposing your services!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>
                    Yet be aware that by default, any email sent to info@yourcompanyname.example.com will create a new lead in your CRM pipeline!<br/>
                    You can verify this by opening the CRM App, opening the sales teams from the Configuration menu, and opening the sales team you have.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html">&#xFEFF;🎓 CRM&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>📜 Getting to the "Go"</h3>
        <p>You just got a all and a customer wants you for the job, congratulations!</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>CRM App</strong> in case this is the fruit of an opportunity, and then click the New quotation button to transform this into a quotation.<br/>
Otherwise, open the <strong>Sales App</strong> and create a new quote.
            </li>
            <li>Select the corresponding products or leverage a quotation template, the "Monthly VAT - Package" typically.</li>
            <li>Send this quote by email so that you new customer confirm the mission and accept your fees.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You can preview the quote at this stage. This view is for your customer to confirm the mission. </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Once confirmed, by your customer, the quote turns into a sales order, which creates the corresponding project and tasks in the projects (where you manage your workload).</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You can as well submit a letter of mission to be digitally signed with the <strong>Sign app</strong>.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-secondary">&#xFEFF;🎓 Sales&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Customer identity management</strong>
        </p>
        <p>Identity management is a must do activity in your business and to support you with that, the contacts encompass all the necessary.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>Contacts App</strong> and reach your new customer form.
            </li>
            <li>Easily request identity document from the gear icon (⚙️) in the bread crumb.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Sending a document request creates an activity for you to follow up without mental load!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                When the document is available, reach the contact ID tab to fill in the contact details.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>When filling in the identity document expiration date, you can leverage the contacts filter "Expired IDs" to efficiently find the IDs to update!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">🔃</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>An automation runs daily to request expiring and expired identity documents to your contacts.
                    Make sure to check the open document request from Documents App.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/essentials/contacts.html" class="btn btn-secondary">&#xFEFF;🎓 Contacts&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Setup the project</strong>
        </p>
        <p>The project creation created as well some tasks to handle from now on.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Open the <strong>Project App</strong> and open the project corresponding to the sale order you just confirmed, or click the Tasks smart button at the top of the sale order.
            </li>
            <li>
                The Customer onboarding task contains details about actions to take to have your customer in order.
                <ul>
                    <li>Set the recurrence for tasks not coming from the project template and the dead line dates to all project tasks.</li>
                    <li>To assign the Project Manager, Assistant and Reviewer, open the Project App and open the settings of the project, clicking the three dots in the top right corner of the corresponding tile.</li>
                    <li>For the project tasks, you can assign the owner or more employees in case you work with Junior / Senior pairing.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Define the to do list and documents to request which suite you in the template project tasks.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>When you confirm a sale order, know that the duplicated project is defined in the product you sold. You can edit the project to adjust the list for customer onboarding actions or folder architecture so that you save time in the future.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Open the <strong>Project App</strong>, open the project pointed by your Customer onboarding product and display the project shortcut for Documents if not yet done.</li>
                    <li>Go to the project documents with the shortcuts to edit the folder architecture at your convenience.</li>
                    <li>Open the Customer onboarding task to edit the action list.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html">&#xFEFF;🎓 Project&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>📬 Follow up on your customer database</h3>
        <p>Having access in record time to all activities and metrics from your customer databases is key.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Connecting your customer database</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open your new customer project settings.</li>
            <li>In the Database tab, set the appropriate hosting option and then fill in the additional required inputs, including API credentials provided by your customer. </li>
            <li>Open the Databases App to have your customer database metrics at your finger tips!</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="image.png" src="/web/image/accounting_firm.ir_attachment_1835" style="width: 100%;"/><br/>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>The Databases App comes with capabilities to efficiently manage tasks, access rights and more!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>🗂️ Document management</h3>
        <p>Since a tedious part of the job is to request and organise documents for reference and traceability, a good document management system is required!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Even though you can manage documents in your database, we highly recommend you to handle those from your customer Odoo databases since those belong to them!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Documents is now creating a dedicated space for you projects to prevent you to mix documents from your customers.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Setting up the project folder email alias</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>To setup the project folder email alias, display the project top bar and add the Documents shortcut.</li>
            <li>Click the Document shortcut to open the Documents folder of this particular project, and deploy the information panel (top right corner i icon).</li>
            <li>Input the email alias for this customer and select the Inbox activity type and the assignee of the activities which will be triggered when receiving new documents.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The documents sent to the email alias of this project will arrive in the root folder of the project. This can be considered as an inbox while sub folders contain treated documents in an organized fashion.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Note that only direct email capture the attached documents. Be clear with your customers to send a new email for any new documents they wish you to process from the email alias.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong>Requesting a document</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>To request a document such as an ID card or a bank statement, click New and then Request.</li>
            <li>Precise the document name you seek for, define the customer to request this from (making sure their email is configured), adjust the Due Date if necessary and finally hit the Request button.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>This creates an empty document in your project to be filled by your customer by uploading a file from the email they receive. You could do so for all required documents by the task.</p>
                <p>On upload of a document, you receive an activity which is visible in the notification for the Documents app.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Don't forget to check as done the activity when your done with a document to have clear visibility of your workload from the activity list.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Read more about Documents to leverage its full potential! </p>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html">&#xFEFF;🎓 Documents&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>⏲️ Time management</h3>
        <p>Some of your services might be time sheet invoiced. You can proceed by different ways to record your time.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>From a task</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Project App</strong> or navigate to the sale order associated tasks with the smart button at the top.</li>
            <li>Open the task you were working on, go to the Timesheets tab and add a new line.</li>
            <li>Saving the task will report this time in the sale order for billing.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <strong>From a project</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the the project you worked on.</li>
            <li>Click the project shortcut for Timesheets and add a line.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <strong>From the Timesheets App</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the Timesheets App, add a line selecting the project and task you worked on, and inputing the time spent today.</li>
            <li>You can as well change view for the list view for example, and click the New button to report some time.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Not all you time might be billable even when working on a customer projects. In such case, just leave the sale order item field blank.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>If you wish you can introduce sections in your sale order to structure it by year of follow up or simply add a note to the product line for example.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/timesheets.html">&#xFEFF;🎓 Timesheet&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>💵 Billing your efforts</h3>
        <p>Whether you performed some work for a fixed price or based on time sheets, you can expense your customer for this.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the <strong>Sales App</strong> and open the sale order you want to expense.</li>
            <li>
                    Click the Create Invoice button to create a draft invoice.<br/>
                    Note that fixed price product can be expensed as soon as the sale order is confirmed and recorded time sheets any time there is time not yet invoiced.
            </li>
            <li>
                    Confirm the invoice and send it to you customer for payment.<br/>
                    Once payed, you know the drill to reconcile the payment.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Invoicing is enabled by Invoicing and Accounting Apps. You can as well create invoices from them.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting/customer_invoices.html" class="btn btn-secondary">&#xFEFF;🎓 Invoicing&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3 class="">🧮 Ultimate beneficial owners' hunt</h3>
        <p>UBO identification can be a tedious task you don't want to lose time on. The Equity App comes with capabilities which will help you with this duty.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the contact from which you expect the UBO list.</li>
            <li>Select the Request UBO from the gear icon (⚙️) menu.</li>
            <li>Fine tune the email if needed and hit the send button.</li>
            <li>Your contact is now provided a portal access to record the UBO.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>An activity has been created for you to follow up on this.<br/>
    It self closes once your contact submits its UBO list.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Note that Equity App comes first with capabilities to capture transactions and valuation which you will find useful.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>💸 Anti-Money Laundering</h3>
        <p>Among your activities, you might as well handle the anti-money laundering aspect.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the contact form of the company you have to handle this for, Second Company for example.</li>
            <li>Navigate to the AML tab to appreciate the last assessment performed.</li>
            <li>Update the captured insights as you need and then update the last update date.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Information captured here are informative only and do not trigger or interact with any capability.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h3>📊 Follow up on project profitability</h3>
        <p>A crucial part of business is as well making sure it is profitable. Odoo helps you following up project profitability with the project Dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Open the Project App and click the Dashboard button from the top bar.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>
                        You have access in the project Dashboard to all related documents and can follow up on earnings and costs effortlessly.<br/>
                        Don't forget to update your employee costs, in the setting tab, to compute relevant costs.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>If relevant to share regular updates, Click New to perform a screenshot of the current progress of the project.</li>
            <li>Give it a name, take notes as you please and finally save this for future references.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Explore the Dashboard App to follow up overall work, progress and profitability cross projects at will.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>&#xFEFF;<a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project/project_management/project_dashboard.html">&#xFEFF;🎓 Project Dashboard&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">🥳</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our &#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">&#xFEFF;documentation&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF; and &#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">&#xFEFF;academy&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF; , and feel free to &#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">&#xFEFF;request a demo&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF; if you need help!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Do You Want to Go Further?</span>
        </h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>
                The Accounting Firm package is of great help but may not cover all your needs...<br/>
                Fortunately, Odoo got you covered:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                    The Accounting Firm package does not include any customization. Note that <strong>Studio App </strong>would enable you to setup specific fields for more robustness as well as much more advanced workflows and automations!
            </li>
            <li>You might want to setup questionnaires to fine tune your quotations and clarify the interactions with your customers. Have a look at the <strong>Survey App</strong> to do so!</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p>&#xFEFF;<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">&#xFEFF;Reach us&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o-paragraph">
            <br/>
        </div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Final word</span>
        </h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>You might have tested the Accounting Firm package with or without demo data.<br/>
                In any case, you may have written records in journals which are not deletable and which might be an issue for your traceability.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
                <p>
                    <strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then to create a new one for your own usage.</strong>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Accounting Firm - Start here!</field>
        <field name="icon">📑</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
