<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0">Odoo for Museums</h1>
        <p>Welcome to the Odoo Museum Management package!</p>
        <p>
            This suite of applications is designed specifically for institutions in the museum sector; whether you're running a historical museum, a contemporary art gallery, or a science and discovery center. Odoo brings everything you need to
            manage your operations in one place: from selling tickets and managing memberships, to curating exhibitions, overseeing artwork inventory, operating your shop, and coordinating staff schedules.
        </p>
        <p>With integrated apps such as Events, Inventory, Website, Point of Sale, and Planning, the solution streamlines daily operations, enhances visitor services, and improves team coordination.</p>
        <p>Focus on curating culture and welcoming visitors, while Odoo handles the behind-the-scenes logistics. 🖼️</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                Use <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Events</font></strong> to manage entry slots, ticket types, and attendance.
            </li>
            <li>
                Promote exhibitions and sell tickets online with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website &amp; eCommerce</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Handle on-site ticket and gift shop sales through <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Automate renewals and benefits with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Subscription</font></strong> for memberships.
            </li>
            <li>
                Track artworks and stock locations using <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Inventory</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Place vendor orders for artworks acquisitions or retail items via <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Digitally sign contracts and agreements using <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sign</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Organize staff shifts with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Planning</font></strong>, from front desk to gallery teams.
            </li>
            <li>
                Store contact details for artists, donors, and partners in <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Contacts</font></strong>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Generate invoices for services and sales through <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing</font></strong>.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage your entire business in it.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-800"><span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span></font>
                </strong>
            </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Museum package and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><br /></h3>
        <h3><strong>Manage Ticket Sales &amp; Memberships </strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Whether your visitors buy their tickets online or at the front desk, Odoo makes the experience seamless and professional.</p>
        <h4><strong>Sell Tickets On-Site</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Set up an <strong>Event</strong> for “Museum Entrance”</p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li><p>Enable “Multiple Slots”.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Use the “Slots” button to set and manage each specific entry time slot.</p></li>
                </ol>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Create a corresponding <strong>ticket product</strong>;<strong> </strong>you can customize prices for adults, kids, seniors,...</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Design a clean and attractive <strong>website page</strong> to showcase the museum’s entry options.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>At the front desk, open the <strong>Point of Sale</strong> session, select the ticket and confirm the payment.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h4><strong>Sell Tickets Online</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Embed the same <strong>Museum Entrance</strong> event on your website.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Visitors can choose a time slot, select ticket types, and pay directly online.</p></li>
            <li><p>Tickets are sent via email with a barcode; ready to scan on arrival via the Registration Desk tab.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <h4><strong>Manage Memberships</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Create a <strong>membership product</strong> (e.g., “Annual Museum Pass”).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Set the product type to <em>Service</em> and link it to a <strong>Membership Level</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign a <strong>special price list</strong> to the level (e.g., 100% discount on general admission).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>When someone purchases the pass, Odoo automatically applies their benefits.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>For example: A member revisiting the site sees all eligible tickets as €0.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3><strong>Manage Your Art Collection </strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Keep full control over your museum’s acquisitions, loans, and donations; all in one place.</p>
        <h4><strong>Track All Types of Artwork Acquisition</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>For each new piece, create a product record with its name, description, artist, and value.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Specify the <strong>acquisition type</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Purchase</strong>: Register a vendor bill and mark the receipt.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Donation</strong>: Record donor details and assign the artwork to a location.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Loan</strong>: Set expected return dates and add a reminder activity to coordinate returns.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Store location details (e.g., <em>Gallery C – Permanent Collection</em>) and include notes like <em>“Display on pedestal, under soft light." </em>on "<em>Description for Receipts field</em>".</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Click on the ⚙️ icon to open the <em>Edit Properties</em> menu. This lets you choose what type of information to collect for each artwork, so you can tailor records to how your museum manages its collection.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h4><strong>Handle Exhibition Display Rights</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>If a piece is on loan with an exhibition display agreement to pay or specify rights, generate a vendor bill reflecting these terms.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>Sign</strong> to upload the contract and get a digital signature from the artist or lender.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Attach the signed agreement to the bill for full traceability.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Create your own “Display Rights Agreement” template in <strong>Sign</strong> with all required fields. When generating a vendor bill, follow these steps:</p>
                <p>
                    Click the ⚙️ icon ‣ Request Signatures ‣ Choose your template ‣ Select the client or lender ‣ Set the signing order ‣ Send for signatures.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Example</strong></p>
        <p>You receive a sculpture on loan from an artist.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Create the item in your system as a product and log it as a Loan.</li>
            <li>If needed, upload the loan agreement and via Odoo.</li>
            <li>Create a receipt to record the loan in your inventory.</li>
            <li>Log the artwork’s location, for example: “Gallery Room B – Wall 3.”</li>
            <li>Schedule a reminder to plan the return date.</li>
        </ul>
        <h3><strong>Run Your Souvenir Shop </strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Offer a smooth retail experience in your museum boutique with everything from stock control to checkout.</p>
        <h4><strong>Set Up the Shop</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Create a <strong>new Point of Sale</strong> session specifically for the boutique.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Add each product (books, prints, souvenirs) with its image, price, and supplier.</p></li>
            <li>Configure tax settings accurately.</li>
        </ol>
        <h4><strong>Keep Your Inventory Up to Date</strong><br /></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>Link each product to inventory so you can track how much is in stock.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Set <strong>reorder rules</strong> to automatically restock from vendors when low.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>View real-time stock levels and generate purchase orders directly from the dashboard.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <p><strong>Process Point of Sales:</strong></p>
        <ol>
            <li><p>Use the POS interface at the cash desk or a mobile device.</p></li>
            <li><p>Accept multiple payment types: cash, card, or gift vouchers.</p></li>
            <li><p>Print or email receipts instantly.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Don't forget to set product categories on your products and assign them to the right Point of Sale. In the POS settings, use <strong>Restrict Categories</strong> to control which product categories are shown at each sales point,
                    like tickets at the entrance and souvenirs in the shop.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><strong>Boost Visibility Online </strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Your website is more than just a page; it’s your digital front door.</p>
        <h4><strong>Build an Engaging Museum Website</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>Use Odoo’s website builder to create an attractive design with your branding.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Add an <strong>Exhibitions page</strong>: Highlight current and upcoming events, feature artwork photos, and introduce the artists.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Include a <strong>Donations</strong> page by adding the “Add Donation” block and customizing it to your needs.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Enable <strong>online ticketing</strong> by embedding entry offers or event pages with booking options. (see above)</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>If you offer <strong>memberships</strong>, create a landing page that explains the benefits and includes a “Join Now” button.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3><strong>Schedule Your Staff </strong></h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Entrance staff, security teams, guides; everyone needs to know where they should be and when.</p>
        <h4><strong>Build Shift Schedules</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>Define your operating hours (e.g., 10am–6pm, Tuesday–Sunday).</p></li>
            <li><p>Create roles like “Front Desk Staff,” “Gallery Attendant,” or “Tour Guide,” and assign them within each Employee’s record.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>auto-plan feature</strong> to assign people based on availability and expertise.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h4><strong>Communicate Efficiently</strong></h4>
        <ol>
            <li><p>Each staff member sees their schedule in their portal or by email.</p></li>
            <li><p>Last-minute changes? Drag-and-drop makes updates quick and clear.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>
                    Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2><strong>Do You Want to Go Further?</strong></h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                With <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>CRM app</strong></font>, attract donors and manage relationships in a streamlined pipeline to stay connected effortlessly.
            </li>
            <li>
                Add the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Restaurant app</strong></font> to run your museum’s café or small restaurant.
            </li>
            <li>
                Enhance your website with the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Digital Collection</strong></font> feature by embedding interactive 3D images of artworks using iframe for an engaging visitor experience.
            </li>
            <li>
                Collect valuable visitor feedback after events and exhibitions using the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Surveys app</strong></font>.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment thanks to our
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font><font class="text-o-color-2"><span style="font-weight: normal;">.</span></font>
                </strong>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><br /></h1>
        <p><br /></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Museums</field>
        <field name="icon">🖼️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
  </odoo>
