<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 data-oe-version="1.0"><span style="font-size: 36px;"><strong>Cake shop</strong></span></h1>
        <p>Welcome to the <strong>Odoo Cake shop package</strong>!</p>
        <p>This setup is tailored for cake shop companies selling directly to consumers. Cake shops are businesses that specialize in offering a variety of cakes, pastries, and other confectionery items, catering to personalized and special orders for occasions like birthdays, weddings, and celebrations.</p>
        <p>They primarily use the Point of Sale application, along with Inventory, Sales, and Purchase apps. For businesses looking to expand online, the Website and E-commerce applications are ideal for showcasing products and handling online orders.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>Basics</h2><p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase App</font></strong> manages raw material orders and vendors.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale App</font></strong> manages in-store orders and payments.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> streamlines customer orders and quotations, such as managing custom cake requests.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website &amp; eCommerce App</font></strong> enables online sales.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
            </div>
        </div><h2>Use Case</h2>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Cake Shop Package</strong> and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Purchase raw materials</h3>
        <p>Maintain stock of fresh ingredients.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Create a purchase order</strong>: Select the materials you need for your cakes and pastries.</li>
            <li><strong>Choose the best vendor</strong>: Pick the vendor offering the best deal for the requested materials.</li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Manage orders and payments</h3>
        <p>Streamline in-store order processing and offer flexible payment options.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Take orders in Point of Sales</strong>: Process in-store cake and pastry orders quickly using the Point of Sales system.</li>
            <li><strong>Accept flexible payments</strong>: Provide multiple payment options (cash, card, mobile).</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Implement Loyalty Programs for repeat customers to encourage future purchases. Offer discounts or rewards for frequent orders, either in-store or online.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Grow your business with e-commerce</h3>
        <p>Expand sales online and offer convenience for customers.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Online orders, In-shop pickup</strong>: Allow customers to order online, pay in-store, and pick up at the shop.</li>
            <li><strong>Custom orders</strong>: Let customers place custom cake orders for special occasions via your online store by allowing them to specify details like size, flavor, and decoration in a custom order form.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                For custom cakes, you can use the <strong>MTO (Make to Order)</strong> method, which means ingredients are only ordered when a specific customer places an order. This helps you avoid keeping large amounts of stock for products you only make occasionally, ensuring that you only purchase what you need when you need it.
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>Do you want to go further?</h2>
        <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your cake shop:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Track stock in real-time, manage multiple storage locations, automate restocking, and monitor expiration dates to ensure ingredient freshness and avoid shortages, with our<strong> Inventory app</strong>.</li>
            <li>Easily craft custom cakes and pastries with the <strong>Manufacturing app</strong> by creating manufacturing orders based on customer demand and linking the necessary ingredients to each product. Use the Make to Order (MTO) route to order ingredients only when a customer places an order, helping you avoid excess stock.</li>
            <li>Restaurant mode: If you offer an "eat-in" option, manage tables, orders, and payments seamlessly with the <strong>Point of Sales app</strong>.</li>
            <li>Employee scheduling: Use the <strong>Planning App</strong> to create and manage employee schedules, ensuring you have the right staff at the right times for busy days and custom cake orders.</li>
            <li>Manage your team efficiently and integrate them into all processes with the <strong>Employees App.</strong></li>
            <li>Easily handle your accounting with the integrated <strong>Accounting App</strong>.</li>
            <li><strong>Marketing automation</strong>: Manage all communication channels (email, social media, SMS) in one place.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                    <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Schedule a demo</a></p>
                </div>
            </div>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Cake Store</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">🍰</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">79.0</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
