<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 data-heading-link-id="876564385421" data-oe-version="2.0">
            <strong>Odoo for non-profit organizations</strong>
        </h1>
        <p>Welcome to the Odoo Non-Profit Management package!</p>
        <p>This set of applications is built for NGOs of all sizes; whether you're supporting local
            communities, protecting the environment, or advocating for human rights. Odoo helps you
            manage everything in one place: donations, petitions, volunteers, events, memberships,
            and communication.</p>
        <p>With connected tools like Donations, CRM, Events, Website, and Planning, you can save
            time on admin work and focus more on your mission.</p>
        <p>Let Odoo handle the logistics, so you can focus on making a difference. 🌍</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="454458992099">
            <span class="h1-fs">
                <strong>Basics</strong>
            </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li><strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Donations</font>
                </strong> records
                contributions and generates fiscal attestations for donors.</li>
            <li><strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Petition</font>
                </strong> tracks
                signatures, signatories, and progress for each petition.</li>
            <li>
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Project</font>
                </strong> structures
                campaigns, assigns tasks, and tracks progress.</li>
            <li> Donors, members, signatories, and partners are organized in <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Contacts</font>
                </strong>.</li>
            <li> Follow-ups and communication logs are handled efficiently with <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font>
                </strong>.</li>
            <li> Create <font class="text-o-color-1">
                    <strong>events</strong>
                </font> to raise awareness, coordinate
                volunteer activities, or host annual general assemblies.</li>
            <li>Promote events, create donation and petition forms, and sell merchandise online
                using <font class="text-o-color-1">
                    <strong>Website &amp; eCommerce</strong>
                </font>.</li>
            <li> Recurring memberships and automated renewals are managed by <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Subscription</font>
                </strong>.</li>
            <li> Volunteer shifts and roles are scheduled and tracked through <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Planning</font>
                </strong>.</li>
            <li> Thank-you notes for donors, petition follow-ups, and newsletters are sent using <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font>
                </strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage
                    your entire business in it.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="1270573576017">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-800">
                        <span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span>
                    </font>
                </strong>
            </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows
            you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free
            to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
            data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true"
                data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt;
                    Upgrade your Non-profit organization package and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1250880587472">Manage Donations &amp; Fiscal Attestations</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Donations records contributions from supporters, including donor details, and easily
            generates fiscal attestations for tax purposes.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Use the <strong>Website</strong> app to create a donation form that collects key
                donor information and preferred amounts.</li>
            <li>Once submitted and paid, the donation appears in the <strong>Donations</strong> app
                with full donor and payment details.</li>
            <li>Generate fiscal attestations in the <strong>Donations</strong> app by selecting the
                relevant year and defining the minimum donation amount required for eligibility.</li>
            <li>Export fiscal attestations list as a CSV file for authorities, including donor
                names, total donations amount, and transaction dates.</li>
            <li>Send PDFs of fiscal attestations to donors via email as proof of their
                contributions.</li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <ul>
                    <li>Add custom fields using the <strong>website editor </strong>to collect the
                        info needed from donors.</li>
                    <li>Use the <strong>Sign app</strong> to upload your fiscal attestation
                        template, add signature and date fields, and sign documents electronically
                        before sending them to donors.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1482938827594">Launch and Track Petitions</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Petition tracks signatures and signatory info, and monitor progress per petition.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Create a new petition in the <strong>Petition</strong> app and customize the
                petition page and form using the <strong>Website Editor</strong>.</li>
            <li>
                <p>Publish petition forms online and share via email or social media.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Each submitted form creates a new signature record in the <strong>Petition</strong>
                    app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track signature progress and analyze data per petition in real time.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Keep signatories informed about petition results by sending follow-up emails.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Add a checkbox on the petition form to let signatories opt-in to receive updates
                    about future actions, events, and news from the NGO, then add those
                    contacts to your mailing list for future updates and events.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1239063230519">Create and Manage Events</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Events helps organize actions like public talks, fundraisers, volunteer days,
            or annual meetings to engage supporters and organize participation
            efficiently.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Create events for public or private audiences, such as a General Assembly for
                members or a Human Rights talk &amp; dinner.</li>
            <li>
                <p>Set entry <strong>slots</strong>, <strong>ticket</strong> types, and <strong>
                    attendance</strong> limits if needed.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Choose the event <strong>visibility</strong> by making it public or accessible
                    only via a shared link.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Customize the<strong> event page</strong> on your website to include all the
                    information you want to share.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Share event links via email or social media for easy sign-up.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Manage volunteer registrations for events like “Refugee Welcome Pack
                    Distribution.” Each month, send a list of upcoming actions, and create events so
                    volunteers can select which ones they want to participate in.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1747421457769">Promote Online with Website &amp; eCommerce</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Website &amp; eCommerce promotes your NGO online by sharing your mission and actions,
            selling memberships, merchandise, collecting donations, and managing petitions forms for
            signatures.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Share the mission and impact clearly on the <strong>website</strong>. Explain the
                NGO’s goals, ongoing projects, and how visitors can get involved or support.</li>
            <li>
                <p>Sell branded merchandise, fundraising products, and memberships online with<strong>
                    eCommerce</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create products like a “Solidarity Candle,” set prices, add images, and
                            activate online sales.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Configure payment providers and methods.</p>
                    </li>
                </ol>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Create a donation form using the “Donation” block in the website editor, and
                    embed petition forms directly on the website.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Promote events with dedicated event pages and online ticket sales.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Set up pricelists to offer special prices when resellers buy in bulk. This helps
                    manage discounts automatically for larger orders.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Go to <strong>Sales</strong> &gt; <em>Configuration</em> &gt; <em>Pricelists</em>
                        .</li>
                    <li>Create a new pricelist (e.g., “Reseller Bulk Pricing”).</li>
                    <li>Add discount rules based on minimum quantities.</li>
                    <li>Assign the pricelist to reseller contacts.</li>
                    <li>Discounts apply automatically on sales orders.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="973763473079">Manage Campaigns with Project and Tasks</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Campaigns help organize fundraising or awareness efforts by breaking them into manageable
            tasks.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Create a new Project for the campaign in the <strong>Project</strong> app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Add Tasks to the project, such as “Design flyers,” “Contact sponsors,” or
                    “Organize event logistics.”</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign tasks to team members or volunteers, setting deadlines and priorities.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track progress by updating task statuses and using the project overview.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use built-in communication tools to discuss tasks and share files within the
                    project.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1229729186302">Manage Contact Portfolio and Relationships</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>CRM and Contacts manages contact relationships and interactions for donors, members,
            and partners.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Store and organize all contacts in <strong>Contacts</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track interactions, plan activities, and log communications in the <strong>CRM</strong>
                    app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use tags and filters in <strong>Contacts</strong> to segment contacts for
                    targeted campaigns or follow-ups.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1521434840664">Communicate Campaigns &amp; News</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Use Email Marketing to send newsletters, donation calls, event promotion, and
            keep supporters and members informed.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Create a new mailing in the Email Marketing app.</li>
            <li>Select recipients using customized or favorites filters like Donors, Members, or
                Volunteers.</li>
            <li>Design your message with the drag-and-drop editor.</li>
            <li>Personalize content using dynamic fields (e.g. name).</li>
            <li>Send or schedule and track opens and clicks.</li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <div data-heading-link-id="258362732667">How to create Contact Segments for Email
                    Campaigns?</div>
                <div>
                    <br />
                </div>
                <ol>
                    <li>Create a new <strong>Mailing</strong> under the <em>Email Marketing</em>
                        app.</li>
                    <li>Select <strong>"Contacts"</strong> as the recipient type.</li>
                    <li>Use the <strong>filter</strong> feature to find contacts based on specific
                        tags.</li>
                    <li>Choose a tag like <strong>Donors</strong>, <strong>Volunteers</strong>, <strong>
                        Partners</strong>, or <strong>Signatories</strong>.</li>
                    <li>Save this filter as a <strong>Favorite</strong> to easily reuse it in future
                        campaigns.</li>
                </ol>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="93321945457">Schedule Volunteer Shifts with Planning</h3>
        <hr />
        <p><strong>Planning</strong> schedules and manages volunteer shifts and assignments
            effectively.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Define volunteer roles like “Outreach Coordinator” or “Event Assistant” in the <strong>Employee
                    form</strong>, under the Settings tab.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>Planning</strong> app to schedule shifts automatically based on
                    availability and roles.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p> Volunteers can check upcoming assignments via their <strong>portal</strong> or
                    through email notifications.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="635739044896">Organize Internal Planning with Calendar</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Use <strong>Calendar</strong> to schedule internal meetings, volunteer briefings,
            fieldwork missions, or training sessions.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Open the <strong>Calendar</strong> app to create appointments, team check-ins, or
                    planning sessions.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Click on a time slot to schedule an event and invite team members.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>View team availability by toggling on their calendars to avoid conflicts.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>How to sync Odoo Calendar with External Calendar like Google or Outlook calendar?</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Go to <strong>Settings</strong> → <strong>Calendar</strong> → <strong>Sync
                        External Calendar</strong>.</li>
                    <li>Connect each user’s Google or Outlook calendar.</li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Events created outside of Odoo will automatically appear in the Odoo
                            calendar.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="39204557186">Keep Expenses Under Control</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Expenses tracks reimbursements and operational costs for campaigns, events, or fieldwork.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>
                    Team members submit expenses with receipts for approval.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p> Review and confirm expenses in the <em>Expense</em> app for tracking and
                    accounting.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="533935947239">Manage Sales and Invoicing</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Sales and Invoicing handle partner contributions, large donations, and eCommerce orders.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Create sales orders for specific donations, bulk merchandise purchases or
                    partnership packages in <strong>Sales</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Confirm orders to generate invoices automatically in <strong>Invoicing</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track payment status and send reminders as needed.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1596868264178">Workflow Example</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>1. <strong>Launch the Campaign</strong>: Create a Project called <em>Stop Child
                Labor</em> and add key tasks like “Create awareness materials” and “Reach out to
            schools and local authorities”.</p>
        <p>2. <strong>Publish Donation &amp; Petition Forms</strong>: Use the Website to embed a
            donation form and a petition urging policy changes.</p>
        <p>3. <strong>Organize Awareness Events</strong>: Schedule events like <em>Community
                Talks</em> or <em>Film Screenings</em> using Events.</p>
        <p>4. <strong>Involve Volunteers</strong>: Create volunteer roles in Employees and assign
            shifts using Planning.</p>
        <p>5.<strong> Sell Campaign Merchandise</strong>: Offer items like a <em>“Stop Child
                Labor” badge</em> via eCommerce, and manage orders and payments online.</p>
        <p>6. <strong>Track Costs</strong>: Log campaign-related expenses in Expenses, linked to the
            project.</p>
        <p>7. <strong>Send Attestations</strong>: Generate and sign donation attestations using
            Donations and Sign, then send to supporters and authorities at the end of the year.</p>
        <p>8. <strong>Keep Supporters Engaged</strong>: Use Email Marketing to send updates and
            thank-you messages to donors and petition signers.</p>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your
                    Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a
                        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a
                        href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel
                    free to<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need
                    help!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Assign <em>analytic accounts</em> to each campaign in <strong>Accounting</strong>
                    for better financial tracking.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>WhatsApp</strong> via <strong>CRM</strong> to coordinate with field
                    volunteers.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Expand your reach through <strong>Social Marketing</strong> on Instagram or X
                    (Twitter).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Track badge and t-shirt stock using <strong>Inventory</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Order materials like posters or banners in bulk with the <strong>Purchase</strong>
                    app.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="1527803283289">
            <span style="font-size: 34px;">
                <strong>Do you want to go further?</strong>
            </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>Assign <em>analytic accounts</em> to each campaign in <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting app</font>
                </strong> for
                better financial tracking.</li>
            <li>Use <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">WhatsApp module</font>
                </strong> to
                communicate easily with field volunteers.</li>
            <li>Expand your reach through <font class="text-o-color-1">
                    <strong>Social Marketing</strong>
                </font>app.</li>
            <li>Track stock of campaign materials with <font class="text-o-color-1">
                    <strong>Inventory</strong>
                </font> and manage supplier orders
                efficiently using the <strong>
                    <font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase</font>
                </strong> app.</li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a
                        demo</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1 data-heading-link-id="602632800967">
            <br />
        </h1>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for non-profit organizations</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="icon">📢</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_13" />
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
    </record>
</odoo>
