<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
                <p>
                <strong><span class="h1-fs" style="font-size: 3rem;">Custom Furniture Production</span></strong>
                </p>
                <p>Hello there! </p>
                <p>You just installed the Odoo package for Custom Furniture Production companies. By doing so, we have installed many necessary apps to run your company efficiently. </p>
                <p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Demo - Use Case. (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc" tabindex="-1">
                <div class="o_knowledge_toc_content">
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Basics:</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Use case:</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">1. Opportunities &amp; CRM 🎯</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">2. Products &amp; services 🪑</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">3. Quotations &amp; sales 💰</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="5" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">4. Purchases &amp; inventory 📦</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="6" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">5. Project &amp; Field Services 🦺</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="7" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">6. Manufacture &amp; Quality ✅</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="8" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">7. Planning &amp; resources 🗓️</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="9" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">8. Invoicing 🧾</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="10" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Do you want to go further? 🚀</a>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h2 style="font-size: 34px;"><strong>Basics:</strong></h2>
                <hr />
                <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
                <ul>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font></strong> and the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales Apps </font></strong>to manage your customer relations, your opportunities and create stunning quotations.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Ensure a perfect follow-up of your projects with <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Project</font></strong> &amp; <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Field Services Apps</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Fasten your <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchases</font></strong>. Keep track of your inventory, and follow your deliveries in the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Inventory App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Level up your Manufacture process with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Manufacture App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Follow your planning and keep track of worked time in the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Planning &amp; Timesheets Apps</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Invoice at the right time with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoice App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                </ul>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
                        <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into an additional cashier (and much more).</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><font class="text-o-color-5"> </font></p>
                <h2 style="margin-bottom: 0px;" class="null">
                <strong><span class="h1-fs">Use case:</span></strong>
                </h2>
                <hr />
                <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a complete flow from the opportunity to delivery and some demo data to execute the flows described hereunder. </p>
                <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various actions you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
                <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it if you like. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Custom Furniture Production package and check the related box. </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>1. Opportunities &amp; CRM 🎯</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>
                The <font class="text-o-color-1"> <strong>CRM</strong> </font> application allows you to collect requests from your potential customers by aggregating several sources:
                </p>
                <ul>
                <li>Create an opportunity each time you face a potential customer, receive a phone call, etc.</li>
                <li>
                        Redirect the emails sent to<a href="mailto:info@my-construction-business.com"> info@my-construction-business.com</a> to the <strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website App</font></strong> to create a contact form that will redirect all the requests to the <strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font></strong>.
                </li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                Take advantage of every opportunity. The <strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font> </strong> centralizes everything and allows you to ensure the efficient follow-up of each request. If the request becomes concrete, create
                the customer in the <strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Contact</font> </strong> app.
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 CRM</a><br /></p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>2. Products &amp; services 🪑</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>Managing your products and their characteristics is critical in Odoo. This package includes several configs, which you can explore by navigating to the Sales App -&gt; Products. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>By default, there is a filter on "Sales" products; remove it from the search bar to see all products available.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>
                <strong><span class="h4-fs">Services</span></strong>
                </p>
                <p>There are 4 different kinds of services available in this configuration:</p>
                <ul>
                <li><strong>Prepaid services, fixed price</strong> (Initial design consultation &amp; Final Inspection. Note that the first one will also create a new project for each confirmed order to ensure Project follow-up).</li>
                <li><strong>Based on timesheets</strong> (Concept Development and 3D renderings, this one will create a specific task in the existing "3D Renderings" Project)</li>
                <li><strong>Based on timesheets, subcontracted</strong> (Design presentation &amp; revisions, this config will create a new Purchase Order to buy this prestation and create a task in the dedicated project).</li>
                <li><strong>Based on timesheets</strong> - Field services (Delivery and installation &amp; Electrical and lighting installation) will automatically create a task in the Field Service App.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                <strong><span class="h4-fs">Goods</span></strong>
                </p>
                <p>You can also find 4 different kinds of goods:</p>
                <ul>
                <li><strong>Manufactured Goods </strong>will be manufactured based on a Bill of Material.</li>
                <li><strong>Purchased Goods</strong> that will be purchased and sold to your customers.</li>
                <li><strong>Consumable goods:</strong> These will not be tracked (Such as bolts, finish painting, and sandpaper).</li>
                <li><strong>Components </strong>that will serve to create manufactured products. </li>
                </ul>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Explore our documentation to ensure the correct configuration for each product, and do not hesitate to duplicate and edit an existing product. </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>3. Quotations &amp; sales 💰</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>Once your products are correctly set up, creating perfect quotations is extremely easy. Access the Sales App and click the New button to create a new quotation. Select your customer and start adding your products. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you usually structure your quotations similarly, use the Quotation Template feature. It will allow you to configure a set of products and sections that will always be imported when you select it.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>For this use case, open the David Patel quotation. You can see a complete setup using all the products mentioned in the previous topic. </p>
                <p>
                Confirm the quotation. Your top bar shows that it creates different tasks in different projects, an upcoming delivery, a purchase, and various hours to plan. These are all automated actions based on your product configuration.
                These will be detailed in the following topics.
                </p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>4. Purchases &amp; inventory 📦</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>To manage your inventory and everything you need to complete the order, navigate to the Inventory App. </p>
                <p>
                In this App, you can see that the delivery is not yet ready to be shipped, as you currently don't have the necessary products. If you navigate to Operations &gt; Replenishment, you will find the list of suggested purchase/manufacture
                orders missing to complete this order. Select everything, and click on "Replenish" &gt; "Order." 
                </p>
                <p>This will create two purchase orders and a manufacturing order. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you want to remove this part of your process, you can use reordering rules. These will ensure a fluid replenishment based on minimum quantities of each product or based on orders.</p>
                        <p>
                        <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase/products/reordering.html" target="_blank" class="btn btn-secondary"><span style="font-weight: normal;">🎓 Reordering rules</span></a><br />
                        </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>In the Purchase Apps, you can see all your Requests For Quotation, which are ready to be sent to your providers. When you have confirmation that your order has been placed, confirm each RFQ to continue the process.</p>
                <p><strong>Jane Design</strong>: She is your subcontractor for Design presentations and revisions. </p>
                <p><strong>My Chairs Vendor</strong>: Will provide you Conference chairs to complete your order.</p>
                <p><strong>My Rug Vendor</strong>: Will provide you the custom area rug in sufficient square meters.</p>
                <p><strong>My Metal Vendor</strong>: Will provide the Conference Table Metal Legs you need to manufacture the conference table.</p>
                <p><strong>My Wood Vendor</strong>: Will send you the Oak Wood Panels you need to create the tables.</p>
                <p>Once all your orders are confirmed, you are ready to receive them in the Inventory App. Access it and select the 4 to process button in the Receipts category. You can now validate the reception of all your orders. </p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>5. Project &amp; Field Services 🦺</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>
                Manage your entire projects with the Project App. You can see that your Sale Order has created a Project with a bunch of already configured tasks. Follow the evolution of your project with tasks, stages, status, and
                activities. 
                </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>
                        You can adapt your overview for each project by selecting the small "Sliders" icon at the top right of your screen. It will allow you to add a bunch of practical views to get the complete overview of your project, including* :
                        </p>
                        <ul>
                        <li>Tasks</li>
                        <li>Dashboard ➡️ Your project's status at a glance.</li>
                        <li>Timesheets</li>
                        <li>Planning</li>
                        <li>Sales Orders</li>
                        <li>Invoices</li>
                        <li>Purchase Orders</li>
                        <li>From WH ➡️ Deliveries from your warehouse to this specific customer</li>
                        <li>To WH ➡️ Products sent back to your warehouse</li>
                        <li>Bills of Materials</li>
                        <li>Manufacturing Orders</li>
                        <li>Analytic Items ➡️ Track any cost using Analytic Items from the Accounting App</li>
                        </ul>
                        <p>You can add other views with specific filters and ease your project follow-up.</p>
                        <p>*This list will, of course, depend on your installed apps and configuration.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>
                Suppose you navigate to the Field Service App. You can also find service tasks like Delivery and Installation or Electrical and lighting installation. This will allow your workers to log time, pick products, and keep track of the tasks
                directly from there. 
                </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Odoo is also integrated into an App. You may want your worker to complete their reports and follow the task on their mobile phone!</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>6. Manufacture &amp; Quality ✅</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>Ensure a frictionless manufacturing process by accessing the Manufacture App. </p>
                <p>You can see a new Manufacture order has been posted by navigating into Operations &gt; Manufacture Orders. </p>
                <p>On your dashboard, you can see 1 order "To Launch" in the Core Board Composing Machine. Open it to start logging your manufacturing process. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>The Manufacture App comes with the Shop Floor app. This will provide a specific view for your worker to keep track of any task in a particular Work Center. </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>Go to the Shop Floor App and validate the first step of your production by clicking on it. Continue with the other steps until you can register your production. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>A Quality Check Point has been set for each product. It requires your worker or the Quality Team to take a picture of any manufactured item. Use any image to pass the check for this demo.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>
                When you are done with your production, you can finally deliver the complete order to your customer. To do so, navigate to the Field Service Apps. From the Installation task, you can see 31 Products that require pick-up. Click
                on the smart button and validate this picking.
                </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you do not have a specific installation task or want to deliver it separately, you can do it in the Inventory App.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>7. Planning &amp; resources 🗓️</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>
                Use the Planning in the Field Service <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">​</font> </strong> app to organize the work of your employees. Define which project and when they have to work. Easily manage shift conflicts, workload, and
                replacements in case of leave.
                </p>
                <p>Record your employees' time spent on each project using the Timesheets app. On the employee form, remember to define an hourly cost.</p>
                <p>
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/timesheets.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Timesheets</a>
                </p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>8. Invoicing 🧾</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>
                Create a down payment from the sales order as the first invoicing step. This will generate the first invoice in the
                <strong>
                        <font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing</font>
                </strong>
                app. Then, schedule one or several "Invoicing Schedule" activities on the sales order so you never forget to send an intermediary invoice to sustain your cash flow.
                </p>
                <p>
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/discuss/overview/plan_activities.html?highlight=activities" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Activities</a>
                </p>
                <p>
                Before generating an intermediary invoice in the
                <strong>
                        <font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing</font>
                </strong>
                app, freeze the project status in the
                <strong>
                        <font class="text-o-color-1">Project</font>
                </strong>
                app to get an overview of the progress in terms of:
                </p>
                <ul>
                <li>Time spent on the project.</li>
                <li>Materials purchased.</li>
                <li>Materials sold.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>All these components will give you an accurate overview on the project profitability.</p>
                <p>
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting/customer_invoices.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Invoicing</a>
                </p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs. </p>
                        <p>
                        Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free
                        to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!<br />
                        </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h1>
                <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Do you want to go further? 🚀</strong></span>
                </h1>
                <hr />
                <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as : </p>
                <ul>
                <li>
                        Create a stunning <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">website</font></strong> and start receiving orders directly in Odoo. Go live with your <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">E-shop</font></strong> in a few
                        minutes.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Manage your employees and all your human resources using the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">HR Suite.</font></strong>
                </li>
                <li>
                        Provide an excellent after-sales service using the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Helpdesk App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Follow your equipment status and maintenance with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Maintenance App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)
                </li>
                <li>
                        Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Marketing Automation</font></strong>, <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font></strong>, 
                        <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Social Media Marketing</font></strong>, and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Organise your events and connect with your customers easily with the<strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Events App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                </ul>
                <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
                        <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further? </p>
                        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Reach us</a></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
            <field name="name">Custom Furniture Production</field>
            <field name="icon">🪑</field>
            <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
            <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_13"/>
            <field name="is_locked" eval="1"/>
            <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
            <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
