<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<odoo>
        <template id="welcome_article_body">
            <p><span class="h1-fs"><strong>Mastering Odoo: A Guide to Streamlining Your Carpentry Business</strong></span></p>

            <p>Welcome, carpenters! This guide will help you elevate your custom table business using Odoo, a platform that br/ings together sales, stock, purchases, and customer contacts in one place. Let's dive into Odoo's features and see how to get the most out of each tool step-by-step.</p><div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div><p><br/></p>
            
            <h2>Why Choose Odoo?</h2>
            <p>With Odoo, you can streamline operations like Sales Management, Stock Management, and Purchase Management to save time and improve customer satisfaction. This integrated approach helps you focus more on crafting your products and providing exceptional service.</p>
            
            <h2>Setting Up Odoo for Carpentry Business</h2>
            <p>Here’s a br/eakdown of how to set up and use Odoo to organize and manage your carpentry business effectively:</p><h3>1. Sales Management</h3>
            <p>Begin with the <strong>Sales Management</strong> app to organize and track your sales orders.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Click on the <strong>Sales</strong> app on the dashboard.</li>
                <li>Select <strong>Create</strong> to open a new sale order form.</li>
                <li>Enter customer details and add product specifics, including quantity and price.</li><li>You can chose a quotation template. This will load a Quote Calculator.</li><li class="oe-nested"><ul><li>In this you have a template, where you can set the area of your framework (b9).</li><li>Filling this will automatically adjust the quantity.</li><li>You can also set the margin as you wish!</li><li>Click on Save and the quotation is automatically changed.</li></ul></li><li>After filling in all necessary details, select <strong>Save</strong> to store the sale order.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>2. Inventory Management</h3>
            <p>Efficient inventory management is crucial for tracking materials and finished products. Here’s how to manage your stock:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Access the <strong>Inventory</strong> app.</li>
                <li>Click on <strong>Products</strong> to view current stock levels.</li>
                <li>Adjust quantities as needed by selecting a product and editing stock levels.</li>
                <li>Routinely check inventory to ensure you're prepared to meet customer demand.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>3. Purchase Management</h3>
            <p>Odoo's <strong>Purchases</strong> app allows you to manage material orders efficiently.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Navigate to the <strong>Purchases</strong> app.</li>
                <li>Click <strong>Create</strong> to open a new purchase order.</li>
                <li>Select your supplier, specify materials needed, and complete the order form.</li>
                <li>Finalize by clicking <strong>Confirm</strong> to process the purchase order.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>4. Contact Management</h3>
            <p>Keeping an organized contact list helps maintain customer relationships and supplier connections.</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Go to the <strong>Contacts</strong> app.</li>
                <li>Click <strong>Create</strong> to add a new contact with relevant details.</li>
                <li>Link contacts to their respective sales orders for easy reference.</li><li>From this view you can also add a report. This lets you chose whether you want a simplified invoice or a complete one per customer.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h2>Advanced Tips and Best Practices</h2>
            <p>Optimize your Odoo experience with these additional features:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Custom Products:</strong> Add your custom tables as products in Odoo for smoother order processing.</li>
                <li><strong>Email Templates:</strong> Use templates to enhance customer communication, such as welcoming new clients or thanking them after purchase.</li>
                <li><strong>Analytics:</strong> Review sales analytics regularly to determine popular products and focus on what sells best.</li></ul><h1>Project and Task Automation for Carpentry Services</h1>
            <p>Odoo can automate project and task creation for service-oriented products, which is useful for managing time-based tasks like custom carpentry work. Here’s an overview of what Odoo can automate:</p>
            
            <h3>Projects Based on Templates</h3>
            <p>For products like custom tables or wood frames, Odoo can automatically create a new project based on a pre-defined template upon sale. Key benefits include:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Automatic project creation for new orders.</li>
                <li>Consistency in project structure, tasks, and timesheets.</li>
                <li>Ability to invoice clients based on completion or milestones.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>Tasks in a Global Project</h3>
            <p>For items such as custom desks, tasks can be created within a larger, ongoing project, which allows for:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Task creation upon sale within an existing project framework.</li>
                <li>Tracking time spent on individual tasks through timesheets for billing accuracy.</li>
                <li>Billing upon task or service completion.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>Advantages of Automated Projects and Tasks</h3>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Automation:</strong> Projects and tasks are created without manual input, improving efficiency.</li>
                <li><strong>Standardization:</strong> Pre-defined templates ensure consistent project structure.</li>
                <li><strong>Time Tracking:</strong> Timesheets make it easy to track work hours and bill clients accordingly.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h2>Using Quotation Templates for Roofing Projects</h2>
            <p>Odoo’s quotation templates simplify complex estimates, especially for projects like roofing where material calculations are needed.</p>
            
            <h3>Automatic Material Calculations</h3>
            <p>Using a quotation template, you can set up material requirements based on project dimensions. This feature enables you to:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Calculate exact quantities of materials like tiles, beams, and insulation based on project dimensions.</li>
                <li>Adjust margins on materials directly in the quotation to ensure profitability.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h3>Simplified Quotations</h3>
            <p>For a clean, professional look, Odoo allows you to present a summarized quotation:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Select <strong>Send Simplified Quotation</strong> to hide detailed lines and provide an overview for customers.</li><li>If you wish to change the portal view too you can select in sales settings the "Simplified Quotations</li>
                <li>If using sections, sales order lines will be grouped under each section for better clarity.</li>
                <li>Sections without sales order lines will display only the project name.</li>
            </ul><h3>Simplified Invoices</h3>
            <p>Following the same logic, you can also send simplified invoices. To do so:</p><ul><li>Select <strong>Simplified Invoice</strong>in report in the contact view to hide detailed lines and provide an overview for customers.</li><li>If using sections, sales order lines will be grouped under each section for better clarity.</li></ul><h3>Benefits of Customized Quotations</h3>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Efficiency:</strong> Automated material calculations save time and reduce errors.</li>
                <li><strong>Flexibility:</strong> Adjust margins and create tailored quotations for various project sizes.</li>
                <li><strong>Presentation:</strong> Simplified quotation views help communicate effectively with customers.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h2>Conclusion</h2>
            <p>By using Odoo’s powerful suite of tools, you can manage your carpentry business more effectively and focus on what matters most—your craftsmanship. From sales and inventory management to automated project creation and customized quotations, Odoo empowers you to run a streamlined, professional operation. Embr/ace these tools to grow your business and take on new opportunities with confidence!</p>
</template>
<record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Cake Store</field>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="category">private</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    <field name="icon">🪵</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2"/>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    <field name="body">
        <![CDATA[]]></field>
</record>
</odoo>
