<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1><strong><span class="display-4-fs">Carpenter</span></strong><br/></h1>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">Welcome to the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Odoo Carpenter package</font></strong>!</span><br/></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">This module is designed to simplify daily project management, helping you effortlessly handle customer relationships, prepare construction sites, manage material purchases, and organize your project calendar. The result is improved efficiency and happier customers across all your production services.</span></p>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">​</span><br/></p>
    <h2><span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span></h2>
    <hr/>
    <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
          <p>
            The<strong> <font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">CRM &amp; Sales app</font></strong> Manages all product and service charges for your clients.
          </p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Purchase App</font><font class="text-o-color-1"> </font></strong>ensures accurate inventory replenishment and tracks subcontracting services.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Project App</font></strong> provides a clear overview of every aspect of your project management</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Document and Sign app</font></strong> centralizes your important documents, allowing you to sign them directly within the app.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Invoice App</font></strong> helps you keep track of all your invoices.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Website App</font></strong> acts as a virtual showroom and a powerful tool for generating new leads.</p>
      </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to <b>manage your entire business from your phone</b>.<s><br/></s></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <p>Since Odoo is not a design tool, all necessary drawings must be created in a dedicated drawing program.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p><br/></p>
    <h2><span class="h1-fs"><strong>Activities</strong></span><br/></h2>
    <hr/>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">To get a rapid understanding of the processes this Odoo package offers, you can execute the following flows and configure the settings to suit your library.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Library package and select the relevant checkbox</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage Quotation and Sales Order 🤝</span></h3>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Effectively managing your sales process starts with a good system. By using a <b>CRM (Customer Relationship Management) app</b>, you can easily track contacts, manage communications, and generate professional quotations. The CRM's built-in tools allow you to customize prices for each client, turning generic products into personalized solutions.</p>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><b>Creating a Sales Order from the CRM</b></h3>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Follow these steps to generate a new sales order directly from your CRM app:</p>
    <ol>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Create an Opportunity</b>: Click <b>"Create"</b> to start a new sales opportunity.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Select a Client</b>: Choose an existing customer from your list or add a new one directly into the customer field.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Communicate and Understand Needs</b>: Use the <b>chatter feature</b> to communicate with the client. This helps you clarify their specific requirements for the project.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Generate a Quotation</b>: Once you understand their needs, generate a quotation from the opportunity.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Build the Quote</b>: Select a <b>quotation template</b>, add the required products and any extra services. Use the <b>quote calculator</b> to price each item based on the customer's specifications. The product tabs are organized by their sequence on the sales lines.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Add Project Management</b>: Add the "Carpentry project" service to track the entire quotation within a dedicated project.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Finalize Details</b>: Update the <b>delivery date</b> to ensure deadlines are met and deliveries are scheduled correctly.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Send the Quote</b>: Send the final quotation to the client, making sure to attach any plans from your drawing software.</p>
      </li>
    </ol>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <ul>
            <li>To dive deeper into the quote calculator, feel free to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/fr_FR/event/odoo-experience-2024-4662/track/revolutionizing-sales-quotations-unleashing-the-power-of-the-quote-calculator-6627" class="btn btn-secondary">Learn more</a> about its features and capabilities.</li>
            <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
            <li>Redirect the emails sent to <a href="mailto:info@your-business.com">info@your-business.com</a> to the <strong>CRM</strong>.</li>
            <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
            <li>Use the Website app to create a contact form that will redirect all the requests to the <strong>CRM.</strong></li>
            <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
            <li>Want to make your quotes stand out? Try the <b>PDF quote builder.</b></li>
            <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
            <li>Don't worry, even if your customer changes their plan, all <strong>historical sales orders </strong>are saved in the chatter.<b></b><br/></li>
          </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 CRM &amp; Sales</a> </p>
    <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage your project️ 📏</span></h3>
    <p><br/></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Confirming a quotation automatically creates a dedicated project in the Project app. Each new project comes with several default tasks to get you started.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">The top bar of your project gives you quick access to all essential aspects, such as purchase orders, manufacturing orders, and invoices. You can also create new documents directly from the project app. For example, by clicking the "Purchase" button, you can create a new purchase order that will be automatically linked to your project and factored into its profitability.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">In the Project app, you can:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Drag and drop tasks</b> to different stages for easy tracking.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Record time on specific tasks</b> (like "External Help"), and that time will be used to calculate your project's profitability.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>View a profitability dashboard</b> that gives you a clear overview of your project's financial performance once you've properly configured all costs from timesheets, production, and purchases.<b></b><br/></p>
      </li>
    </ul>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
      <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <ul>
            <li>If your projects are diverse, you can create different project templates to suit your needs.</li>
          </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <p>To avoid double-counting costs and ensure an accurate profitability dashboard, be careful with how you link expenses to your projects.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>If you are manually invoicing for timesheet hours from an external resource, do not also link those hours to the project in your system. This will prevent the costs from being counted twice on your profitability dashboard.</li>
            <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
            <li>When purchasing components for a new product, you can create a purchase order that isn't directly linked to the project. Then, link only the <b>receipt</b> to the project. This gives you a clear overview of your purchases while ensuring the cost is counted just once.</li>
          </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Centralize all the important information 📝</span></h3>
    <p><br/></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Starting a construction project implies a lot of important documents such as contracts, building plans, instructions for use, subcontracting agreements, etc. Instead of scattering them in your emails, storage services or computer, attach them in the chatter and they will be automatically centralized in the <strong>Documents</strong> app.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Speed up the signing process thanks to the <strong>Sign</strong> app. Once again, all the signed documents will be stored in the <strong>Documents</strong> app.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/sign.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Sign</a>    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Document</a></p>
    <h2 style="text-align: justify;"><br/></h2>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Manage purchasing &amp; dropship on site 🛒</span></h3>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Within the <b>Project app</b>, you can use the <b>Purchase</b> button to create all the purchases your project needs. You have the flexibility to deliver products to your production workshop or directly to the customer site using dropshipping. Additionally, if you need to subcontract any activities, you can add service products directly to your purchase lines.</p>
    <div style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h5-fs"><strong>Creating a New Purchase Order</strong></span></div>
    <div style="text-align: justify;"><br/></div>
    <ol>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;">Select the <b>vendor</b> and <b>expected delivery date</b>.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;">Add all the products or services you need to purchase.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;">For direct-to-client delivery, choose <b>dropship delivery</b> and select the customer's address.</p>
      </li>
      <li>
          <p style="text-align: justify;">Once confirmed, a receipt will be automatically generated, ready for you to confirm upon delivery.</p>
      </li>
    </ol>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"> <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase.html">🎓 Purchase</a></p>
    <h2 style="text-align: justify;"><br/></h2>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Manage your stock and production 🔨</span></h3>
    <div><span class="h6-fs"><br/></span></div>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">The <b>Manufacturing and Inventory app</b> is designed to help you manage your in-house production and keep a close eye on the stock levels of your raw materials.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">If you don't need to track inventory but still want to monitor costs, purchases, and production, you can simply <b>disable the tracking option</b> in the product settings.</p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <div><span class="h6-fs">Within the Manufacturing App</span></div>
          <ul>
            <li>Create a <strong>bill of materials (BOM) </strong>for each finished product.</li>
            <li>Set the inventory <strong>route to "Manufacture"</strong> for all manufactured products.</li>
            <li>Use a single generic product entry for <strong>custom finished products, using lots</strong> to distinguish between them.</li>
          </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h5-fs"><strong>Create a Finish product</strong></span></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">To create a finished product, follow these steps:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Generate a Manufacturing Order</b>: Within your project, create a new <b>Manufacturing Order</b>. Add all the necessary components that will be used, whether they are from your current stock or are new costs.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Validate Production</b>: Once you've completed the manufacturing process, validate the order to finalize it.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Create a Delivery Order</b>: Go to the <b>Project App</b> and create a new <b>"From WH" (Warehouse) operation</b>. This acts as a delivery order, listing all the finished products that need to be taken from your stock and delivered to the customer.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Confirm Delivery</b>: Once you validate this operation, the products will be automatically removed from your inventory, and the delivery can be completed.</li>
      <li class="oe-nested">
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
      </li>
    </ul>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
      <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">Optimize Your Inventory<span class="oe-tabs" style="width: 35px;">	</span>​</span></p>
          <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Define Lead Times:</b> Set lead times for all your products to ensure accurate stock planning.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Use the Replenishment Dashboard:</b> Get a clear overview of exactly what you need to order.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Automate Replenishment:</b> Set up reordering rules for key products so you never run out of stock.</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
          <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs">Optimize Your Production</span></p>
          <ul>
            <li class="h6-fs" style="text-align: justify;"><b>Manage By-Products:</b> Use the <b>by-products</b> feature in the Manufacturing app to reuse any remaining product parts after a production run. This lets you track and manage leftover materials that are created during production, reducing waste and improving efficiency.</li>
          </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/manufacturing.html">🎓 Manufacturing</a> <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html">🎓 Inventory</a></span><br/></p>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><br/></h3>
    <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Invoice at the right time</span> 📈</h3>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">As the first invoicing step, create a down payment from the sales order. This will generate the first invoice in the <strong>Invoicing</strong> app. Then, schedule one or several "Invoicing Schedule" activities on the sales order with the aim to never forget to send an intermediary invoice in order to sustain your cash flow.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Before generating an intermediary invoice in the <strong>Invoicing</strong> app, freeze the project status in the <strong>Project</strong> app to get an overview on the progress in terms of:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">Time spent on the project.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">Materials purchased.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">Materials sold.</li>
    </ul>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">All these components will give you an accurate overview on the project profitability.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs"></span><br/></p>
    <h1 style="text-align: justify;">Do you want to go further?</h1>
     <hr/>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Enrich the core apps by installing the following ones.</p>
    <h2 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs"><strong>Efficiently schedule the work </strong></span>📆</h2>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Use the <strong>Planning</strong> app to organize the work of your employees. Define on which project and when they have to work. Easily manage shift conflicts, workload and replacements in case of leaves.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/planning.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Planning</a></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Create an attractive website 🌐</strong></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Increase your visibility and get more leads by creating a beautiful <strong>Website</strong>! When a potential customer sends a request through the contact form, it could automatically create an opportunity in the <strong>CRM</strong> app.</p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html">🎓 Website</a></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Accounting made easy 🧮</strong></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">Use the <strong>Accounting</strong> app to easily handle:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">The customer reminders.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">The vendor bills payment.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">The synchronization with the banks.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;">The financial reporting.</li>
    </ul>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Accounting</a></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h6-fs"><b>Expanding Your Workshop</b></span></p>
    <p style="text-align: justify;">A <b>bigger workshop</b>  provides more space for machinery, materials, and a more efficient layout. This can significantly increase production capacity and improve workflow by reducing clutter and bottlenecks.</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Implement a real-time quality check.</b> You can add quality checks for specific products at critical moments in the manufacturing process. This ensures that any defects are caught early, reducing waste and the cost of rework.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Use a shopfloor app.</b> If you have a growing team, a digital shopfloor app can ensure that every employee receives the right information at the right time. It can provide work instructions, track progress, and facilitate communication, leading to smoother operations and fewer errors.</li>
      <li style="text-align: justify;"><b>Manage product variations efficiently.</b> To handle different versions of a product, such as a table made from various types of wood, you can use a <b>product variant</b> system. This allows you to reuse the same <b>Bill of Materials</b> (BOM) but with minor adjustments for different material types, saving time and preventing errors in inventory management and production planning.</li>
    </ul>
    <p style="text-align: justify;"><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/quality.html">🎓 Quality</a>  <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/manufacturing/shop_floor/shop_floor_overview.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Shopfloor</a>  <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales/products_prices/products/variants.html?highlight=product%20variant">🎓 Variants</a> </p>
    <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
      <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
          <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </template>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Carpenter</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="icon">🔨</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
  </record>
</odoo>
