<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint">
            <span class="display-4-fs"><strong>Odoo for eLearning Platforms</strong></span>
        </h1>
        <p>Building and running an eLearning platform can be complex: you need to create engaging content, attract learners, manage access, and track progress seamlessly.</p>
        <p>
            Odoo brings all of these pieces together in one integrated solution. With powerful apps for course creation, sales, marketing, and student engagement, Odoo empowers you to deliver exceptional learning experiences while keeping
            administration efficient and scalable.
        </p>
        <p>Whether you’re a training company or using eLearning for internal staff development, Odoo makes education management smooth, centralized, and fully connected with your other business processes.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><span class="h1-fs">Basics</span></h2>
        <hr />
        <div><strong>Apps &amp; What They Do:</strong></div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>eLearning</strong>: Build, structure, and publish courses with lessons, quizzes, gamification, and certifications.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website</strong>: Present your training catalog beautifully and provide an easy-to-navigate user experience.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>eCommerce</strong>: Sell your courses online with integrated payments and automated access.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Marketing apps</strong>: Send targeted campaigns to promote courses &amp; connect and engage audiences through multiple social platforms.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every feature of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr />
        <h2>Create and Customize Courses 🎓</h2>
        <p>
            The eLearning app is the foundation of your digital training. It allows you to create courses with multimedia content such as videos, articles, or downloadable materials. Add interactive elements like quizzes, certificates, and
            gamification to boost learner motivation. Assign course managers to keep content up to date and responsive to feedback.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Gamification</strong>: Add leaderboards, badges, and XP points for learner engagement.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Certifications</strong>: Issue completion certificates automatically.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Continuous improvement</strong>: Assign responsible managers to keep content evolving.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website integration</strong>: Courses are published directly on your Odoo website.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/elearning.html" class="btn btn-secondary">eLearning<strong></strong> Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <hr />
        <h2>Sell Courses Online 🛒</h2>
        <p>
            Monetize your courses by publishing them on your Odoo website’s shop. Learners can browse your catalog, purchase a course, and automatically gain access. Internal employees can be granted free access when courses are used for training
            purposes.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Track student progression</strong>: See which modules they’ve completed.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Feedback &amp; reviews</strong>: Collect star ratings and comments.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sales reports</strong>: Monitor revenues and identify popular courses.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Internal use</strong>: Assign courses free of charge for employee onboarding or training.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/ecommerce.html">eCommerce Documentation</a></p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><strong>Tip: </strong>Use pricelists for discounts, gifts, and promotions.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <hr />
        <h2>Promote and Engage Learners 📣</h2>
        <p>Social Marketing integrates platforms like YouTube, LinkedIn, and Instagram into your communication strategy. Schedule posts, track engagement, and stay in touch with your community to boost brand presence and student loyalty.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Targeted email campaigns</strong>: Segment learners by interests or past purchases.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Social scheduling</strong>: Plan posts across multiple platforms.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Engagement analytics</strong>: Measure clicks, open rates, and conversions.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Community building</strong>: Use Odoo’s Forum and Reviews features to stimulate peer-to-peer support.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/marketing/social_marketing.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Social Marketing Documentation</a>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/marketing/email_marketing.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Email Marketing Documentation</a>
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Create Mail Marketing templates, schedule posts for the right hours, and expand your userbase.</p>
                <p><strong>Tip </strong>: Check out Marketing Automation for content funnel optimization.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <hr />
        <p><br/></p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    <strong><span class="h2-fs">Tips for Success</span></strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Gamify your courses: </strong>Add badges and leaderboards to encourage competition and motivation.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><strong>Automate communications: </strong>Set up automated emails for course completion reminders, certificates, or upselling new courses.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested">​<br/></li>
                    <li><strong>Leverage analytics: </strong>Track student progress to identify bottlenecks and adjust course content accordingly.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
                    <li><strong>Engage through social media: </strong>Repurpose snippets of your lessons into posts or teasers to drive traffic back to your platform.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested"><br/></li>
                    <li><strong>Bundle your offers: </strong>Create course packages to increase perceived value and average cart size.<strong></strong><br/></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><br/></h1>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Odoo’s flexibility doesn’t stop at eLearning. Expand your platform with additional apps to cover the full spectrum of your operations:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Knowledge</strong> &amp; <strong>Documents</strong>: Centralize your internal documentation for trainers and staff.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting</strong>: Manage revenues, taxes, and financial reports from course sales.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Surveys</strong>: Gather learner feedback to continuously improve course quality.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Projects</strong>: Organize course development and track future content roadmaps.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Dashboards</strong>: Monitor KPIs like course sales, student engagement, or marketing performance in real time.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>With Odoo, your eLearning platform becomes more than a course library—it becomes a fully integrated digital academy.</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1><br/></h1>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for eLearning</field>
        <field name="icon">🎒</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_10"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
  </odoo>
