<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="product_template_67" model="product.template" context="{'create_product_product': False}">
    <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="elearning_platform/static/src/binary/product_template/67-image_1920"/>
    <field name="name">Furniture Workshop Essentials</field>
    <field name="description_sale"><![CDATA[Turn your ideas into beautiful, functional furniture.]]></field>
    <field name="type">service</field>
    <field name="list_price">99.99</field>
    <field name="service_tracking">course</field>
    <field name="purchase_ok" eval="False"/>
    <field name="service_type">manual</field>
    <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
    <field name="description_ecommerce"><![CDATA[<p>Discover the craftsmanship behind beautiful, functional furniture with <em>Furniture Workshop Essentials</em>. This course takes you step by step through the fundamentals of woodworking and furniture-making—from understanding materials and tools to mastering joints, finishes, and design basics.</p>
<p>With <strong>lifetime access</strong>, you’ll have the freedom to learn at your own pace and revisit techniques whenever you need a refresher. Whether you dream of building your first chair or refining your workshop skills, this course gives you the solid foundation to create pieces that last.</p>
<p>✨ <strong>What you’ll get:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p>Unlimited lifetime access to all lessons and resources</p></li>
<li><p>Hands-on demonstrations of core woodworking techniques</p></li>
<li><p>Guidance on tools, safety, and workshop setup</p></li>
<li><p>Practical projects to apply your skills</p></li>
</ul>
<p>Build confidence. Build furniture. Build your future. 🪚</p>]]></field>
    <field name="website_sequence">10230</field>
  </record>
  <record id="product_template_73" model="product.template" context="{'create_product_product': False}">
    <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="elearning_platform/static/src/binary/product_template/73-image_1920"/>
    <field name="name">Intro to IT</field>
    <field name="description_sale"><![CDATA[Your first step into the world of IT]]></field>
    <field name="type">service</field>
    <field name="list_price">99.99</field>
    <field name="service_tracking">course</field>
    <field name="purchase_ok" eval="False"/>
    <field name="service_type">manual</field>
    <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
    <field name="description_ecommerce"><![CDATA[<p>Step into the world of technology with <em>Intro to IT</em>, a beginner-friendly course designed to demystify computers, networks, and digital systems. From hardware basics and operating systems to software applications and online security, you’ll gain the essential knowledge to feel confident in today’s tech-driven world.</p>
<p>With <strong>lifetime access</strong>, you can revisit topics anytime, refresh your understanding, and keep growing as technology evolves. Whether for personal growth or professional development, this course lays the groundwork for your IT journey.</p>
<p>✨ <strong>What you’ll get:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><p>Complete lifetime access to all modules and updates</p></li>
<li><p>Clear explanations of core IT concepts</p></li>
<li><p>Practical exercises for real-world understanding</p></li>
<li><p>A solid foundation to branch into more advanced IT studies</p></li>
</ul>
<p>Your gateway to the digital world starts here. 💻</p>]]></field>
    <field name="website_ribbon_id" ref="website_sale.new_ribbon"/>
  </record>
  <record id="website_sale_slides.default_product_course_product_template" model="product.template" context="{'create_product_product': False}" forcecreate="0">
    <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="elearning_platform/static/src/binary/product_template/66-image_1920"/>
    <field name="name">Gardening from A to Z</field>
    <field name="description_sale"><![CDATA[Your Complete Gardening Guide, for Life]]></field>
    <field name="type">service</field>
    <field name="service_tracking">course</field>
    <field name="categ_id" ref="product.product_category_services"/>
    <field name="list_price">99.99</field>
    <field name="service_type">manual</field>
    <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
    <field name="description_ecommerce"><![CDATA[<p data-oe-version="2.0"><strong>Gardening from A to Z – Lifetime Course Access</strong></p><p>Unlock the secrets of gardening with <em>Gardening from A to Z</em>, your all-in-one guide to cultivating a thriving garden. This comprehensive course covers everything—from soil preparation and planting techniques to pest control, seasonal care, and advanced tips for sustainable growth.</p><p>With <strong>lifetime access</strong>, you’ll be able to learn at your own pace, revisit lessons whenever you need, and grow your knowledge year after year. Whether you’re a complete beginner or looking to refine your green thumb, this course will equip you with the skills and confidence to turn any space into a flourishing garden.</p><p>✨ <strong>What you’ll get:</strong></p><ul>
<li><p>Full, unlimited access to all course materials—forever</p></li>
<li><p>Step-by-step lessons covering the entire gardening journey</p></li>
<li><p>Expert tips, practical examples, and easy-to-apply techniques</p></li>
<li><p>Flexible learning: study anytime, anywhere</p></li>
</ul><p>Grow your passion into mastery. 🌱</p>]]></field>
  </record>
</odoo>
