<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body" >
        <h1 style="font-size: 54px;">Odoo for Microbrewery</h1>
<p>Hello there! </p>
<p>You just installed the Odoo for Microbrewery package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your Microbrewery efficiently. </p>
<p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
        <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Use Case.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h1><strong>Basics</strong></h1>
<hr/>
<p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
<ul>
    <li>Crafting Beer - Using mainly the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Manufacture App</strong></font></li>
    <li>Outside Sales (B2B - Bar &amp; Retail) - Using the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong></li>
    <li>Visit of the Brewery (B2C) - Managed via the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Appointment App</font></strong></li>
    <li>Bar &amp; Shop at the Brewery (B2C) - Using the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sales App</font></strong></li>
    <li><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Ecommerce</font></strong> (B2C)</li>
</ul>
<p>This article will guide you through the business flows of a Microbrewery to see how Odoo can support all these critical activities for a microbrewery to help people so they can be efficient and spend more time on what matters.</p>
<p> <br/></p>
<h1><strong>Use case</strong></h1>
 <hr/>
<p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a bunch of interesting presets to ensure you can easily execute the following use case.</p>
<p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
<p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
<div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
    <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
        <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Microbrewery package and check the related box. </p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h2><strong>Crafting 📦</strong></h2>
 <hr/>
<h3>Create a recipe</h3>
<p>In the manufacturing application, you can create a bill of materials to define how the beer should be crafted. </p>
<ol>
    <li><strong>Indicate what will be the finished product </strong>at the end of your recipe and the quantity that should be produced with the recipe. for example:</li>
    <li class="oe-nested">
        <ul>
            <li>Beer bottle (33cl), 3000 units (+- 10hL)</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li>Then <strong>create and add the components </strong>you need, the quantity required and you can also indicate in which operation it will be consumed, for example:</li>
    <li class="oe-nested">
        <ul>
            <li>Water - Good, no inventory tracking - Mashing</li>
            <li>Malt - Goods, inventory tracking by lot. <br/></li>
            <li>Hops - Goods, inventory tracking by lot.</li>
            <li>Yeast - Goods, inventory tracking by lot.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li><strong>Create and add the By-product</strong>s, for example:Spent Grain</li>
    <li class="oe-nested">
        <ul>
            <li>Spent Grain</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li><strong>Create the operations</strong> of your recipe with the right work center, for example:</li>
    <li class="oe-nested">
        <ul>
            <li>Mashing - Work center: Mash tun</li>
            <li>Lautering - Work center: Lauter tun</li>
            <li>Boiling - Work center: Kettle</li>
            <li>Fermenting - Work center: Fermentation Vessel</li>
            <li>Filtering - Work center: Fermentation Vessel</li>
            <li>Bottling - Work center: Bottler</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li><strong>Indicate if there are instructions</strong> the operator should do during some operation, for example:</li>
    <li class="oe-nested">
        <ul>
            <li>Register the quantity of spent grain produced at the end of the lautering.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
</ol>
<p>Now that the recipe is ready, you can create a manufacturing order but you will see that if you don't have the components to create your beer, you will need to purchase the required components.</p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3">
        <p>It is interesting to mention that a lot of microbreweries do not have the machines for the kegging but it is possible to create a separate bill of Materials with the type subcontracting, if the bottling is made externally.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h3>Purchase and receive components</h3>
<p>Go into the purchase application and create a new purchase order with all the components you need to execute your recipe. Make sure you buy enough quantity of each components and validate the order.</p>
<p>Once it is confirmed a delivery order should have been created meaning you are waiting for the vendor to deliver the goods.</p>
<p>Go on the delivery order and indicate the quantity you received and create the lot numbers for each components.</p>
<p>Validate the delivery and check your inventory, now you have everything </p>
<p> <br/></p>
<h3>Start brewing</h3>
<p>Now that you have all the components required to craft the beer, let's start brewing beer. In the manufacturing application, create a new manufacturing order for the bill of materials you made for your recipe.</p>
<p>Then, from the "Shop Floor" application, execute the different operations and follow the instruction as you were the operator.</p>
<p>Once you finished all the operations, you should now be ready to sell your crafted beer.</p>
<p> <br/></p>
<h3 class="">Products and Bills of Material</h3>
<p>There are two ways to handle your products and bills of material, each coming with pros and cons.</p>
<h5>Kits only / Inventory in bottles</h5>
<p>The kit defines the assembly of beer bottles and a crate into a beer box.</p>
<p>We setup an example of this setup with the blond beer bottle and box products in this module.</p>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <ul><li>The inventory is driven by beer bottles.</li><li>The bottled beer is directly the finished product and no semi-finished bottle product is required.</li></ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <ul><li>When moving boxes from a place to another using box product, in practice, beer bottles and deposits are moved (see corresponding deliveries).</li><li>The count on beer boxes is informative only since boxes are considered available as soon as the components, beer bottles and crate, are available.</li></ul>
    </div>
</div>
<h5 class="">Automated manufacturing orders / Inventory in crates</h5>
<p>Automated manufacturing order bill of materials define how semi-finished bottles are packaged into boxes and how boxes can be split into beer bottles.</p>
<p>We setup an example of this setup with the lager and brown beer bottle and box products in this module.</p>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <ul><li>The inventory is driven by beer boxes.</li><li>Deliveries of beer boxes are clear.</li><li>The split of beer box into beer bottles a the bar is clear.</li></ul>
    </div>
</div>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <ul><li>A semi-finished beer bottle unit product is required to be packaged into boxes, which in practice the same as the as the finished product beer bottle, the last one being here to support the split use case at the bar.</li><li>Two bills of material are needed.</li></ul>
    </div>
</div>
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false" contenteditable="true">
        <p>If you want to automatically split products sold in a specific packaging such as beer boxes, precise a unit sale product in the so-called field and the number of units contained.</p>
        <p>This will automatically create a Bill of Material and process a Manufacture Order each time you need to split your product and reflect this operation in your stock perfectly.</p>
        <p>For example:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Bown Beer - Box in 24x33cl is your main product</li>
            <li>Bown Beer - Bottle in 33cl is the unit sale product</li>
            <li>Crate &amp; Bottles 24x33cl is the complete deposit product (deposits of all bottles and crate)</li>
            <li>Crate 24x33cl is the empty deposit product</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Every time you need to sell a single Bown Beer - Bottle, if you don't have enough in stock, it will split a Bown Beer - Box, when you have some in stock, in 24 units and take into account an extra empty bin that will be left at the end.</p>
        <p>The inventory of all products will be updated accordingly.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<h5>With or without crate inventory?</h5>
<p>The described setup accounts for the inventory management of crates.</p>
<p>It is however possible to neglect this by:</p>
<ul><li>removing the deposit products from the bill of materials</li><li>removing the tracking of deposit products (in the product form</li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<h2><strong>Selling 💸</strong></h2>
 <hr/>
<h3><strong><span class="h3-fs">Sell your products and deliver it to a bar</span></strong></h3>
<p>By default the "Contact us" page of the website will send you an email, but you can edit the page and change the behavior of the submit button to create a lead into the CRM application instead.</p>
<p>Now you can generate a new lead by submitting the form and go into the CRM application to find this new lead. As the salesperson in charge of this lead, you can exchange email with the customer directly with the chatter and finally you can schedule a meeting with him. </p>
<p>After (or during) the meeting, you can use the button "New Quotation" to create an offer for the customer. Once it is done, send it to the customer.</p>
<p>You can then use the "Preview" button on the offer to see the result and accept it as if you were the customer!</p>
<p>Now if you go back on the quotation in the Sales application, you will see that it is now a confirmed order and a delivery order has been created. Go on that delivery order and validate it.  </p>
<p>You can now finalize the flow by creating the invoice. </p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3">
        <p data-o-mail-quote="1" data-o-mail-quote-node="1">From the Sales application, you can create standardized offer to make the creation of offers more efficient. For example you can have a template with all your beers already in it. You can also create pricelists that you can assign on your customers too;</p>
    </div>
</div>
<h3> <br/></h3>
<h3><span class="h3-fs"><strong>Visit the website and make an order.</strong></span></h3>
<p>From the website application, you can access the Navigate on the page "Shop". You will see that your products may not be published yet. Click on a product to land on the product page, customize it then publish it so visitors can start ordering it.</p>
<p>Add products in your cart and pay using the payment method "Demo" which is a fake payment method you can use to test flows.</p>
<p>Ecommerce can be used to create a brand that is more than a beer. You can use it to do "cross-selling" by adding some merchandising products (t-shirt, sweet shirt, beer glass, ...) that will be bought by your fans that will become your ambassadors.</p>
<p> <br/></p>
<h3><span class="h3-fs"><strong>Analyse your sales.</strong></span></h3>
<p>On top of all the reporting you can find in the different applications, you can consult the dashboard application to follow the volume of Sales you have made.</p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3">
        <p>If you need to declare your <strong>periodic sales in a consolidated volume</strong>, ensure your unit of measure and products are correctly configured and use the Pivot Table in Sales App &gt; Reporting &gt; Sales. </p>
        <p>You can configure a monthly sales overview using the "Volume" Measure, selecting "Product categories" in X axis and "Order date &gt; Month" in Y axis.</p>
        <p>Want to know more about unit of measures ?</p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary flat" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/product_management/configure/uom.html?highlight=unit%20measure">🎓 Units of measure</a></p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h3><strong><span class="h3-fs">Rental</span></strong></h3>
<p>If you want to rent Beer Taps to your customer, you can explore the rental App and discover how you can manage your rental schedule easily and provide a great extended service to your customers.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<h2><strong>Visiting the Brewery 🎫</strong></h2>
<hr/>
<h3><strong><span class="h3-fs">Schedule a visit from the website.</span></strong> <br/></h3>
<p>In the Appointment app, you can create an agenda for the visits of the brewery. You can mention which employee will do the visit and you can ask an upcoming payment to book and link the product "Visit of the brewery". Once everything is fine, you can publish it and then hit the button "Go to Website" to see the website page where future visitors can book online a visit of the brewery.</p>
<p>You can pick a time and pay to finalize the booking.</p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3">
        <p>The appointment app can also be used to share your availability with a customer or a vendor if you want him to book a meeting with you.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1"> <br/></p>
<h3><span class="h3-fs"><strong>Take an order at the Bar</strong></span> <br/></h3>
<p>After the visit, it is always great for visitors to be able to share a moment around the good beer. Go into the "Point Of Sales" application and create a product to sell in your bar/restaurant (e.g. Draft beer, snack, ...).</p>
<p>Now go back in the "Point of Sales" dashboard and start a Session of the bar (or restaurant), indicate how much cash you have when opening the bar. An now you are ready to take an order.</p>
<p>Select a table (inside or outside), then select the ordered products and confirm the order. </p>
<p>At any time you can select a table and register the payment to close the table.</p>
<div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
    <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3">
        <p>It could also be interesting for your customer to buy souvenirs, gifts or simply some pack of beers after the visit. You can have both a bar/restaurant and a shop or you can manage both from the same </p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h2>Deposit Management ♻️</h2><hr/>
<p>Manage your deposit more precisely and efficiently than ever before.</p>
<h3>Deposit assignation</h3>
<ul>
    <li>Create deposit products for each different type of consignments and assign them a category with "Is a deposit category" set like the Deposit category.</li>
    <li>Set a deposit product on your product to apply deposit taxes. This will ensure that you invoice correctly the price of consignments.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Deposit return from customers</h3>
<ul>
    <li>Collect deposits when you deliver to your customer. It is easy. When validating your delivery, you can directly set a "Return" and precisely count the number of each type of deposit your customer gave you. It will automatically be reflected on his invoice or issue a credit note.</li>
    <li>You can also collect deposits directly on your Point of Sale. Select the correct product and encode a negative quantity.</li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
        <p>The automated crate split based on BoM (defined from crate products with "contains" fields) is not supported from the bar (PoS).</p>
        <p>As workarounds, you might:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Rely on the kit setup mentioned in the "Products and Bills of Material" section.</li>
            <li>Manually convert crates into unit bottles at the bar on reception.</li>
        </ul>
    </div>
</div>
<p>&#xFEFF;<a href="https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/19.0/deposit_management" class="btn-sm btn btn-outline-primary">&#xFEFF;🎓 Deposit Management&#xFEFF;</a>&#xFEFF;</p>
<p><br/></p>
<h2>Excise Management 🧾</h2>
<hr/>
<p>In case you import or purchase products for which excises need to be recorded, you can handle it with this package.</p>
<p>Excise management consists in two dimensions in this package:</p>
<ul>
    <li>The maintenance of excise categories and the assignation of excises to products</li>
    <li>The reporting of received and delivered excise concerned products, a legal implication for any fiscal deposit</li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false" contenteditable="true">
        <p>When installing this module, all Fiscal Positions are set as Fiscal Deposit.<br/>Adjust the Fiscal Positions which are not to consider the Excise Taxes in your orders.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<h3>Excise categories maintenance</h3>
<p>From the <strong>Inventory app</strong>, open the Excise categories from the menu Configuration / Excise Categories. <br/>Here you can define new and maintain existing excise categories.</p>
<p>Imagine you create a new category of products which need excise management...</p>
<ul>
    <li>Create a new excise category defining its name, description and reporting unit following the legislation which applies.</li>
</ul>
<p>Then create your product: </p>
<ul>
    <li>Define the required product fields. </li>
    <li>Assign the relevant excise category, input the Excise Amount and the Excise Quantity in the reporting unit and then save your product.</li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>When you sell this product, the excise is accounted separately in a tax and summarised at the end of your sale orders, allowing you to offer clear discounts on your product irrespectively of the excise.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<h3>Excise reports</h3>
<p>On a regular basis, excises need to be declared. To support you with this duty, a report generated weekly provides the quantity by excise category entering and exiting your fiscal deposit warehouse with a dedicated activity for it.</p>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>The assignee of the excise reporting activities can be set from the Inventory settings.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<ul>
    <li>
        <p>Open the <strong>Inventory app</strong> and reach the Excise Reports from the Reporting menu.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Entry from FD corresponds to products entering you fiscal deposit warehouse from the fiscal deposit of a supplier. To define such suppliers, adapt their fiscal position to handle excise tax.</li>
            <li>Exit to FD refers to products exiting your fiscal deposit warehouse to the fiscal deposit of a customer. To define such customers, adapt their fiscal position to handle excise tax.</li>
            <li>Exit means that products exited your fiscal deposit, to another warehouse of your or through a delivery to a customer without fiscal deposit warehouse.</li>
            <li>Entry is here in case you purchase products or are returned products not from a fiscal deposit warehouse. In such case, you ask for excise credits with your excise declaration.</li>
            <li>Transfer is here to handle the transfers between multiple fiscal deposit warehouses of yours.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Receipts and Deliveries from and to Partners having no Fiscal Position defined are handled with the product taxes.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p>Remember that only stock moves to or from your fiscal deposit warehouses are reported here.</p>
<p>This is normal not to see any move related to a sale from a front store warehouse since it is not a fiscal deposit for example</p>
<h3>Excise reporting</h3>
<p>On top of the legal reporting, you need as well to know at all time the quantity of excise submitted products in your fiscal deposit warehouses.</p>
<ul>
    <li>Open the <strong>Inventory app</strong> and reach the Excise Reports from the Reporting menu.</li>
    <li>Rows come with the same move types detailed as the Excise Reports.</li>
    <li>The Total row allows you to capture your currently in fiscal deposit warehouse product quantity!</li>
</ul>
<p>You now have the keys to easily report those to the relevant authorities!</p>
<p><a href="https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/19.0/excise_management" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" target="_blank">🎓 Excise Management</a></p>
<p><br/></p>
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
    <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false" contenteditable="true">
        <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs. </p>
        <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/fr_FR/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help! <br/></p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
<h1><span class="h1-fs">Do you want to go further?</span></h1>
<hr/>
<p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as : </p>
<ul>
    <li>Manage Internal Projects and research and development in the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Project App</font></strong>.</li>
    <li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)</li>
    <li>Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Marketing Automation</font></strong>, <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font></strong>, <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Social Media Marketing</font></strong>, and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing</font></strong>.</li>
    <li>Organise your events and connect with your customers easily with the<strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Events App</font></strong>.</li>
</ul>
<p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
<p> <br/></p>
<div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
    <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
        <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further? </p>
        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
    </div>
</div>
<p> <br/></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Microbrewery</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">🍺</field>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
