<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo auto_sequence="1">
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="2.0">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>Odoo for Summer Camps</strong>
            </span>
        </h1>
        <p>Running a summer camp involves more than just fun and games—it requires seamless organization, clear communication, and reliable data tracking. Odoo empowers summer camp organizers with an all-in-one platform to manage registrations, payments, attendee records, logistics, communications, and post-camp feedback, all from one integrated system.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Basics</span>
        </h2>
        <hr/>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website 🌐 :</strong>Showcase your camps online with dedicated pages, integrated registration, mobile-friendly design, and secure payment—all from a visually engaging and parent-friendly website.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Events 🏨 :</strong>Create and manage every camp session with custom forms, pricing, capacity, tags, attendee tracking, automated emails, and a live check-in desk—all in one central app.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Projects 📋 :</strong>Organize the behind-the-scenes work of each camp using task lists, deadlines, assignments, and logistics tracking to ensure smooth preparation and coordination.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Appointments 📅 :</strong>Let families book meetings to discuss camp options, sync your team’s calendars, and reduce no-shows with automatic reminders and structured scheduling.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>CRM 🎯 :</strong>Capture inquiries from your website, organize and qualify leads in a visual pipeline, assign sales tasks, and convert interest into bookings with quotations and notes tracking.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sign ✍️ :</strong>Collect parental consent securely with reusable digital signature templates, embedded links in confirmation emails, and centralized access to signed documents.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <hr/>
        <h2>
            <strong>Website 🌐</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>The <strong>Website</strong> app allows you to showcase your summer camps in a visually appealing and informative way. It serves as the entry point for parents and guardians to discover camp offerings, explore details, and register children directly online.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create dedicated summer camp pages</strong> with detailed information, schedules, and visuals.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Integrated "Register Now" buttons</strong> link to event registration.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Mobile-friendly experience</strong> ensures easy booking from any device.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Built-in payment integration</strong> allows smooth and secure transactions.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <hr/>
        <h2>
            <strong>Events 🏨</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>The <strong>Events</strong> app is the heart of summer camp management. It provides tools to create, customize, and manage all aspects of each camp session.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Odoo helps you:</strong>
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Design and publish summer camp listings using <strong>event templates</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>tags</strong> to categorize camps by duration, activities, lodging type, or meal plans.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Define <strong>pricing, early bird discounts, and capacity limits</strong> per ticket type.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Configure <strong>custom registration forms</strong> to gather camper details, medical info, dietary restrictions, and more.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Automate <strong>confirmation emails, reminders, and follow-up communications</strong>.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Configure <strong>Email Templates</strong> to attach<strong>packing lists</strong> and consent forms as PDFs or shared links.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Access real-time data like <strong>registration numbers, revenue per camp</strong>, and detailed attendee info.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>Registration Desk view</strong> to check campers in upon arrival.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-08-07 at 14.25.50@2x.png" src="/web/image/summer_camps.ir_attachment_1131"/>
        </p>
        <hr/>
        <h2>
            <strong>Projects 📋</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>The <strong>Projects</strong> app helps with behind-the-scenes preparation and operational planning.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Break down camp preparation into <strong>task lists</strong>: material preparation, staff assignments, pre-camp checklists.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign responsibilities to team members and <strong>track deadlines</strong>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Manage <strong>equipment logistics</strong>, staff planning, and on-site activity coordination.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-08-07 at 14.28.34@2x.png" src="/web/image/summer_camps.ir_attachment_1132"/>
        </p>
        <hr/>
        <h2>
            <strong>Appointments 📅</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>The <strong>Appointments</strong> app makes it easy for families to connect with your team before committing to a camp. Whether they want to ask questions, discuss special needs, or find the best fit for their child, this tool helps you offer personalized service—without the back-and-forth of scheduling emails.</p>
        <p>With just a few clicks, parents can book a call or in-person meeting directly from your website or email campaigns. You and your colleagues stay organized, avoid double-bookings, and ensure every camper is matched with the right experience.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Let customers self-schedule</strong> discovery calls or info sessions at a time that suits them.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sync with Google or Outlook calendars</strong> to prevent conflicts and stay updated.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Automated email and SMS reminders</strong> reduce no-shows and keep everyone informed.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Assign different team members or time slots to specific <strong>camp types or age groups</strong> for optimized scheduling.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>The result? Better service, more trust, and a smoother registration journey.</p>
        <hr/>
        <h3>
            <strong>CRM 🎯</strong>
        </h3>
        <p>The <strong>CRM</strong> app helps you manage every inquiry that comes through your website's contact form—turning initial interest into confirmed registrations. Whether it's a parent asking for more info, a school proposing a group booking, or a returning family inquiring about availability, the CRM keeps your sales pipeline organized and actionable.</p>
        <p>From the moment a lead is captured, you can qualify, follow up, and guide them through the booking process with clarity and ease.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Capture inquiries automatically</strong> from your website's contact forms.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Organize opportunities by stage</strong> (e.g., New, Contacted, Quotation Sent, Confirmed) using a visual kanban pipeline.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Add custom tags</strong> like “IT Camp,” “Group Booking,” or “Special Needs” to filter and segment leads.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Schedule meetings or calls</strong> directly from the CRM and sync with your calendar.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Take notes, log calls, and attach documents</strong> on the opportunity record to centralize communication.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Assign opportunities to the right team members</strong> based on region, language, or camp type.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create quotations</strong> directly from the CRM when the lead is ready to book, linking seamlessly with the Sales app.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>With Odoo CRM, you stay on top of every conversation and never let a potential camper slip through the cracks.</p>
        <hr/>
        <h2>
            <strong>Sign ✍️</strong>
        </h2>
        <p>The <strong>Sign</strong> app allows you to collect parental authorizations quickly and securely through digital signatures. It's a reliable way to ensure compliance while minimizing paperwork.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Configure consent forms</strong> as reusable <strong>Sign document templates</strong> for different camps.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Drag and drop signature, text, and date fields</strong> to collect all necessary information (e.g., emergency contact, medical permissions).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Generate a public share link</strong> for each template that can be reused.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Insert the share link directly into your confirmation emails</strong> so parents can sign the document easily before arrival.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-08-07 at 14.21.46@2x.png" src="/web/image/summer_camps.ir_attachment_1127"/>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can easily edit your email templates. Enter "/" to access special styling features, such as buttons, tables, bold, italics, links, and so on.</p>
                <p>In the following examples, we used the "/buttons" function, and inserted the shared Consent Form document from the Sign app.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-08-07 at 14.22.18@2x.png" src="/web/image/summer_camps.ir_attachment_1128"/>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>The bottom of the Email template contains an "Attachments" section. Here, you can add files to send automatically with the template, such as a packing list, more information, etc.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" data-file-name="CleanShot 2025-08-07 at 14.23.51@2x.png" src="/web/image/summer_camps.ir_attachment_1130" style="width: 50%;" data-mimetype-before-conversion="image/png" data-x="23.232165404040405" data-y="19.74258207070707" data-width="930.412563131313" data-height="229.17045454545453" data-scale-x="1" data-scale-y="1" data-mimetype="image/png"/>
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Note : you can create as many email templates as you want, and associate them all to the desired events.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>
                    <strong>
                        <span class="h2-fs">Tips for Success</span>
                    </strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Use <strong>event templates</strong> for recurring camp formats to save time.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Group attendees by <strong>tags or registration form answers</strong> to tailor communications.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Track real-time performance via the <strong>Events dashboard</strong>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Visit our E-Learning platform </strong>on <strong><a href="http://Odoo.com/slides">Odoo.com/slides</a></strong>
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><strong>Experiment ! </strong>Did you know you can create a copy of your database to try things out ? Simply go to <a href="http://Odoo.com">Odoo.com</a>, go to My Databases, then click the <strong>gear icon </strong>to duplicate your database.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr/>
        <p>Enhance your summer camp management with these additional Odoo apps:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Email Marketing 🌟</strong>: Promote upcoming camps or send follow-ups post-camp.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Social Marketing 💊</strong>: Share updates and stories across social media platforms.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Survey 📊</strong>: Collect feedback from parents and campers to improve future sessions.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting 📈</strong>: Handle invoicing, revenue tracking, and full financial reporting in one place.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>With Odoo, managing your summer camp becomes easier, more professional, and better connected. Ready to take your camp operations to the next level? Let’s build something great together.</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p>
                    <a class="btn btn-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br/>
        </p>
        <h1>
            <br/>
        </h1>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Summer Camps</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="icon">🏕️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_10"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">69.46171874999999</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
