<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo auto_sequence="1">
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 data-oe-version="2.0">
            <span style="font-size: 40px;"><strong>Odoo for Cosmetics Store</strong></span>
        </h1>
        <h1 data-heading-link-id="1358620764821">
            <span style="font-size: 14px;">
                Welcome to the <font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);"><strong>Odoo Cosmetics Shop package</strong></font>!
            </span>
            <span style="font-size: 40px;"><strong></strong></span><span style="font-size: 14px;"><br /></span>
        </h1>
        <p>
            This set of applications is designed for beauty businesses of all sizes; whether you're running a retail boutique, managing a skincare brand, or selling makeup online. Odoo helps you manage everything in one place: sales, inventory,
            eCommerce, purchases, and customer loyalty.
        </p>
        <p>With connected tools like Point of Sale, Sales, Website, Inventory, and CRM, you can streamline daily operations and spend more time on product innovation and customer experience.</p>
        <p>Let Odoo handle the backend, so you can focus on making beauty your business.💄</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="1263400253671">
            <span style="font-size: 30px;"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Point of Sale app</font></strong> enables in-store sales of skincare, makeup, and beauty tools using a barcode or touch-screen interface.
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Website &amp; eCommerce app</font></strong> supports online sales of cosmetic products through a brand-focused website.
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Sales app</font></strong> manages wholesale and custom client orders, including the creation of professional quotations.
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Purchase app</font></strong> handles the restocking of ingredients, packaging, and finished goods from preferred suppliers.
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Inventory app</font></strong> tracks cosmetic stock levels in real time and automates reordering processes.
            </li>
            <li>
                The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Invoicing app</font></strong> automates customer billing and manages payments, refunds, and credit notes.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage your entire business in it.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="1150241908609">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>
                    <font class="text-800"><span style="font-size: 30px;">Use Case</span></font>
                </strong>
            </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Cosmetics Shop package and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="897003540407">Manage Sales and Payments in Point of Sale</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Manage in-store transactions for skincare, makeup, or beauty tools with the <strong>Point of Sale app</strong>.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the <strong>Point of Sale App</strong> and start a session by clicking on your register.</li>
            <li>Add products to the cart by scanning barcodes or searching manually, and manage cosmetics with product variants (e.g. shade, size, scent) to offer customers personalized options and accurate stock tracking.</li>
            <li>Proceed to payment by using the selected method: cash, card, or on the Customer Account if the client pays later.</li>
            <li>Inventory levels update automatically after each sale.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    <strong>Configure Optional Products</strong>: Suggest complementary items such as adding a body cream as an optional product to a scrub for a complete body care routine. These suggestions appear during checkout to encourage
                    upselling.
                </p>
                <p>Offer €50 gift cards that can be purchased and redeemed on any product—ideal for special occasions. Set this up in <strong>Gift Cards &amp; eWallet.</strong></p>
                <p>Reward loyal customers with points by enabling a loyalty program in <strong>Discount &amp; Loyalty</strong>. For example, give 1 point per €1 spent and offer €5 off at 100 points.</p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Link the Sale to a Customer</strong>: On the PoS screen, select a customer before finalizing the sale. This ensures any loyalty program or customer-specific rewards are correctly applied and tracked.<strong></strong>
                    <br />
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1137973009678">Grow your business with e-commerce</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Sell cosmetics and skincare products online using the <strong>Website and eCommerce apps</strong>, providing a seamless digital shopping experience for customers.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Configure the website to showcase your brand story, product origins, and beauty philosophy with a clean, attractive layout that builds trust and connects with your audience.</li>
            <li>Organize products by categories (e.g., skincare, makeup, body care) to help customers easily find what they need.</li>
            <li>Add detailed eCommerce descriptions for each product, on the product form, to explain ingredients, benefits, and how to use them effectively.</li>
            <li>Set up payment and delivery options allowing customers to choose between home delivery or in-store pickup, with secure payment gateways for trusted transactions.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Add <strong>alternative product</strong>s to display below the main product on the eCommerce page. For example, if a customer buys shampoo, show the conditioner as a complementary product to encourage a complete routine
                    purchase.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Offer automatic discounts to professional clients who buy in bulk. Go to <strong>Sales &gt; Configuration &gt; Pricelists</strong>, create one (e.g., <em>“Reseller Bulk Pricing”</em>), and add rules like 10% off for 20+ units.
                    Assign the pricelist to reseller contacts—discounts apply automatically on their sales orders.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="1625318886569">Manage Purchase Orders</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Streamline purchasing of cosmetics and packaging materials to keep your business supplied efficiently.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Create a <strong>Purchase Order</strong> in the <strong>Purchase app</strong> when you need to buy products such as skincare items, makeup, or packaging supplies.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Choose the best vendor by comparing prices, delivery times, and supplier reliability to secure favorable purchasing terms.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Confirm the Purchase Order and send a <strong>Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> via email to suppliers or manually confirm the order when ready.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Upon receiving the shipment, use the <strong>Receipt</strong> smart button to validate the incoming goods and update your purchase records accordingly.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="201125290265">Inventory &amp; Stock Replenishment</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>Use the <strong>Inventory app</strong> to track cosmetic products and packaging materials in real-time and maintain optimal stock levels.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the <strong>Inventory app</strong> and select the product you want to manage (e.g., facial serum, body lotion).</li>
            <li>Monitor stock quantities across different warehouse locations or stores to ensure availability.</li>
            <li>Use <strong>Smart Buttons</strong> on the product page to view stock moves.</li>
            <li>
                Set <strong>Reordering Rules</strong> by defining minimum and maximum stock levels to automate replenishment. Example: For a solid shampoo, set the minimum stock at 5 units and maximum at 15 units to trigger automatic
                reordering when stock falls below 5.
            </li>
            <li>When stock drops below the minimum threshold, Odoo automatically generates a Purchase Order based on these rules to avoid stockouts.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Add <strong>vendor lead times</strong> on each product to anticipate delivery delays and plan procurement accordingly (e.g., 7-day lead time for imported skincare products).</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3 data-heading-link-id="201125290265">Workflow Example</h3>
        <hr />
        <ol>
            <li>Sell a facial serum in-store using the <strong>Point of Sale (PoS) app</strong>, selecting the desired scent or size, and suggest complementary products like a moisturizer.</li>
            <li>Showcase your products nicely on your website with detailed descriptions and ingredient info, then handle incoming orders through the <strong>Website &amp; eCommerce apps</strong>.</li>
            <li>Create a Purchase Order in the <strong>Purchase app</strong> to restock popular items based on sales trends.</li>
            <li>Receive the shipment and validate it in the <strong>Inventory app</strong> to update stock levels automatically.</li>
            <li>When stock falls below your set minimum, Odoo automatically triggers reorder based on your reordering rules.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>
                    Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2 data-heading-link-id="927821145389">
            <span style="font-size: 30px;"><strong>Do You Want to Go Further?</strong></span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your flower business:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Create and manage your own cosmetic products with the <strong>Manufacturing app</strong>, tracking raw materials like essential oils, pigments, or containers, defining step-by-step production orders (e.g., mix, fill, label), and
                adding quality checks during packaging or formula testing.
            </li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Planning app</strong> to schedule retail staff or lab shifts for batch production or promotional campaigns.</li>
            <li>Host in-store makeup demos, beauty workshops, or influencer pop-ups using the <strong>Events app</strong> to connect with your audience.</li>
            <li>Monitor your carbon footprint, ethical sourcing, and sustainable goals with the <strong>ESG app</strong>.</li>
            <li>Easily handle your accounting with the integrated <strong>Accounting App</strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
  </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Cosmetics Store</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="icon">💄</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">45.60000000000001</field>
        <field name="last_edition_uid" ref="base.user_admin"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
