<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="sale_order_template_1" model="sale.order.template">
    <field name="name">Office Cleaning</field>
    <field name="note"><![CDATA[<h3 data-oe-version="1.1"><strong>TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS</strong></h3><h4><strong>1. Introduction</strong></h4><p>These Terms &amp; Conditions govern the provision of cleaning services by <strong>[Your Company Name]</strong> ("Company," "We," "Us") to business clients ("Client," "You"). By engaging our services, you agree to these terms.</p><h4><strong>2. Services Provided</strong></h4><p>2.1. The Company provides commercial cleaning services, including but not limited to:</p><ul><li>Office cleaning</li><li>Industrial cleaning</li><li>Retail space cleaning</li><li>Janitorial services</li><li>Specialized cleaning (e.g., deep cleaning, disinfection)</li></ul><p>2.2. The scope of services will be outlined in a separate Service Agreement or Work Order.</p><h4><strong>3. Service Schedule &amp; Access</strong></h4><p>3.1. Cleaning services will be performed as per the agreed schedule.</p><p>3.2. The Client must provide access to the premises during scheduled cleaning times.</p><p>3.3. Any changes to the schedule require at least <strong>[X]</strong> hours’ notice.</p><h4><strong>4. Payment Terms</strong></h4><p>4.1. Fees are outlined in the Service Agreement.</p><p>4.2. Invoices are issued <strong>[weekly/monthly]</strong> and payable within <strong>[X]</strong> days from the invoice date.</p><p>4.3. Late payments may incur interest of <strong>[X]%</strong> per month.</p><p>4.4. Additional services requested outside the agreed contract will be billed separately.</p><h4><strong>5. Cancellation &amp; Rescheduling</strong></h4><p>5.1. The Client may cancel or reschedule a cleaning session with at least <strong>[X]</strong> hours’ notice.</p><p>5.2. Cancellations with less notice may be subject to a cancellation fee of <strong>[X]%</strong> of the service charge.</p><p>5.3. The Company reserves the right to reschedule services due to unforeseen circumstances (e.g., staff shortages, emergencies).</p><h4><strong>6. Health &amp; Safety Compliance</strong></h4><p>6.1. The Company adheres to all health and safety regulations.</p><p>6.2. The Client must inform the Company of any hazardous conditions or special requirements on the premises.</p><p>6.3. The Client must ensure safe working conditions for the cleaning staff.</p><h4><strong>7. Liability &amp; Insurance</strong></h4><p>7.1. The Company carries liability insurance to cover damages caused by negligence.</p><p>7.2. The Client must report any damage claims within <strong>[X]</strong> hours of service completion.</p><p>7.3. The Company is not liable for pre-existing damage or loss of unattended valuables.</p><h4><strong>8. Confidentiality &amp; Data Protection</strong></h4><p>8.1. The Company will keep all Client information confidential.</p><p>8.2. Any personal data shared will be processed in compliance with <strong>[relevant data protection laws]</strong>.</p><h4><strong>9. Termination</strong></h4><p>9.1. Either party may terminate the agreement with <strong>[X]</strong> days’ written notice.</p><p>9.2. Immediate termination may occur if either party breaches these terms.</p><h4><strong>10. Dispute Resolution</strong></h4><p>10.1. Any disputes should first be resolved through negotiation.</p><p>10.2. If unresolved, disputes may be referred to arbitration in <strong>[jurisdiction]</strong>.</p><h4><strong>11. Governing Law</strong></h4><p>These Terms &amp; Conditions are governed by the laws of <strong>[your country/state]</strong>.</p>]]></field>
    <field name="require_signature" eval="True"/>
    <field name="prepayment_percent">1.0</field>
  </record>
</odoo>
