<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_1" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Restaurant(Food &amp; Cafe Store)</field>
        <field name="icon">🍽️</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1>
                    <span style="font-size: 36px; font-weight: bolder;">Restaurant(Food &amp; Café Store)</span>
                </h1>
                <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
                    <font class="text-o-color-5">
                        The restaurant industry is a diverse and competitive sector that involves the preparation and service of food and beverages to customers. It includes a wide range of establishments, from fine dining restaurants to fast-food joints, cafés, food trucks, cloud kitchens, and more.
                    </font>
                </p>
                <h2>
                    <span style="font-size: 18px; font-weight: bolder;">Flow 1: Dine In</span>
                </h2>
                <h3>
                    <span style="font-size: 14px;"><font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);">1.1 Online Table Booking</font></span>
                </h3>
                <p>
                    Customers can book a table for their meals directly from the website.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Popular restaurants tend to get booked quickly, especially during peak hours or on weekends. It is advisable to book your table in advance to secure your preferred date and time.
                </p>
                <h3>
                    <span style="font-size: 14px;"><font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);">1.2 Order at table</font></span>
                </h3>
                <p>
                    From the table, a customer can scan and see the menu. The waiter will collect the order table-wise from the Point of Sale app.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <font class="text-black"><strong>Point of Sale</strong></font> &gt; Open Restaurant/Shop &gt; Select the table  &gt; Collecting an order from different categories of food items.
                </p>
                <h3>
                    <font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);"><span style="font-size: 14px;">1.2 Kitchen Display</span></font>
                </h3>
                <p>
                    The orders collected can be viewed in the Preparation Display and managed accordingly. Once prepared by the chef, the food is ready to be served by the waiters, Even the serving process also being tracked.
                </p>
                <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
                    Preparation Display: 'A kitchen Display where orders can viewed by Chef and make it ready to serve'.
                </blockquote>
                <h3>
                    <font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);"><span style="font-size: 14px;">1.3 Bill &amp; Payment</span></font>
                </h3>
                <p>
                    Now, it is time to generate a receipt prior to the payment, which will be collected through Cash &amp; Bank(Stripe, Paypal, Sodexo cards, etc.). Additionally, this allows for splitting bill.
                </p>
                <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
                    Spilt Bill: 'Split total or order lines amongs the people'.
                </blockquote>
                <h2>
                    <span style="font-size: 18px; font-weight: bolder;">Flow 2: Pick up/takeaways offline</span>
                </h2>
                <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
                    Pick-up orders are a convenient option for customers who order food from a restaurant and then take it away to eat at home or elsewhere. Examples of such orders include Chow Mein, Pizza, Cakes, and more.
                </p>
                <p>
                    - A walk-in customer comes and orders their food in person. Payment will be made immediately and based on receipt, the food will be delivered or 'Ship Later'.
                </p>
                <p>
                    - <strong>Point of Sale</strong> &gt; Open Restaurant/shop &gt; Enter the amount of food to be delivered(if available) &gt; Received the payment via Cash/Bank/Cards along with selecting the option to 'Ship Later' and expected delivery date.
                </p>
                <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">
                    <span style="font-style: normal;">Ship Later: 'Sell products and deliver them later(It can be today or later)'.</span>
                </blockquote>
                <p>
                    - A deliveryman will validate the delivery based on the POS order receipt.
                </p>
                <h2>
                    <span style="font-size: 18px; font-weight: bolder;">Flow 3: Pick up/takeaways online</span>
                </h2>
                <p>
                    Use an online ordering system for restaurants to begin accepting online orders through their website. This will help minimize customer wait times when placing an order and streamline business operations. For example, the system can be used to accept orders for burgers, cakes, pizza, and other menu items.
                </p>
                <h3>
                    <font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);">Website</font>
                </h3>
                <p>
                    - Products that are available to sell online, should be <strong>Published</strong> on your website.
                </p>
                <p>
                    - Customer can log in and put their orders online and payment for the same via bank transfer or cards(Stripe, PayPal, etc.)..
                </p>
                <p>
                    - We'll deliver Website orders from Website &gt; orders &gt; SO no. &gt; delivery &gt; validate.
                </p>
                <p>
                    - Invoice can be downloaded from the customer portal itself.
                </p>
                <hr/>
            ]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
