<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_9" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Lounge and Bar</field>
        <field name="category">private</field>
        <field name="parent_path">9/</field>
        <field name="icon">&#128747;</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_12" />
        <field name="cover_image_position">52.400000000000034</field>
        <field name="full_width" eval="True" />
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
        <![CDATA[
                <h1><span style="font-size: 36px;">Lounge and Bar</span><br></h1>
                <p><span style="width: 40px;" class="oe-tabs">	</span>​This setup is for service&nbsp;companies who provides all kind of service that customer can avail&nbsp;at the Airport like Porter Service, Buggy Service, Airport Assistance etc..</p>
                <p><span style="width: 40px;" class="oe-tabs">	</span>​This Services can be avail directly from the airport and individuals can also purchase the services from the website.</p>
                <p><br></p>
                <h1>Business Flows</h1>
                <p><br></p>
                <h3>Flow 1: Sell&nbsp;Service Online<br></h3>
                <ol>
                        <li>Visit the website &amp; select the service you want buy.</li>
                        <li>Place the order by filling the required details&nbsp;during checkout process.</li>
                        <li>Once the order placed, customer receive the call from the service department&nbsp;for the confirmation.</li>
                        <li>Customer will get the order detail via email.</li>
                </ol>
                <p>Sometime we also got call or email and based on that we book the service manually by creating the Sales order.</p>
                <p><br></p>
                <h3>Flow 2: Sell&nbsp;Service using POS<br></h3>
                <p>We have a multiple&nbsp;employees who are at the airport to provide all type of airport service on the go. Each one has their own POS shop with log in credentials.</p>
                <ol>
                        <li>Customer will visit the airport and wants to buy a Porter Service.</li>
                        <li>Porter user will open the POS and select desire the service.</li>
                        <li>Select the payment method and place the order.</li>
                </ol>
                <p>this process will be same for other services like Buggy Service, Airport Assistance etc...</p>
                <p><br></p>
                <h3>Flow 3: Lounge with Bar</h3>
                <p>We also server beer in the bar. We serve the beer in 125 ml of Glass only and also purchase in the bottle of 500 ml or 1 Ltr.</p>
                <h3>Setup</h3>
                <p>a. Create two product one which you purchase(ex. Beer 500 ml) and another which you will sell(ex. Beer 125&nbsp;ml).</p>
                <p>b. Create new UOM as "Bottle of 500 ml" under UNIT category and define the ration 0.5 and the type will be smaller and save it.</p>
                <p>c.&nbsp;Now create a <strong><font class="text-o-color-2">KIT</font></strong> type bill of material for the product of <strong>Beer 125 ml</strong>. Components will be <strong>Beer 500 ml</strong> product with consume qty 0.25.<span></span></p>
                <p>Once above setup is done, we are ready to start our sell from the POS Session.</p>
                <h3>Process Flaw</h3>
                <p>- Employee will log in with the credential in the Airport Assistance POS.</p>
                <p>- Now customer ask for 2 glass of Beer, Will select the <strong>Beer 125 ml</strong> product and set the qty as 2.</p>
                <p>- Complete the order by received the payment.</p>
                <p>Now if we check the inventory then <strong>Beer 500 ml</strong> product is consumed by 0.5 ml from the current stock because of the <strong><font class="text-o-color-2">KIT</font></strong> type Bill of material.</p>
        ]]>
        </field>
</record>
</odoo>
