<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint">Community Care</h1>
        <p>The Community Care industry is currently undergoing a digital revolution. This Odoo
            industry package is designed to rescue educators and caregivers from "administrative
            debt"—those exhausting hours lost to paper files and fragmented spreadsheets that should
            be spent with the residents. By verticalizing Odoo, we provide a professionalized,
            unified "Single Source of Truth" that handles the complexity of social care with the
            simplicity of a modern utility.</p>
        <p>With millions of residents in small facilities globally, the need for a secure,
            integrated system has never been higher. This package leverages Odoo's powerful core
            modules to transform how small homes manage staff, legal records, and daily care.
            Ultimately, we are giving care teams the tools to refocus on their true mission: <b>providing
            a safe, supportive environment for every resident, not just managing clicks.</b>
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Basics</h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Residents App:</b> A specialized workspace to manage the placement lifecycle from
                admission to successful transition.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Contacts:</b> Securely manage residents, guardians, and medical networks in a
                centralized, categorized database.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Planning:</b> Coordinate 24/7 staff coverage to ensure safety ratios and
                consistent caregiver presence.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Documents:</b> Store sensitive legal orders, school reports, and care plans in a
                secure, searchable location.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Timesheets:</b> Log specific care hours and administrative tasks for accurate
                facility operational reporting.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Calendar:</b> Organize medical appointments and family visits with automated
                reminders for the entire team.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Employees:</b> Manage staff certifications and hierarchies to ensure the most
                qualified team is always on-site.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Time Off:</b> Handle leave requests seamlessly without compromising critical
                caregiver-to-resident safety ratios.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Knowledge:</b> Draft collaborative observation logs and formal reports using
                standardized, professional templates.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Project:</b> Track long-term developmental milestones and facility maintenance
                tasks through organized stages.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Use case</h1>
        <hr />
        <h2>🏠 Resident admission &amp; management</h2>
        <p>Streamline your admission process by moving from the <b>Residents</b> to <b>Documents</b>
            and <b>Knowledge</b>. This ensures that as soon as a resident is created, their network
            of guardians is mapped, their legal mandates are filed, and their first appointments are
            scheduled.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Residents app:</b> Use the dedicated dashboard to view your current residents.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Specialized profiles:</b> Capture unique data like Nicknames, Primary Languages,
                and Date of Birth to provide personalized, trauma-informed care.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Relationship mapping:</b> Within the Contacts Tab, link parents, legal guardians,
                social workers, and primary physicians to create a 360-degree care circle.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Related data:</b> Leverage the smart buttons from residents to reach their
                Documents and notes efficiently.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>🕒 Staffing 24/7</h2>
        <p>Link your human resources directly to resident needs. By integrating <b>Employees</b>, <b>
            Planning</b>, and <b>Time Off</b>, you ensure that the house is always staffed with the
            right certifications and that safety ratios are never compromised.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Planning App:</b> Utilize the Gantt View to visualize 24/7 coverage. Create
                templates for recurring shifts to save hours on weekly scheduling.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Time Off Management:</b> Automatically sync staff absences with the Planning App
                to identify coverage gaps before they become safety risks.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Timesheets:</b> Staff can log hours against specific care activities, providing
                management with clear data on administrative vs. direct-care time.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Employee Records:</b> Store mandatory certifications and training records in the
                Employees App to ensure compliance with local care regulations.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>🏥 Health, safety, &amp; compliance</h2>
        <p>Centralize critical medical data and legal mandates to eliminate dangerous information
            silos. This sequence ensures that in an emergency, life-saving information like
            allergies and blood types is accessible in seconds.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Medical &amp; Safety Dashboard:</b> Located directly on the Resident profile,
                this tab provides instant visibility of Blood Types, Allergies, and Medication
                Protocols.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Documents App:</b> Organize files by folder (e.g., Legal, Health, School) and use
                the Group By Folder view to find a specific scan or report instantly.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Allergy Alerts:</b> Leverage color-coded tags for Allergies and Medical
                Conditions that appear on the Resident Kanban and List views for high-visibility
                warnings.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Legal Compliance:</b> Store the Placement Mandate and Court Orders directly in
                the record, ensuring staff always know the current legal status of a minor.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>📝 Knowledge transfer &amp; daily liaison</h2>
        <p>Replace scattered notebooks with a collaborative <b>Knowledge Base</b>. This sequence
            allows staff to log daily observations, record meeting outcomes, and share mentorship
            strategies in real-time.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Daily Liaison Logs:</b> Use Knowledge Articles to record anecdotes and shift
                handovers. This ensures that the night shift knows exactly what happened during the
                day.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Standardized Templates:</b> Create "Report Ready" articles for School Reports or
                Life Goal Plans, significantly reducing the time spent on formal correspondence.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Meeting Focus:</b> Utilize the Smart Button on the Resident profile to jump
                directly to meeting notes that focus on that specific individual.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Mentorship Planning:</b> Document long-term "Life Paths" and collaborative goals
                between mentors and residents, tracking progress through the Project App.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>📊 Funding justification &amp; impact reporting</h2>
        <p>Secure your financial baseline and prove your utility to state regulators without the
            end-of-month spreadsheet panic. The <b>Dashboard app</b> automates the tedious task of
            prorating monthly night stays for billing, while aggregating long-term demographic data
            to generate audit-proof annual reports.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b>Monthly overnights:</b> Automatically generate nominative lists of overnight
                stays for the previous month. The built-in mathematical engine handles ongoing stays
                (empty departure dates) flawlessly, eliminating manual night-by-night counting. </li>
            <li>
                <b>Annual impact metrics:</b> Review aggregated charts giving your board of
                directors clear evidence of your social footprint: <ul>
                    <li>Household status at entry;</li>
                    <li>Referral Sources;</li>
                    <li>Reason of admission and departure;</li>
                    <li>Referral sources;</li>
                    <li>Top 10 countries of origin breakdown;</li>
                    <li>Demographic pyramid using legal care age groups (0-3, 4-11, 12-17, 18-25,
                26-59, 60+) calculated against the beginning of the observed period, protecting
                historical accuracy for funding tied to minors or young adults.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p><b>Interactive Audit Mode:</b> Access the underlying Spreadsheet behind the
                    dashboard to switch from "Automatic" to "Manual" mode. Input any historical
                    dates to recalculate the entire report instantly. This is perfect for answering
                    retro-active funding disputes or state audits from 6 months ago.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your
                    Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a
                        href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a
                        href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel
                    free to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need
                    help!</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🥇</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    <strong>Tips for success</strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>Use the Kanban Grouping:</b> Group your Residents App by age or legal
                        status to get an instant bird's-eye view of your facility's demographic and
                        legal landscape.</li>
                    <li>
                        <b>Leverage Color Tags:</b> Use bright colors for Allergies and Medication
                        alerts. This visual cue is the fastest way to prevent errors during meal
                        times or activities.</li>
                    <li>
                        <b>Standardize Handovers:</b> Encourage all staff to use a specific
                        Knowledge Template for shift handovers. Consistency in documentation leads
                        to better continuity of care.</li>
                    <li>
                        <b>Secure Your Folders:</b> Regularly audit the Documents App folder
                        permissions to ensure that sensitive legal data is only accessible to
                        authorized "Need to Know" staff.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Explore additional apps to enhance your community care management:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Accounting</strong> – Advanced financial management and reporting.</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Sign</strong> – Collect digital signatures for placement mandates and
                approvals.</li>
            <li>
                <b>Maintenance</b> – Track repairs for the facility and safety equipment.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Odoo offers scalable solutions that grow with your organization. By integrating these
            apps, care homes can maximize operational efficiency, improve resident outcomes, and
            maintain regulatory compliance.</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p>
                    <a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Final word</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>You might have tested this package with or without demo data. <br /> In any case, you may
            have written records which are not deletable and which might be an issue for your
            traceability.</p>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    <strong>In such situation, feel free to experiment with this database and then
                        to create a new one for your own usage.</strong>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Community Care</field>
        <field name="icon">🧒</field>
        <field name="sequence" eval="1" />
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
