<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1><span style="font-size: 36px;">Software Resellers, IT Services</span><br /></h1>
        <p>
            <span style="font-size: 14px;">
                This setup if for IT companies reselling software licenses, and consulting services. The typical sale is a 1 year Oracle Database license that is purchased to Oracle, and resold to client at a margin, with extra services to setup
                the database.
            </span>
        </p>
        <p>
            Licenses are managed as tasks in the project management app, with custom properties; license key, number of users, software version, ... these properties depend on the type of software sold (i.e. Odoo is sold based on the number of
            users periodically, but Oracle requires a lot of information: number of CPUs, number of developer seats, size of DB, etc)
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Business Flows: Licenses Management</h1>
        <hr />
        <h2>Flow 1: Sell Oracle Licenses</h2>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Sell Oracle Licenses</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            Open the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> and create a <strong><font class="text-o-color-2">subscription​</font></strong> to any customer with the
            <strong><font class="text-o-color-2">product "Oracle Database"</font></strong><font class="text-o-color-2">,</font> for 5 users for one year. Once you confirm this order, two documents will be created:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>A purchase order to Oracle; to buy the license for this client</li>
            <li>A task to manage the license, in stage "New Requests"</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Purchase the licenses</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            From the subscription, using the top buttons, jump to the purchase order to buy these licenses to Oracle. You can send by email your request for quotation, then confirm the order. At that point, Oracle will send you the license number.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Manage customer licenses</u></strong><br />
        </p>
        <p>Go back to the sale order, then jump to the task. On the task, set the different informations based on what oracle sends you:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Environment: Production</li>
            <li>Version: 20.0.1</li>
            <li>License Key: XYZ</li>
            <li>Assignee: your account manager / user</li>
            <li>Deadline: corresponding to the license key expiration date</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            In the chatter, leverage the email template to send those information to your customer by clicking the Send message button, opening the full composer and then selecting the Send licenses template from the three dots menu of the composer
            bottom bar. The sent email appears in the chatter!
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You can customize the email template with additional details and instructions, even including additional documents such as license setup procedure.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h2>Flow 2: Manage your licenses</h2>
        <p>
            From the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Licenses App</font></strong>, specially tailored for the Software reseller industry, you can have an overview of all your software licenses. Click on one specific license to track license
            keys belonging to each customer.
        </p>
        <p>From a license key:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Record all information related to the license (version, type of license, ...). These information are different from one license type to another (Oracle vs Odoo)</li>
            <li>You can communicate with customers on the chatter, to keep a history of the discussions or leverage the email template as mentioned previously.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Licenses</font></strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> </font><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">App</font></strong> has 3 menus:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Licenses by Software (in kanban)</li>
            <li>All Licenses (default to list)</li>
            <li>Licenses to rework: licenses for which you have to do some work periodically</li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>A studio scheduled action automatically turns the license state to Changes Requested when the license key expires within 15 days.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2 data-o-mail-quote="1" data-o-mail-quote-node="1">Flow 3: Renew a license</h2>
        <p data-o-mail-quote="1" data-o-mail-quote-node="1">To renew a license, you should just renew the subscription from the sale order; the task remains the same.</p>
        <p data-o-mail-quote="1" data-o-mail-quote-node="1"><br /></p>
        <p data-o-mail-quote="1"><br data-o-mail-quote="1" /></p>
        <h1>Business Flow: Selling Services</h1>
        <hr />
        <h3>Flow 3: Selling Odoo with Services</h3>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Sell a project</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            Usually, you sell the software licenses with additional services. To test this flow from the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Sales App</strong></font>, as you create a quotation, use the quotation template
            <strong>
                <font class="text-o-color-2">"Odoo Standard Implementation"</font>
                <font style="color: inherit;"><span style="font-weight: normal;">. That will add the services billed on timesheets (default setup: sell days, but timesheets per hour).</span></font>
            </strong>
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    From the Product Sales tab, you can also add development serves in one click as Optional Products.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>As you confirm the order, it will:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><font style="background-color: inherit;">Create a purchase order to buy the Odoo license to Odoo S.A.</font></li>
            <li>Create a task to track the license</li>
            <li>Create 3 tasks to track services</li>
            <li>Create 200 hours to plan, in the planning</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Invoice Licenses</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            As you confirm the order, the license line is blue as you can already invoice it. The consulting services are black as there is nothing to invoice; you'll be able to invoice at the end of the month, based on the time spent on the
            project.
        </p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>On this order, the way to manage licenses is similar to the above section. So, we'll mostly focus on the delivery of the extra services.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Plan Consultants</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            From the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Planning App</font></strong>, click New:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Select the services to plan "Business Need Analysis" and "Odoo Configuration" (training will be planned later on, on phase 2)</li>
            <li>Assign these services to the right person and make this fit in their shifts.</li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Alternatively you can leverage the roles assigned to your employees and leverage the "Auto Plan" capability beside the Publish button. This creates and assign all shifts automatically.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Don't forget to hit the Publish button from your planning to let your employees know what their coming weeks look like.</p>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Timesheet Work done</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>
            From the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Timesheet App</font></strong>, or on one task, consultants and developers can timesheet their spent time on the different phases of the project: Business Need Analysis, Odoo
            Configuration, or Training &amp; Support. This will be reflected as "Delivered Quantity" on the sale order lines.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong><u>Invoice Projects</u></strong>
        </p>
        <p>At the end of the month, salespeople go to the menu "Orders to Invoice" in <strong>Sales App</strong>. From there they can select an order (or select all), and invoice what has been delivered on the order.</p>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>
                    Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a> , and feel free
                    to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                Start receiving orders directly in Odoo or go live with your <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">E-shop</font></strong> in a few minutes.
            </li>
            <li>
                Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </template>    
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Software Resellers</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">🤘</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_3" />
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True" />
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
