<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
  <record id="appointment_type_grooming_service" model="appointment.type">
    <field name="name">Grooming Services</field>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="appointment_duration">1.5</field>
    <field name="location_id" ref="base.main_partner"/>
    <field name="staff_user_ids" eval="[(4, ref('base.user_admin'))]"/>
    <field name="event_videocall_source" eval="False"/>
    <field name="allow_guests" eval="True"/>
    <field name="category">recurring</field>
    <field name="message_intro"><![CDATA[<ul><li><strong>Bath &amp; Dry</strong> – wash with pet-safe shampoos, conditioners, blow-dry.</li><li><p><strong>Brushing &amp; De-shedding</strong> – remove loose fur, undercoat, reduce shedding.</p></li>
<li><strong>Haircuts &amp; Styling</strong> – breed-standard trims (poodles, terriers) or custom owner requests.</li>
<li><p><strong>Puppy’s First Groom</strong> – gentle introduction session for young dogs.</p></li></ul>
<div>Our core grooming services cover all the essentials to keep your pet looking fresh, comfortable, and well cared for. Whether it’s a quick bath and brush or a full haircut tailored to your pet’s breed, we handle it with expertise and care.</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>Every session begins with a gentle wash using high-quality, pet-safe shampoos and conditioners suited to your pet’s coat type. After drying, we brush thoroughly to remove tangles and loose hair. For pets that require haircuts, we offer trims and styling according to breed standards or your personal preferences.</div>
<div><br></div>
<p>These services are ideal for routine upkeep, managing shedding, and keeping your pet’s coat in top condition. From the very first “puppy’s groom” to regular maintenance, our goal is to make grooming a positive, stress-free experience for your furry friend.</p>]]></field>
    <field name="max_schedule_days">30</field>
    <field name="slot_creation_interval">2.0</field>
    <field name="work_hours_activated" eval="True"/>
    <field name="product_id" ref="appointment_account_payment.default_booking_product"/>
    <field name="slot_ids" eval="[
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '1', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '1', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '2', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '2', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '3', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '3', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '4', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '4', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '5', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '5', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
    ]"/>
  </record>
  <record id="appointment_type_animal_wellness" model="appointment.type">
    <field name="name">Animal Wellness Service</field>
    <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    <field name="category">recurring</field>
    <field name="staff_user_ids" eval="[(4, ref('base.user_admin'))]"/>
    <field name="message_intro"><![CDATA[<h6>✨ Premium / Spa Services</h6>
<ul>
<li><p><strong>De-matting</strong> – untangling severe knots in long-haired breeds.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Coat Conditioning Treatments</strong> – special shampoos, oils, or masks.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Creative Grooming</strong> – coat dyeing, fur sculpting, accessories (bows, bandanas).</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Seasonal Packages</strong> – “Summer cut” or “Winter coat maintenance.”</p></li></ul>
<p>For pets that deserve the extra touch, our premium and spa services transform routine grooming into a relaxing, pampering experience. These treatments go beyond the basics to provide luxurious care tailored to special coat and skin needs.</p>
<p>Options include de-matting for long-haired breeds prone to tangles, coat conditioning masks that nourish and revitalize fur, and creative grooming such as coat dyeing or sculpted styles for unique looks. We also offer seasonal packages like a “Summer Cut” to keep your pet cool, or “Winter Coat Care” for warmth and comfort during colder months.</p>
<p>Every premium treatment is performed with patience and attention to detail, ensuring your pet not only looks their best but also enjoys the process. Perfect for special occasions, show preparation, or simply because your companion deserves a spa day.</p>]]></field>
    <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_2"/>
    <field name="slot_ids" eval="[
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '1', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '1', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '2', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '2', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '3', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '3', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '4', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '4', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '5', 'start_hour': 9.0, 'end_hour': 12.0}),
        (0, 0, {'weekday': '5', 'start_hour': 14.0, 'end_hour': 17.0}),
    ]"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
