<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="sale_order_line_2" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_5"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_2"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_3" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Vermi Compost - Powder (1 Kg) Vermi Compost Powder is a nutrient-rich organic fertilizer created through the natural process of composting with earthworms. This fine powder is teeming with beneficial microorganisms and essential nutrients, enhancing soil fertility and promoting healthy plant growth when applied to gardens and crops.</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_12"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_2"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_4" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Onion Seeds (1 Kg) Onion seeds are the tiny, potent beginnings of one of the most versatile and essential vegetables in the culinary world. These seeds hold the promise of growing into pungent, layered bulbs that can add depth and flavor to a wide array of dishes. With various onion varieties available, each seed encapsulates the potential for creating a diverse range of flavors, from sweet to sharp. Planted and nurtured, onion seeds yield the foundation for countless savory recipes and garden delights.</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_8"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_1"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_5" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Discount: 10% on specific products - On product with the following taxes: 15%</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_26"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_1"/>
        <field name="points_cost">1.0</field>
        <field name="reward_id" ref="loyalty_reward_2"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_6" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Standard delivery</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="delivery.product_product_delivery"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_1"/>
        <field name="is_delivery" eval="True"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_7" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Multi Fruit Fertilizer is a specialized agricultural product designed to enhance the growth and yield of various types of fruits. Formulated with a balanced blend of essential nutrients, minerals, and organic compounds, this fertilizer supports the unique nutritional requirements of different fruit crops. Its innovative composition promotes healthy root development, robust plant growth, and improved fruit quality. By providing a comprehensive solution for multiple fruit varieties, Multi Fruit Fertilizer contributes to increased productivity and overall crop success in orchards and gardens.</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_11"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_3"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_8" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">Fast Root Fertilizer is a potent and specialized formula designed to promote rapid root development in plants. Packed with essential nutrients and growth stimulants, this fertilizer accelerates the establishment of strong and healthy root systems, enhancing overall plant growth and vitality.</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_10"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_4"/>
    </record>
    <record id="sale_order_line_9" model="sale.order.line">
        <field name="name">The Soil Activator is a natural solution that boosts soil health and plant growth. Packed with beneficial microorganisms and nutrients, it revitalizes the soil ecosystem, promoting better nutrient absorption and stronger, more vibrant plants.</field>
        <field name="product_id" ref="product_product_13"/>
        <field name="order_id" ref="sale_order_5"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
