<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.0">Environmental Agency</h1><p>Welcome to the <strong>Odoo Environmental Agency Package</strong>!</p>
        <p>This package is designed to support environmental agencies and consulting firms in optimizing operations, managing projects, and assessing environmental impact with clarity and credibility. Whether conducting carbon footprint analyses, developing sustainability strategies, or guiding organizations in reducing their environmental impact, it enhances overall efficiency and decision-making.</p>
        <p>With this module, you can manage opportunities, structure sustainability projects, track consultancy hours, and organize key reports. Features like CRM, Project, and Timesheet simplify daily tasks, while Appointment allows clients to book demos with ease.</p>
        <p>Let's get started to see the change you want to see in the world! 🌍</p>
        <h2>Basics</h2><hr/>
        <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">CRM App</font></strong> helps you manage client interactions and track potential leads.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Sales App</font></strong> streamlines quotations and contract management.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Project &amp; Documents App</font></strong> organizes your projects and centralizes key documents.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Timesheet App</font></strong> tracks time spent on impactful projects and billable hours.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Website App</font></strong> showcases your environmental services and expertise.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Appointment App</font></strong> allows clients to book demos online.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>Use Case</h2><hr/>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Environmental Agency package and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3><strong>Manage leads and client relationships with CRM</strong></h3>
        <p>Track potential clients and manage interactions effectively.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong>, create a new lead for an organization interested in sustainability services, and assign the lead to a team member.</li>
            <li>Log meetings, calls, and emails directly in the CRM. Use the pipeline to<strong> track the progress of each lead</strong> (e.g., New → Internal Analysis → Qualified → Proposal → Won).</li>
            <li>Once a lead shows interest, generate a <strong>quotation in the Sales App</strong> offering services like strategy consulting, carbon footprint assessments, or ESG reporting.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p> Measure the impact of each project and prioritize effectively. 🌳</p>
                <p>Use automated follow-ups and plan activities to stay engaged with prospects and improve conversion rates.</p>
            </div>
            </div><br/>
            <h3><strong>Structure and track impactful projects</strong></h3>
            <p>Structure your work efficiently with <strong>Project &amp; Documents Apps</strong>.</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Create a new project (e.g., "Client X – ESG Reporting") in the<strong>Project App </strong>or open the existing one linked to the confirmed quotation.</li>
                <li><strong>Manage tasks </strong>by organizing them into stages such as 'To Do,' 'In Progress,' and 'Done,' <strong>while collaborating with the team</strong> by assigning deadlines and responsibilities.</li>
                <li><strong>Upload key documents</strong>, such as client reports and regulatory guidelines, directly into the dedicated project folder, accessible via the smart button on the project page or in the <strong>Document App</strong>.</li>
            </ol>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Organize tasks by Milestones and assign specific dates to key stages in the case.</p>
                    <p><strong><em>Example:<br/><br/>Milestone:</em></strong><em> Carbon Footprint Analysis <br/></em><strong><em>Tasks:</em></strong><em> Collect Emissions Data, Evaluate Resource Consumption, Prepare Initial Report</em></p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <hr/>
            <h3><strong>Track billable hours for consulting services</strong></h3>
            <p>Ensure accurate invoicing and productivity tracking.</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Open the <strong>Timesheet app.</strong></li>
                <li>Use the<strong> timer functionality </strong>to track time spent on a specific client case.</li>
                <li>Manually add a new line to register time on specific tasks if needed.</li>
                <li>Access the Timesheet app via the <strong>smart button</strong> on the project page to view timesheets related to the project or a specific task.</li>
                <li>Link timesheets to invoices in the <strong>Sales App</strong>, generate the invoice based on recorded time, and send it to the client.</li>
            </ol>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Use reporting to analyse time spent on different service categories (e.g., strategy consulting, carbon footprint calculations).</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h3><strong><br/>Allow clients to book demos online</strong></h3>
            <p>Simplify client engagement with the Appointment App.</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Open the <strong>Appointment App</strong> and configure available slots for demos.</li>
                <li>Share a booking link on your website (via the <strong>Website App</strong>) so clients can schedule a demo at their convenience.</li>
                <li>Set up automated <strong>email confirmations and reminders</strong> to ensure clients are notified of their booked demo and any changes.</li>
            </ol>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Set up different appointment types (e.g., "Discovery Call" and "Advanced ESG Strategy Demo") to meet the specific needs of your clients.</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                    <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!</p>
                </div>
            </div>
            <h2><br/>Do you want to go further?</h2>
            <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your environmental agency:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Create custom ESG surveys in the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Survey App</font></strong> to collect data from clients, suppliers, and partners about their environmental practices and sustainability impact.</li>
                <li>Organize sustainability workshops, conferences, and training sessions through the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Event App</font></strong> to raise awareness and promote environmental initiatives.</li>
                <li>Digitally collect commitments from clients and partners to adhere to sustainability standards and environmental principles using the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Sign App</font></strong>.</li>
                <li>Manage consulting fees, track project expenses, and generate financial reports using the <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">Accounting App</font></strong> for seamless financial management.</li>
            </ul>
            <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                    <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
                </div>
            </div>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Environmental Agency</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_4"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">♻️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_position">93.39999999999998</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
