<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_1" model="knowledge.article" >
        <field name="name">Corporate Gifts</field>
        <field name="sequence">1</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_2" />
        <field name="icon">&#127873;</field>
        <field name="body">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>
                <span style="font-size: 36px;">Corporate Gifts</span><br>
            </h1>
            <p>
                <span style="font-size: 14px;">This setup is for marketing companies selling and producing customized corporate gifts, like mugs and t-shirts. A typical sale order is a company buying 50 red t-shirts for his employees, customized with their logo on the pocket, with quantities like:&nbsp; 5 Small, 10 Medium, 25 Large, 10 XL.</span>
            </p>
            <p>In addition, the company runs a B2C eCommerce, for individual buyers to buy products online. Clothes are defined with multiple variants, like size and color.</p>
            <p>To customize products, they use 3 techniques:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>serigrahy; printing on t-shirts, using a frame (the main one on t-shirt)</li>
                <li>embroidery (more costly, so usually for shirts, or hats)</li>
                <li>printing the logo and sticking the printed paper (mugs)</li>
            </ol>
            <p><br></p>
            <h1>Business Flows</h1>
            <h2>Flow 1: Website -&gt; CRM -&gt; Simple Quotes</h2>
            <hr>
            <h3>Website: Request a Quote</h3>
            <p>From the website:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Visit the B2C Shop: show variants and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">select other colors on t-shirt</font><font class="text-o-color-5"><span style="font-weight: normal;"> (photos change)</span></font></strong></li>
                <li>Show the B2B Form: from top menu, you can "<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Request a Quote</font></strong>"</li>
            </ol>
            <p>This customized form will create an opportunity in the CRM, with the right information, and the optional logo of the client.</p>
            <p><br></p>
            <h3>Salesperson meet client</h3>
            <p>From the CRM, schedule a meeting. As you meet the client, you can <strong>create a quotation</strong>&nbsp;and use the <strong>product catalog </strong>to add swag like keyrings &amp; mugs.</p>
            <p><br></p>
            <h2>Flow 2: Buy 50 t-shirts</h2>
            <hr>
            <p>Create a <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">purchase order</font></strong> from B&amp;C, with the product "B&amp;C Inspire Women". As this product is often purchased and sell in batches, a&nbsp;matrix of quantities per color and sizes opens, allowing to place an order for:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Red: 5 Small, 10 Medium, 25 Large, 10 XL</li>
                <li>Purple: 10&nbsp;Small, 8&nbsp;Medium, 20 Large, 12 XL<br></li>
            </ul>
            <p>Validate the reception for all quantities at once. You cals show the product catalog, another approach that could be useful if you want to check the stock on hand as you purchase.</p>
            <p><br></p>
            <h2>Flow 3: Sell&nbsp;20 Customized T-shirts, with pocket logo</h2>
            <hr>
            <h3>Quotation &amp; Sale</h3>
            <p>To create a quotation, <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">select the template "Pocket Serigraphy"</font>.</strong> That will insert the two mandatory services:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Setup cost: creating a frame for the printing (Qty: 1)</li>
                <li>Printing the 20 t-shirts (Qty: 20)</li>
            </ol>
            <p><span style="font-size: 14px;"><font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Then add the product "B&amp;C Inspire Woman"</strong></font>, a grid open to select multiple quantities per size. Print the quotation to see how it looks.</span></p>
            <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">Note: the template also adds "Custom Keyrings" as an option to the offer, to upsell the client. If the customer orders the keyring, it's configuration is to purchase them automatially to manufacturer SwagPro. (make to order)</blockquote>
            <h3>Confirm Sale Order</h3>
            <p>As the customer confirms the sale order, two tasks will be created:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>Build the serigraphy frame based on customer logo</li>
                <li>Print t-shirts</li>
            </ol>
            <h3>Prepare the frame: Project "Logo Design"</h3>
            <p>First, you need the receive the logo from the customer. From the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">project "Logo Design":</font></strong></p>
            <ol>
                <li>Designers&nbsp;move the task to the stage "Request Logo"</li>
                <li class="oe-nested">
                    <ul>
                        <li>That sends an email automatially to the client to request the logo</li>
                    </ul>
                </li>
                <li>When the client replies to the email with his logo: the logo is automatically attached to the task</li>
                <li>Once received, the designer checks the quality of the file, and move to "Frame Creation, then "Done"</li>
                <li><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Once the frame is Done, The Serigraphy Task is automatically moved</font></strong> to "Frame Received" + Green (Studio automated Action)</li>
            </ol>
            <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1">Note: all logos appear in the Document Management System, under the Project &gt; Logo Design workspace. You might tag the final version of each document, if you want ot use document management.</blockquote>
            <p><br></p>
            <h3>Print t-shirts</h3>
            <blockquote data-o-mail-quote-node="1" data-o-mail-quote="1"><font style="color: rgb(115, 24, 66);">In this setup, we chose a very simple approach, based on tasks, rather than manufacturing orders. Workers just see the tasks to do in a project. That simplifies the workflow.</font></blockquote>
            <p>Serigraphy workers work in the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>project "Serigraphy"</strong></font>; a task has been created to follow the printing job. As they start customizing the t-shirts, they move the task to "In Printing", and then "Done" when it's finished.</p>
            <p>Quantities to customize are available from the linked Sales Order.</p>
            <h3>Deliver products</h3>
            <p>Now that the t-shirts are customized, you can deliver the 20 products from the inventory application. Use the barcode scanner, or the backend, up to you.</p>
            <p><br></p>
        ]]>
        </field>
        </record>
</odoo>
