<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>Automobile spare parts retailer</h1>
        <p><br /></p>
        <p>
            This set-up is for companies selling automobile spare parts. These businesses are expected to have various car brands parts that cover the main components and needs of a car such as the engine, maintenance, and accessories.
        </p>
        <p>To support the business, the following applications are included:</p><ul><li>Point of Sale (PoS) - for face-to-face sales with customers,</li><li>Inventory - to manage the stock of the parts,</li><li>and Sales, Purchase and Accounting to support smooth operations.</li></ul>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <h1>Configuration</h1>
        <p><font style="color: rgb(255, 156, 0);">EAN/UPC Code</font><font class="text-o-color-2">:</font> the Barcode field label has been renamed to this. This is to clarify that every product is expected to use its standard global EAN/UPC code.<br /></p>
        <p><font style="color: rgb(255, 156, 0);">Part Number</font>: the product Internal Reference field has been renamed to this, to follow the industry naming standard.</p>
        <p>
            <font style="color: rgb(255, 156, 0);">OEM No</font>: new field for parts provided by an Original Equipment Manufacturer. If the product is manufactured by the company that provides that same part for the manufacturing of the vehicle, then it should have a OEM Number.</p>
        <p><font style="color: rgb(255, 156, 0);">Brands</font>: new field to record the relevant car brands the part is used in.</p>
        <h1>Business Flows</h1>
        <h2>Flow 1: Purchase<br /></h2>
        <p>1. Create a request for quotation (RFQ) for the Vendor and select the desired products. Then send the RFQ via email.</p>
        <p>2. After negotiations are completed, put the price of the product in the RFQ and confirm it so that it becomes a Purchase Order (PO).</p>
        <p>
            3. After confirming the PO, a receipt will be generated based on the product quantities in your PO. Within the receipt, you indicate quantities received per product under the "Quantity" column. If some products have a lot or serial number, then you have to
            provide these values before validating the receipt.
        </p>
        <h2>Flow 2: B2B Customer<br /></h2>
        <p>
            1.For Business to Business (B2B) sales, the standard sales process to create the quotation is followed. First select the products and send the quotation. After negotiations are completed, you confirm the quotation with the agreed upon quantities and prices and a delivery will automatically be generated. Within the delivery, the qualities being sent are entered under the "Quantities" column and is considered completed when the delivery is validated.<br />
        </p>
        <blockquote >for B2B customers you can use the B2B Price list.</blockquote>
        <p >
            2. If you want to manage warranties for certain products: first enable Lot &amp; Serial Numbers and Expiration Dates in the settings. Then enable tracking by lots or serial numbers in the corresponding products' form views. Once activated, set the warranty period in days under the Expiration Date field in the same form view. When the product is delivered, this number of warranty days will automatically be applied to the lot/serial number based on the delivery date and stored under its expiration date field.
            </p>
        <h2>Flow 3: B2C Customer - Point of Sale<br /></h2>
        <p>1.For Business to Customer (B2C) sales, customers are expected to come to the shop and a salesperson will sell parts to them using the PoS app. The parts being sold and the payment by the customer are all handled within the PoS.<br /></p>
        <blockquote >for B2C customers, you can use the B2C Pricelist.</blockquote>
        <p >
            2. If you want to manage warranties for certain products: first enable Lot &amp; Serial Numbers and Expiration Dates in the settings. Then enable tracking by lots or serial numbers in the corresponding products' form views. Once activated, set the warranty period in days under the Expiration Date field in the same form view. When the product is delivered, this number of warranty days will automatically be applied to the lot/serial number based on the delivery date and stored under its expiration date field.
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>    

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Automobile Spare Parts</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="icon">🛠️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_5"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
