<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1>Odoo for Public Institution</h1>
    <p>
        Public institutions today face the dual challenge of increasing citizen expectations and tightening administrative
        budgets. Small city halls, in particular, often struggle with fragmented communication and manual processes that
        hinder their ability to serve their communities effectively. Odoo offers you a unified solution that transforms
        these administrative hurdles into streamlined digital services.
    </p>
    <p>
        By integrating every aspect of municipal management, from citizen requests and public hall rentals to council
        meeting organization, Odoo empowers public servants to focus on high-value community initiatives. This guide
        provides a roadmap for implementing a "Digital City Hall" that fosters transparency, accessibility, and operational
        efficiency across all departments.
    </p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
        <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
        <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
            <p>
                If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should import the demo data and try the Demo - Use Case
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p><br /></p>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h1>Basics</h1>
    <hr/>
    <p>
        You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Helpdesk:</b> Tracks citizen inquiries, pothole reports, and complaints from initial submission through
                to final administrative resolution.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Appointments:</b> Provides a 24/7 self-service portal for citizens to book meetings with officials or
                schedule document renewals.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Website:</b> Acts as the digital town square where residents find information, services, and official
                updates.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Sign:</b> Facilitates legal digital signatures for permits, petitions, and internal approvals,
                eliminating the need for physical paperwork.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Rental:</b> Manages the availability and payment for community halls, sports fields, and public
                equipment.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Events:</b> Organizes, promotes, and tracks attendance for local fairs, town halls, and community
                workshops.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Survey:</b> Gathers community feedback on public initiatives, urban planning, and local service
                satisfaction.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Project:</b> Structures council agendas and tracks administrative tasks to ensure accountability across
                all municipal departments.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Blog:</b> Publishes official news, emergency alerts, and community stories to keep the public
                well-informed.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h1><strong>Use cases</strong></h1>
    <hr />
    <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products, sale orders and more.</p>
    <p>
        You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with
        this package using Odoo.
    </p>
    <p>
        Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps,
        delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!
    </p>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
            <p>
                You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your package and check
                the related box
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>🛠️ Citizen service &amp; issue resolution</h2>
    <p>
        Modernize the way your city handles service requests by replacing physical logs with a trackable digital ticketing
        system.
    </p>
    <p>
        This sequence begins with a resident noticing a local issue and ends with a verified resolution, ensuring no citizen
        concern is overlooked.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Website:</b> The resident accesses a simple reporting form on the municipal site, providing details and
                photos of the issue (e.g., a broken streetlight or missed trash collection).
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Helpdesk:</b> The submission automatically generates a ticket. Staff can categorize the request by
                department and assign it to the relevant maintenance team.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Chatter &amp; Notifications:</b> As the ticket status changes from "In Progress" to "Resolved," the citizen
                receives automated email updates, building trust in public services.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Activity Tracking:</b> Managers use internal notes and scheduled activities within the ticket to ensure
                deadlines for public safety issues are met.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>📅 Professional appointment scheduling</h2>
    <p>
        Eliminate waiting room congestion by allowing citizens to book fixed time slots for specialized services or meetings
        with local leaders.
    </p>
    <p>
        Streamline the interaction between the public and city officials by providing clear availability for high-demand
        services.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Appointment Types:</b> Configure specific durations for different needs, such as "ID Renewal (15 mins)"
                or "Urban Planning Consultation (45 mins)."
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Online Booking:</b> Citizens choose their preferred date and time from the website, receiving an instant
                confirmation and a calendar invite.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Reminders:</b> Automated SMS or email reminders are sent 24 hours before the meeting, significantly
                reducing missed appointments.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Staff Calendar:</b> The official's Odoo calendar is automatically updated, preventing double-bookings and
                allowing for better preparation.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <strong>Appointment Link</strong>: Use flexible appointments to define when you can take longer meetings
                and share a link for citizens to book at their convenience.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>🏠 The unified citizen dashboard</h2>
    <p>
        Offer residents a "My City" account where they can track their interactions, documents, and payments in one place.
    </p>
    <p>
        The portal serves as the central hub for citizen engagement, providing a sense of agency and organization for every
        resident.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Helpdesk Integration:</b> Citizens can view the live status of their submitted tickets (e.g., "Pothole
                repair scheduled for Tuesday") without having to call the front desk.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Document Access:</b> All signed permits, tax documents, or rental agreements are stored securely and
                remain accessible for download at any time.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Communication History:</b> The portal tracks all official messages exchanged with the city hall, creating
                a reliable audit trail for both parties.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Project Visibility:</b> Selected city projects can be shared in the portal to show the community the
                progress of major infrastructure works.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>✍️ Paperless permitting &amp; official signatures</h2>
    <p>
        Accelerate the approval of permits and petitions by transitioning from physical paper trails to secure digital
        signatures.
    </p>
    <p>
        Digitizing the signature process removes the geographic barrier, allowing citizens to complete administrative tasks
        from the comfort of their homes.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Document Templates:</b> Store standard forms for building permits, parking stickers, or community
                petitions as reusable digital templates.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Odoo Sign:</b> Send a signature request via email. The citizen signs on their smartphone or computer, and
                the system records the IP address and timestamp for legal validity.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Internal Approvals:</b> Use the same tool for the Mayor or Council to sign off on budgets and official
                decrees without passing physical folders around the office.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Automatic Archiving:</b> Once fully signed, the document is automatically stored in the
                <b>Documents</b> app and visible in the <b>Citizen Portal</b>.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>🏛️ Resource management &amp; hall bookings</h2>
    <p>
        Maximize the use of community assets by providing a transparent online booking system for halls, fields, and
        equipment.
    </p>
    <p>
        Coordinate the use of public spaces efficiently while ensuring that maintenance and financial tracking are handled
        automatically.
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Resource Catalog:</b> List all available assets on the website with high-quality photos, capacity limits,
                and clear pricing rules.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Conflict Management:</b> The system ensures that no two community groups can book the same town hall or
                tennis court at the same time.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Rental Agreement:</b> Link the booking to <b>Odoo Sign</b> to ensure the citizen accepts the terms of use
                and liability before the reservation is confirmed.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Invoicing:</b> For paid rentals, Odoo generates an invoice automatically, which can be paid online via
                the citizen portal using integrated payment providers.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>🎡 Community events &amp; public consultation</h2>
    <p>
        Foster a vibrant community by organizing local events and gathering resident feedback through integrated digital
        tools.
    </p>
    <p>Engage your residents beyond administrative tasks by involving them in the social and political life of the town.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Events Management:</b> Create pages for the annual summer fair or town hall meetings. Citizens can
                register for free or paid tickets, allowing you to track expected attendance.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Public Surveys:</b> Use the <b>Survey</b> app to poll residents on new projects (e.g., "What should be
                the priority for the new park?").
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Results Transparency:</b> Share the anonymized results of community polls on the website to show how
                public opinion influenced a final decision.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Marketing &amp; Newsletter:</b> Use the registered emails from events and surveys to send official monthly
                city newsletters via the <b>Email Marketing</b> app.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>📝 Council governance &amp; meeting follow-up</h2>
    <p>Transform your council meetings into action-oriented sessions by tracking agenda items as collaborative tasks.</p>
    <p>Good governance relies on the bridge between a meeting room decision and real-world execution by municipal staff.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Project Management:</b> Create a project for "City Council 2024." Each agenda item for an upcoming
                meeting is entered as a task.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Meeting Minutes:</b> Use the task description or the <b>Notes</b> app to record the debate and the final
                vote for each item during the session.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Action Items:</b> If a decision requires action (e.g., "Repair the park fence"), the task is assigned to
                a staff member with a specific deadline.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Timeline View:</b> Use the Gantt or Kanban views to see how many council directives are currently being
                processed by the administration.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h2>📰 Public news &amp; transparency</h2>
    <p>Keep residents informed about road closures, local successes, and upcoming deadlines through a modern city blog.</p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Blog posts:</b> Publish official statements on municipal projects, emergency alerts (like weather
                warnings), or highlights from community events.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Searchable archives:</b> Residents can easily find past announcements regarding tax changes, zoning laws,
                or historical meeting minutes.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Social sharing:</b> Link your blog posts to social media channels to ensure the message reaches residents
                wherever they are online.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Transparency:</b> Regularly post the minutes of council meetings and financial reports for public
                scrutiny to ensure accountability.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
            <p>
                You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your
                business needs.
            </p>
            <p>
                Discover more about Odoo by diving into our
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to
                <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h1><strong>Tips for Success</strong></h1>
    <hr/>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>The Portal-First Strategy:</b> Encourage citizens to use the portal for all requests. This reduces phone
                interruptions and creates a permanent record of all interactions.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Standardize Your Templates:</b> Build clean templates for your most common permits in <b>Odoo Sign</b>.
                This ensures legal consistency and professional municipal branding.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Centralize Communication:</b> Discourage staff from using personal emails for official business. All
                communication should happen inside the <b>Odoo Chatter</b> to ensure continuity if a staff member is absent.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p><br /></p>
    <h1><strong>Do You Want to Go Further?</strong></h1>
    <hr />
    <p>
        The Odoo "Digital City Hall" is just the beginning of your modernization journey. As your municipality grows in
        digital maturity, you can expand your system to manage the complex "Back-Office" of government:
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Accounting:</b> Manage the municipal budget, automate vendor payments, and produce standardized public
                financial reports.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Employees:</b> Maintain a secure directory of city hall staff, tracking their certifications, training,
                and departmental assignments.
            </p>
        </li>
        <li>
            <p>
                <b>Payroll:</b> Ensure compliant and timely salary processing for all public servants, from the central
                administration to the public works crew.
            </p>
        </li>
    </ul>
    <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
    <p><b>Ready to transform your community management?</b></p>
    <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false">
        <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
        <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
            <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
            <p>
                <a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a>
            </p>
        </div>
    </div>
  </template>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Public Institution</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="icon">🏛️</field>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
