<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
                <h1>
                <strong>
                        <span class="display-4-fs"><font class="text-800">Odoo for Bookstore</font></span>
                </strong>
                </h1>
                <p>Hello there! </p>
                <p>You just installed the Odoo for Bookstore package. By doing so, we have installed a bunch of necessary apps to run your bookstore efficiently. </p>
                <p>Discover the basics of this package and explore all the possibilities Odoo offers to improve your experience.</p>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
                        <p>If you want to execute a practical guided tour of this module, you should Import demo data and try the Demo - Use Case. (In the next Knowledge Article)</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc" tabindex="-1">
                <div class="o_knowledge_toc_content">
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Odoo for Bookstore</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Basics</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Use Case</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">1. Point of sale</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">2. Customer orders</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="5" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">3. Institutional customers</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="6" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">4. Weekly replenishment</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="7" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">5. Encode new release</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="8" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">6. Returns</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="9" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1">7. Monitoring &amp; reporting</a>
                        <a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="10" class="o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0">Do you want to go further?</a>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h1>
                <span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span>
                </h1>
                <hr />
                <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
                <ul>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Point of Sale</font></strong> for your sales at the desk. Manage your customer accounts and advantage in the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Contacts App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales App</font></strong> to order books for your customers, create quotations for your institutional clients (libraries, schools, etc.), and invoice them on the go using
                        the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoicing App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Purchase App</font></strong> to order books from your distributors.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Inventory App</font></strong> to manage your orders receive and deliver your products.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Use the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Barcode App</font></strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> </font>to scan your products and create new entries directly from this App to encode new books faster than ever.
                </li>
                </ul>
                <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3">
                        <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into an additional scanner (and much more).</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h1><br /></h1>
                <h1>
                <span class="display-4-fs">
                        <strong>
                        <font class="text-800"><span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span></font>
                        </strong>
                </span>
                </h1>
                <hr />
                <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few products and 2 sample contacts.</p>
                <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
                <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Bookstore package and check the related box. </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h3><br /></h3>
                <h3>1. Point of sale</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>From the Point of sale, open your register on the main dashboard.</p>
                <p>1. Welcome Elise, your favorite customer, she wants to buy the "Da Vinci Code".</p>
                <p>2. Elise also wants to buy a 50€ Gift Card for a friend.</p>
                <p>3. Elise has a customer account; select her using the "Customer" button. </p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You can see that Elise has a Loyalty Card. The demo Library applies a 5% discount for every 200€ spent. Manage Promotions, and Loyalty programs under Point of Sale &gt; Products. <br /></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>4. Register Elise's payment. You can now go back to your main dashboard by selecting "Backend" in the top-right burger menu.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>
                        If you look for Elise in your "Contact" database, you can see that the Odoo Smart Buttons at the top of her page can bring you to her customer history, Elise may even see it on her website account if you activate the
                        relevant apps and configurations.
                        </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h3><br /></h3>
                <h3>2. Customer orders</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>1. You welcome now Hanna Liseuse, but she has a very specific need. She's looking for "Media Burn: Ant Farm and the Making of an Image". You don't have this book in stock, let's order it. </p>
                <p>
                2. Once you've found it on your local books database, go to the sales app and create a new product using its ISBN code : 9781941753354. Define the current distributor in your region by going to the "Purchase" tab (use "My Book
                Distributor" for this case).
                </p>
                <p>3. You can now create a new quotation. Type her name in the "Customer" field to create a new contact.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Use the internal link button, at the right of the field, to view the new contact record created, and don't forget to add an email address for her to receive notifications. Go back to your quotation using the breadcrump.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>4. Add the product to your quotation by searching for its ISBN. You can directly click on the confirm button to turn your quotation in a Sales Order.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You can make a down payment using the Point of Sales. To do so, just go back to this app and click on the Quotation/Order button to retreive the Sales Order.</p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h3><br /></h3>
                <h3>3. Institutional customers</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>Let's say you now need to create a quotation for "The Great Library" near your shop. </p>
                <p>1. Go to the "Sales" App and create a new quotation using the main "New" button on the top left. </p>
                <p>2. They want to get an offer for three copies of "Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone," "Hidden Life of Trees," and "Sapiens: Brief History of Humankind."</p>
                <p>3. Once your quotation is ready, you can email it or confirm it. </p>
                <p>4. Check the smart buttons, a new delivery has been created, but you need to have all products in stock.</p>
                <p>5. Go to the Inventory App. A new Replenishment is suggested under Operations &gt; Replenishment.</p>
                <p>6. If you select your product and click on "Order", a new Purchase Order is created, you can then email it to your distributor and confirm the order placement.</p>
                <p>7. A few days later, you receive your order from the distributor. Go to the Inventory App on you dashboard, you'll see that a new receipt is ready to be processed. Select it and validate your reception. </p>
                <p>8. The last product is now in stock, you can go back to your Sales Order and process the delivery by clicking the "Delivery" smart button. </p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>4. Weekly replenishment</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>1. We can now go through your weekly replenishment report to ensure a good supply in your shop. To do so, navigate to the Inventory App &gt; Operations &gt; Replenishment. </p>
                <p>2. By clicking on the search bar, you can select the "Weekly replenishment" filter. It displays every products sold this week and their remaining quantity. </p>
                <p>3. Choose how much of each you want to buy by entering the value in the "To Order" column.</p>
                <p>4. Click then on the "Order" button to add it to your purchase orders. </p>
                <p>5. Navigate to the Purchase App. You can see that all purchase orders have been created and are ready to be sent to your distributors. Enter your purchase orders and send them to your vendors using the Send by Email button.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You can also use automated Reordering rules to ensure you will always have your best seller in stock. </p>
                        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase/products/reordering.html" target="_blank" class="btn btn-secondary">Learn more</a><br /></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>5. Encode new release</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>This time, you received a new release from one of your distributors. Prepare your scanner and go to the Barcode App.</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Or easier, download the Odoo App on your mobile phone, connect to your database, and select the Barcode App to transform your phone into an additional scanner!<br /></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p>1. Go to the Barcode App, and select "Operations".</p>
                <p>2. In "Receipts", create a new reception by clicking the "New" button. </p>
                <p>3. Scan your products. If it does not exist in your database, they will be created with the correct picture, title, and price. </p>
                <p>4. Enter the cost of each new product so you can easily reorder it afterward.</p>
                <p>5. Validate the reception, and this is it! (A purchase order will be automatically created so you can easily reconcile your vendor bills).</p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">📖</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you want to sale consignment products, this is standard in Odoo.</p>
                        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/warehouses_storage/advanced_operations_warehouse/owned_stock.html" target="_blank" class="btn btn-secondary">Learn more</a><br /></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h3>6. Returns</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>Time to return some unsold products. This works like a reverted purchase order.</p>
                <p>1. Go to the Purchase App. </p>
                <p>2. Create a new request for quotation, and start adding your products. </p>
                <p>3. Set the quantity in negative value to create a reverted purchase. </p>
                <p>You can now confirm the purchase, validate the delivery using the smart button, and print your delivery slip.</p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h3>7. Monitoring &amp; reporting</h3>
                <hr />
                <p>As monitoring your success is essential, there are some views that might interest you:</p>
                <p>1. View results</p>
                <ul>
                <li>​Track your sales order in Sales App &gt; Reporting &gt; Sales</li>
                <li>​Track your Point of Sales results in Point of Sales &gt; Reporting</li>
                <li>​Track your purchases performance in Purchase App &gt; Reporting &gt; Purchase</li>
                </ul>
                <p>2. Control your stock</p>
                <ul>
                <li>Get your stock level at anytime in Inventory &gt; Reporting &gt; Stock</li>
                <li>Navigate to Inventory &gt; Reporting &gt; Performance to get insight on each books categories</li>
                <li>Control the aging of your stock, and easily export aged stock in the inventory valuation report (Inventory &gt; Reporting &gt; Valuation).</li>
                </ul>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🎉</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs. </p>
                        <p>
                        Discover more about Odoo by diving into our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/">documentation</a> and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/all/tag/odoo-tutorials-9">academy</a> , and feel free
                        to <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">request a demo</a> if you need help!<br />
                        </p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <p><br /></p>
                <h1><span class="h1-fs">Do you want to go further?</span></h1>
                <hr />
                <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as : </p>
                <ul>
                <li>
                        A free, personalized, integrated <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website</font></strong> in a few clicks. Start receiving orders directly in Odoo and go live with your 
                        <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">E-shop</font></strong> in a few minutes.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)
                </li>
                <li>
                        Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Marketing Automation</font></strong>, <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font></strong>, 
                        <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Social Media Marketing</font></strong>, and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing</font></strong>.
                </li>
                <li>
                        Organise your events and connect with your customers easily with the<strong> <font class="text-o-color-1">Events App</font></strong>.
                </li>
                </ul>
                <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
                <p><br /></p>
                <div class="o_editor_banner o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-protected="true">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 ms-3" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further? </p>
                        <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a></p>
                </div>
                </div>
                <h1><br /></h1>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Bookstore</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="icon">📖</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[ ]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
