<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="product_product_10" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">19.44</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/14-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;First British Limited Edition hardcover, Bloomsbury Press.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9780747532699</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_11" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">The Mysteries of Nature: the Hidden Life of Trees (Hardcover)</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="weight">411.0</field>
        <field name="list_price">23.5</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/15-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;A NEW YORK TIMES WASHINGTON POST AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER - One of the most beloved books of our time: an illuminating account of the forest and the science that shows us how trees communicate feel and live in social networks. After reading this book a walk in the woods will never be the same again. Breaks entirely new ground.. [Peter Wohlleben] has listened to trees and decoded their language. Now he speaks for them. --The New York Review of Books NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY BRAINPICKINGS - HONORABLE MENTION: SEJ Rachel Carson Environment Book Award - Shortlisted: Audible International Book of the Year Award - Books For a Better Life Award - Indie Choice Award--Nonfiction Book of the Year Are trees social beings? In The Hidden Life of Trees forester and author Peter Wohlleben convincingly makes the case that yes the forest is a social network. He draws on groundbreaking scientific discoveries to describe how trees are like human families: tree parents live together with their children communicate with them support them as they grow share nutrients with those who are sick or struggling and even warn each other of impending dangers. Wohlleben also shares his deep love of woods and forests explaining the amazing processes of life death and regeneration that he has observed in his woodland. A declaration of love and an engrossing primer on trees brimming with facts and an unashamed awe for nature. --Washington Post Heavily dusted with the glitter of wonderment. --The New Yorker Includes a Note From a Forest Scientist by Dr.Suzanne Simard Published in Partnership with the David Suzuki Institute.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9781771642484</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_12" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">The Lean Startup</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">12.49</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/16-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;Most startups are built to fail. But those failures according to entrepreneur Eric Ries are preventable. Startups don t fail because of bad execution or missed deadlines or blown budgets. They fail because they are building something nobody wants. Whether they arise from someone s garage or are created within a mature Fortune 500 organization new ventures by definition are designed to create new products or services under conditions of extreme uncertainly. Their primary mission is to find out what customers ultimately will buy. One of the central premises of The Lean Startup movement is what Ries calls validated learning about the customer. It is a way of getting continuous feedback from customers so that the company can shift directions or alter its plans inch by inch minute by minute. Rather than creating an elaborate business plan and a product-centric approach Lean Startup prizes testing your vision continuously with your customers and making constant adjustments -- Every so often a business book comes along that changes how we think about innovation and entrepreneurship. Eric Ries s The Lean Startup has the chops to join this exalted company.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="weight">407.0</field>
        <field name="barcode">9780670921607</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_13" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">The Name of the Rose</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="x_author">Kurt Wolff</field>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">3.81</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/17-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;It is the year 1327. Franciscans in an Italian abbey are suspected of heresy, but Brother William of Baskerville’s investigation is suddenly overshadowed by seven bizarre deaths. Translated by William Weaver. A Helen and Kurt Wolff Book.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9780151446476</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_14" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">Narratives of Exile and Return</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="categ_id" ref="product_category_9"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">4.48</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/18-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;Excellent Marketplace listings for "Narratives of Exile and Return" by Chamber starting as low as $92.46!&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9780312164843</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_17" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">5% on your order</field>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="sale_ok" eval="False"/>
        <field name="purchase_ok" eval="False"/>
        <field name="list_price" eval="False"/>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_20" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">Media Burn: Ant Farm and the Making of an Image (Paperback)</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">22.03</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/24-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;A detailed account of Ant Farm s 1975 Media Burn performance a legendary act of consumerist critique This book examines the complex set of cultural references and art-making strategies informing Ant Farm s seminal 1975 performance Media Burn in which a customized Cadillac dubbed the Phantom Dream Car was driven through a wall of burning television sets. Originally conceived as a conceptual architectural practice Ant Farm evolved into a full-service art collaborative culminating in such notable works as House of the Century (1971-73) Cadillac Ranch (1974) and The Eternal Frame (1975). In Media Burn the artists flourished in a rich tumult of ideas that engaged contemporary media theory an oddly complicated aesthetic spectacle textual appropriation and an all-encompassing branding effort. Written by Steve Seid (Berkeley Art Museum/Pacific Film Archive) and drawing upon a rich visual documentation this book delves into the little-known critical backstory to this influential performance (and video work) involving a massive effort to mount a subversive critique of media hegemony while continually re-imagining the crux of the performance itself.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9781941753354</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_3" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">De Sapiens En Sapiens</field>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="x_author">André Chamay</field>
        <field name="categ_id" ref="product_category_36"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">17.0</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/3-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;André Chamay (Auteur) - Paru le 01/06/2019 chez Jets D'encre.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="barcode">9782355231254</field>
    </record>
    <record id="product_product_9" model="product.product">
        <field name="name">Da Vinci Code</field>
        <field name="is_storable" eval="1"/>
        <field name="available_in_pos" eval="True"/>
        <field name="pos_categ_ids" eval="[(6, 0, [ref('pos_category_1')])]"/>
        <field name="list_price">14.99</field>
        <field name="image_1920" type="base64" file="bookstore/static/src/binary/product_template/13-image_1920"/>
        <field name="purchase_method">receive</field>
        <field name="description">&lt;p&gt;A hand-inspected Used copy of "Da Vinci Code" by Dan Brown. Ships directly from Textbooks.com.&lt;/p&gt;</field>
        <field name="service_type">manual</field>
        <field name="invoice_policy">order</field>
        <field name="weight">1.0</field>
        <field name="standard_price">11.49</field>
        <field name="barcode">9780307474278</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
