<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
                <p><span class="display-4-fs"><strong>Odoo for Beverages distributor</strong></span>
                </p><p>
                Welcome to your new Odoo Drink Distributors package! This guide will help you navigate the key features and get your distribution business running smoothly, with a focus on inventory management, efficient operations, and online sales.
                </p><div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div><div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                        <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps. </p>
                        <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on Odoo.com/trial</p>
                </div>
                </div><p><br/></p><h2><span class="h1-fs">Basics</span></h2> <hr/><h3>Inventory Management 📦</h3><p>The Inventory app is the core of your distribution business:</p><ul>
                <li>Track stock levels across multiple warehouses</li>
                <li>Manage consignment for drinks sold in crates</li>
                <li>Process incoming and outgoing shipments</li>
                <li>Set up reordering rules for popular products</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Inventory</a></p><p><br/></p><h3>Deposit Management 🍻</h3><p>Manage your deposit more precisely and efficiently than ever before. </p><ul>
                <li>Create deposit products for each different type of consigns</li>
                <li>Apply DEP XX taxes to these consigns. </li>
                <li>Set a deposit product on your product to apply these taxes. This will ensure that you invoice correctly the price of consigns.</li></ul><div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>If you want to automatically split products sold in a specific packaging, precise a unit sale product in the so-called field and the number of units contained in the main product. </p>
                        <p>This will automatically create a Bill of Material and process a Manufacture Order each time you need to split your product and reflect this operation in your stock perfectly. </p>
                        <p>For example: </p>
                        <ul>
                        <li>Mobius Blanche - 24x33cl is your main product</li>
                        <li>Mobius Blanche - 33cl is the unit sale product</li>
                        <li>[FULL 33 BIN] Regular 24x33 Bin is the complete deposit product (4.5$ value)</li>
                        <li>[EMPTY 33 BIN] Regular 24x33 Bin is the empty deposit product (2.1$ value)</li>
                        </ul>
                        <p>Every time you need to sell a single Mobius Blanche - 33cl, if you don't have enough in stock, it will split your main product in 24 units and take into account an extra empty bin that will be left at the end. </p>
                        <p>The inventory of all products will be updated accordingly.</p>
                </div>
                </div><div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>This deposit management system is a specific features of this package. Proceed carefully if you need to adapt anything.</p>
                </div>
                </div><ul>
                <li>
                        Collect deposit when you deliver your customer. It is easy. When validating your delivery, you can directly set a "Return" and precisely count the number of each type of deposit your customer gave you. It will automatically be
                        reflected on his invoice or issue a credit note.
                </li>
                <li>You can also collect deposit directly on your Point of Sale. Select the correct product and encode a negative quantity.</li>
            </ul>
            <div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                    <p>The automated crate split based on BoM (defined from crate products with "contains" fields) is not supported from the bar (PoS).</p>
                    <p>As workarounds, you might:</p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Rely on the kit setup mentioned in the "Products and Bills of Material" section.</li>
                        <li>Manually convert crates into unit bottles at the bar on reception.</li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </div>
            <p><br/></p>
The deposit are as well supported with company branches!
Create your branches from your company settings: Navigate to Settings &gt; General Settings &gt; Companies &gt; Branches tab
For each of your branches, switch to its own view from the drop down list in the top bar
Create a warehouse for each branch: Go to Inventory &gt; Configuration &gt; Warehouses
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
        <p>The automations to create automated BoM and replenishment rules to split pack products into their unit products work only when setup after branches configuration as listed above. Make sure to properly define your branches and warehouses prior configuring your products.</p>
        <p>If you add a new branch since your expand (congratulations🙌), you will need to replicate the configuration of BoM and replinishment rules for already setup products.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/general/companies.html#general-companies-branches" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Branches</a></p>
<p><br/></p>
<h3>Excise Management 🧾</h3>
<p>In case you import or purchase products for which excises need to be recorded, you can handle it with this package.</p>
<p>Excise management consists in two dimensions in this package:</p>
<ul>
    <li>The maintenance of excise categories and the assignation of excises to products</li>
    <li>The reporting of received and delivered excise concerned products, a legal implication for any fiscal deposit</li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false" contenteditable="true">
        <p>When installing this module, all Fiscal Positions are set as Fiscal Deposit.<br/>Adjust the Fiscal Positions which are not to consider the Excise Taxes in your orders.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p><strong>Excise categories maintenance</strong></p>
<p>From the <strong>Inventory app</strong>, open the Excise categories from the menu Configuration / Excise Categories. <br/>Here you can define new and maintain existing excise categories.</p>
<p>Imagine you create a new category of products which need excise management...</p>
<ul>
    <li>Create a new excise category defining its name, description and reporting unit following the legislation which applies.</li>
</ul>
<p>Then create your product: </p>
<ul>
    <li>Define the required product fields. </li>
    <li>Assign the relevant excise category, input the Excise Amount and the Excise Quantity in the reporting unit and then save your product.</li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
    <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" contenteditable="true">
        <p>When you sell this product, the excise is accounted separately in a tax and summarised at the end of your sale orders, allowing you to offer clear discounts on your product irrespectively of the excise.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p><strong>Excise reporting</strong></p>
<p>On a regular basis, excises need to be declared. To support you with this duty, a report is setup to reach the quantity by excise category entering and exiting your fiscal deposit warehouse.</p>
<ul>
    <li>
        <p>Open the <strong>Inventory app</strong> and reach from the Reporting menu the Excises.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Entry from FD corresponds to products entering you fiscal deposit warehouse from the fiscal deposit of a supplier. To define such suppliers, adapt their fiscal position to handle excise tax.</li>
            <li>Exit to FD refers to products exiting your fiscal deposit warehouse to the fiscal deposit of a customer. To define such customers, adapt their fiscal position to handle excise tax.</li>
            <li>Exit means that products exited your fiscal deposit, to another warehouse of your or through a delivery to a customer without fiscal deposit warehouse.</li>
            <li>Entry is here in case you purchase products or are returned products not from a fiscal deposit warehouse. In such case, you ask for excise credits with your excise declaration.</li>
            <li>Transfer is here to handle the transfers between multiple fiscal deposit warehouses of yours.</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
</ul>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>Receipts and Deliveries from and to Partners having no Fiscal Position defined are handled with the product taxes.</p>
    </div>
</div>
<p>Remember that only stock moves to or from your fiscal deposit warehouses are reported here.<br/>This is normal not to see any move related to a sale from a front store warehouse since it is not a fiscal deposit for example.</p>
<p>You now have the keys to easily report those to the relevant authorities!</p>
<div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status" contenteditable="false" role="status">
    <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
    <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3" contenteditable="true">
        <p>The default breakdown is done by week and you can configure it to be by month if needed.</p>
    </div>
</div>
            <h3>Sales Management 🍾</h3><p>Use the Sales app to:</p><ul>
                <li>Manage your product catalog</li>
                <li>Create and track sales orders</li>
                <li>Set up pricing strategies for different customer segments</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Sales</a></p><p><br/></p><h3>Customer Relationship Management (CRM) 🤝</h3><p>The CRM app helps you:</p><ul>
                <li>Track leads and opportunities</li>
                <li>Manage your sales pipeline</li>
                <li>Follow up with potential clients</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 CRM</a><br/></p><h2><br/></h2><h3>Purchase Management 🛒</h3><p>The Purchase app allows you to:</p><ul>
                <li>Create purchase orders</li>
                <li>Manage supplier relationships</li>
                <li>Track incoming shipments</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm">🎓 Purchase</a></p><p><br/></p><h3>Point of Sale (POS) 💳</h3><p>For B2C sales, the POS app enables you to:</p><ul>
                <li>Process quick sales at your distribution center</li>
                <li>Handle returns and consignment easily</li>
                <li>Keep your inventory updated in real-time</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" target="_blank">🎓 Point of Sale</a></p><p><br/></p><h3>Barcode Scanning 📱</h3><p>The Barcode app enhances your inventory operations:</p><ul>
                <li>Scan products for quick data entry</li>
                <li>Perform efficient stock takes</li>
                <li>Streamline picking and packing processes</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/barcode.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" target="_blank">🎓 Barcode</a></p><p><br/></p><h3>eCommerce Website 🌐</h3><p>Your B2B eCommerce portal allows clients to:</p><ul>
                <li>Place orders online 24/7</li>
                <li>View their order history and reorder easily</li>
                <li>Access customer-specific pricing</li>
                </ul><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary btn-sm" target="_blank">🎓 Website</a></p><h2><br/></h2><div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>
                        <strong><span class="h2-fs">Tips for Success</span></strong>
                        </p>
                        <ul>
                        <li>Use barcode scanning for all inventory movements to ensure accuracy</li>
                        <li>Regularly update your website with new products and promotions</li>
                        <li>Train your team on efficient use of the barcode system in warehouse operations</li>
                        <li>Encourage your B2B clients to use the online ordering system for improved efficiency</li>
                        <li>Leverage the reporting tools across all apps to gain insights into your business performance</li>
                        </ul>
                </div>
                </div><h2><br/></h2><h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1> <hr/><p>Odoo offers additional possibilities to enhance your drink distribution business:</p><ul>
                <li>Implement the Quality app to ensure consistent product quality</li>
                <li>Utilize the Fleet app to manage your delivery vehicles efficiently</li>
                <li>Use the Marketing Automation app to nurture leads and promote new products</li>
                <li>Implement the Surveys app to gather customer feedback and improve your service</li>
                </ul><p>These features can be added to your current subscription. Feel free to explore and expand your Odoo experience!</p><p><br/></p><div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
                <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                        <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                        <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" target="_blank" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a><br/></p>
                </div>
                </div><p><br/></p> 
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
            <field name="name">Odoo for Beverages distributor</field>
            <field name="icon">🍾</field>
            <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="1"/>
            <field name="is_locked" eval="1"/>
            <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_9"/>
            <field name="cover_image_position">25.939</field>
            <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
            <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
