<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1><strong><span class="display-4-fs">Odoo for Physical Therapy</span></strong></h1>
        <p>Welcome to the Odoo Physical Therapy package!</p>
        <p>This industry package is designed specifically for physical therapy and rehabilitation practices, including kinesiotherapists, physiotherapists, osteopaths, and other rehabilitation and therapy professionals, helping you manage your patients, appointments, and billing in one fully integrated system.</p>
        <p>By installing this package, you gain access to a set of essential applications, including CRM, Appointments, Calendar, and Invoicing, allowing you to focus on patient care while Odoo handles your daily operations.</p>
        <p>Getting Started
            To begin, you'll find the key applications you need on your Odoo dashboard. Let's take a closer look at how you can use these tools.
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <br/>
        <h2><span class="h1-fs"><strong>Basics</strong></span></h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM App</font></strong>(Customer Relationship Management) helps you manage patient inquiries and follow-ups.</li>
            <li>The <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Appointments App</font><font class="text-black"><span style="font-weight: normal;"> manages your appointment types and allows patients to book consultation.</span></font><font class="text-o-color-1"></font></strong></li>
            <li><strong><font class="text-black"><span style="font-weight: normal;">Manage your schedule and your availability in the </span></font><font class="text-o-color-1">Calendar App</font><font class="text-black"><span style="font-weight: normal;">.</span></font></strong></li>
            <li>Ease your invoicing process with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Invoice App</font></strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone to manage your entire business in it.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2><span class="display-4-fs"><strong><font class="text-800"><span class="h1-fs">Use Case</span></font></strong></span></h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various flows you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Pysical Therapy package and check the related box.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3>1. Create a new opportunity</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>You receive a call from a new patient, Emily, who is experiencing lower back pain and would like to consult a kinesiotherapist.</p>
        <p>In the <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>CRM App</strong></font>, you create a new opportunity for Emily, recording her contact details and the reason for consultation (e.g. back pain, postural issues, rehabilitation).</p>
        <p>As you review her needs, you move the opportunity to Qualified, indicating that a consultation is required.</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You can also configure an email alias so everyone sending email to this one will create a new opportunity for you.</p>
                <p>To do so, go to CRM &gt; Configuration &gt; Sales Teams.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3>2. Book an appointment</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>From Emily's opportunity in the CRM, you can invite her to book her first session in just a few clicks.</p>
        <p>Using the Chatter on the right side of the opportunity, click <strong>Send a message</strong>, select the “<strong>Book your next appointment</strong>” email template, and send it to the patient. The email contains a direct booking link, allowing the patient to select an available time slot and book the appointment online.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🌐</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>You may also create a personalized website in a few clicks by adding the Website App, your appointment page will be automatically added.</p>
                <p><a href="/odoo/apps" class="btn btn-primary">Let's Try</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>All emails sent and received are automatically recorded in the <strong>Chatter</strong>, giving you a clear history of your communication with the patient. Once the patient books an appointment, it is automatically synchronized across CRM, Appointments, and Calendar, keeping your schedule up to date without manual work.</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You can easily adapt this flow using automations. For example:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                    <p>When an opportunity moves to <strong>“Qualified”</strong>, automatically send the booking email to the patient</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                    <p>When an appointment is completed, automatically send a follow-up email suggesting the next session</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>To configure this, click the <strong>gear icon</strong> at the top of a CRM column and select <strong>Automation</strong>, or add automated emails directly in the <strong>Appointment Type</strong> settings.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>For treatment plans that require multiple sessions (for example, 10 sessions prescribed by a doctor), go to the <strong>Calendar App</strong>, create an appointment, assign the patient, and set it as recurring.</p>
                <p>By doing this, the corresponding time slots are automatically reserved and will no longer be available on the public booking link, ensuring your availability remains accurate.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🪂</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>To reduce your no show rate drastically, appointments automatically comes with reminders by Email and SMS.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3>3. Verify your schedule</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Once an appointment is booked, you can see it in the <strong>Calendar App</strong>.</p>
        <p>From there, you can:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Move or reschedule the appointment (the patient is notified automatically)</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Cancel a session</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Block time slots for treatments or personal availability</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>The <strong>Appointments App</strong> and <strong>Calendar App</strong> are fully synchronized, ensuring your availability is always up to date.</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>The Odoo Calendar App is compatible with Outlook and Google Calendar. Activate the sync in the Calendar App settings.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3>4. Take notes during your appointment</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>During or after a therapy session, you can easily record clinical notes:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>Use <strong>Log Note</strong> on the patient's contact to keep internal treatment notes</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Create a dedicated <strong>knowledge article</strong> for each patient to track progress, exercises, or treatment plans</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To follow up on a patient's treatment plan, you can quickly see how many sessions have already been completed by clicking the <strong>Appointments stat button</strong> on the patient’s contact form.</p>
                <p>
                    This is especially useful when sessions are prescribed by a doctor and need to be tracked accurately.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-protected="true" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>Be careful, using the "Log Note" in your contact will be displayed only for you and your eventual team. If you select the "Send message" option, this will notify your customer (which can be really interesting also).</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h3>5. Check your invoices</h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>If you navigate to the Invoice App, you can manage your invoices. You have many possibilities to streamline your invoicing process:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Auto-post your invoice on a regular basis.</li>
            <li>Add an upfront payment in your Appointment Type.</li>
            <li>Invoice yourself, manually.</li>
            <li>Add the Subscription App and invoice automatically based on a subscription type.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you only need to invoice part of a session or treatment plan to the patient (for example, X% paid by the patient while the rest is covered by insurance or a mutual fund), you can use a down payment.</p>
                <p>
                    The down payment is deducted from the final invoice, keeping billing clear and accurate for both the patient and the insurer.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p>
                <p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help! <br/></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <h2><span class="h1-fs"><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></span></h2>
        <hr/>
        <p>Odoo offers you infinite possibilities, such as:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Automated recurring invoicing with the <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Subscription App</font></strong>.</li>
            <li>Create a professional <font class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Website</strong></font> for your practice and allow patients to book appointments online.</li>
            <li>Manage your team's and integrate them in all processes by adding the<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Employees App</font></strong>.</li>
            <li>Manage your accounting easier than ever with a completely integrated environment. (<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Accounting App</font></strong>)</li>
            <li>Manage all your communication channels in one place with Odoo<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Marketing Automation </font></strong>,<strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font></strong>,<strong><font class="text-o-color-1"> Social Media Marketing </font></strong>, and <strong><font class="text-o-color-1">SMS Marketing </font></strong>.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <br/>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Odoo for Physical Therapy</field>
        <field name="icon">👩‍⚕️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">52.40000000000001</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
  </odoo>
