<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <p><span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent; font-weight: 700; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none; font-size: 24px;">The Arts and Crafts Shop</span></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;">
            <span style="font-size: 13pt; color: #000000; background-color: transparent; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none;"></span>
            <span class="text-o-color-2" style="background-color: transparent; font-weight: 400; font-style: normal; text-decoration: none;">
                <font class="text-800">
                    Tailored specifically for the world of creativity, this Odoo industry package offers a complete solution for arts and crafts stores. It effectively manages a diverse range of inventory with complex variants, ensuring that you can always meet customer demand for specific colors or materials. The system integrates powerful tools for POS and eCommerce, making it easier to run your store efficiently both online and offline. It is the essential tool for combining artistic passion with professional business management.
                </font>
            </span>
            <p>
                <font class="text-800"></font><br/>
            </p>
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <p style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><b style="font-weight: normal;"></b><br/></p>
        <h1><strong>Activities</strong><span class="h1-fs"> </span> </h1>
        <hr/>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">To get a rapid understanding of the processes this Odoo package offers, you can execute the following flows and configure the settings to suit your Arts &amp; Crafts Store.</p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3"> <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Arts &amp; Crafts Store package and select the relevant checkbox</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <h3> <br/> </h3>
        </ul>
        <h3><br/></h3>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage Customers &amp; Special Offers🤝</span></h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Manage your entire customer database and view individual profiles to take direct action from the contact module.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Track Promotion Eligibility:</b> Instantly see exactly which active rewards and promotional programs a specific customer can access.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Generate Membership Barcodes:</b> Link a unique barcode to a customer’s digital or physical membership card for seamless scanning at your Point of Sale (POS).</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>From the Sales App</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Centralize Rewards:</b> Effortlessly build, monitor, and manage your entire ecosystem of loyalty campaigns and promotional programs from one dashboard.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status"> <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><b>Ready to take it a step further?</b> Explore the <b>Membership</b> and <b>Pricelists</b> features to easily manage exclusive pricing for your members.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage your products️ 📦</span> </h3>
        <hr/>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Odoo enables complete control over your <b>product catalog</b> and<strong> basic </strong><b>stock management</b>, ensuring your inventory data is always accurate.</p>
        <h4 style="text-align: justify;"> <u>Create and Categorize Products</u> </h4>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Start by creating your products within the <b>Products</b> tab, filling in all necessary details. The system uses three distinct categories to provide maximum flexibility across your business:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Product Category:</b> For internal tracking and reporting.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>E-commerce Category:</b> For easier product retrieval by customers on your online store.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Point of Sale Category:</b> For organizing transactions within your shop system.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"> <b>Key Product Settings:</b> </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    Accurately <b>update the inventoried quantity</b>.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Decide whether to allow sales of <b>out-of-stock products</b>.</p>
            </li>
            <p style="text-align: justify;"> </p>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status"> <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🚀</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>The current setup keeps things simple by using basic product counts to track stock. If you need more power, the <b>Inventory app</b> introduces advanced features like barcode scanning, location tracking, and serial number management.</p>
                <p><b>Note:</b> Increased capability leads to higher complexity and more maintenance.</p>
                <p><b>Our Advice:</b> Stick with your current streamlined configuration until you’re fully comfortable. When you're ready to upgrade, try the Inventory module on a duplicated database first to ensure it fits your workflow. 😉</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><br/></h3>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Selling in the Store 🛍️</span> </h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Odoo’s <strong>Point of Sale (POS)</strong> system ensures fast and smooth transactions in your shop.</p>
        <p> <strong> <u>Process</u> </strong> </p>
        <ul>
            <li style="text-align: justify;"><strong></strong>To start an order in your Point of Sale (POS) session, scan or select all items. </li>
            <li style="text-align: justify;">Select the customer to apply the appropriate coupons.</li>
            <li>
                <p>Accept multiple payment options: cash, card, and mobile payments.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Generate printed or digital receipts for customers.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h3> <span class="h2-fs">Selling Online 💻️</span> </h3>
        <hr/>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Your E-commerce setup involves three main areas: <b>Product Settings</b>, <b>Website-Wide Settings</b>, and <b>Payment &amp; Delivery Methods</b>.</p>
        <h4 style="text-align: justify;"> <u>1. Configure Products and Their Display</u> </h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Publishing:</b> Each product can be <b>published independently</b> on your online store.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Product-Level Settings:</b> Define core product settings directly on the <b>product form</b>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Layout Settings:</b> Adjust the visual presentation and layout of products using the <b>website editor</b>.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4 style="text-align: justify;"> <u>2. Review General E-commerce Policies</u> </h4>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Navigate to <b>Website Settings</b> to configure global e-commerce policies.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Crucial Review:</b> You must review all e-commerce settings to ensure they align with your internal business policies (e.g., when invoices are generated, whether a mandatory customer check-in is required for ordering, etc.).</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4 style="text-align: justify;"> <u>3. Set Up Payment and Delivery</u> </h4>
        <p style="text-align: justify;">Use the <b>Website &gt; Configuration</b> menu to enable all your transaction options.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Payment Providers &amp; Methods:</b> Go to <b>Website &gt; Configuration &gt; Payment Providers</b> and install <b>all</b> the payment methods and payment providers you plan to offer (e.g., credit card processors, PayPal, etc.).</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>Delivery Methods:</b> Go to <b>Website &gt; Configuration &gt; Delivery Methods</b> to define all available options and their costs.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>External Providers:</b> Check if a predefined Odoo connection exists if you work with specific shipping carriers.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p style="text-align: justify;"><b>In-Store Pickup (Click &amp; Collect):</b> If you wish to offer this, you must <b>activate the setting</b> within the <b>Website Settings</b> first.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p> <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory/shipping_receiving/setup_configuration.html"> <span style="font-weight: normal;">🎓 Delivery Methods</span> </a></p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage Purchases 🛒</span><br/></h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Track and oversee your entire procurement workflow directly within the <b>Purchase App</b>. The moment you confirm a receipt, your stock levels update automatically.</p>
        <p><b>Want to automate your purchasing?</b> &gt; Integrate the <b>Inventory App</b> to unlock automated reordering. Keep in mind while expanding your ecosystem provides much greater capability, it also introduces more advanced configurations to manage.</p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Manage Events &amp; Email Marketing🧑‍🤝‍🧑</span></h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Connecting the <b>Event App</b> with <b>Email Marketing</b> gives you a powerful toolkit to launch events and drive registrations simultaneously.</p>
        <h3>🎟️ Inside the Event App</h3>
        <p>Set your event logistics and rules in just a few clicks:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Logistics &amp; Pricing:</b> Define ticket prices, event times, and capacity limits.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Registration &amp; Launch:</b> Choose how attendees sign up and publish the event page directly to your website.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3>📧 Inside the Email Marketing App</h3>
        <p>Turn your contact database into an audience:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Targeted Outbound:</b> Launch promotional campaigns tailored to specific mailing lists.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Direct Redirection:</b> Embed high-converting call-to-action (CTA) buttons that send readers straight to your event registration page.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status"> <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p><b>Ready to scale your reach?</b> Explore the <b>SMS Marketing</b>, <b>Social Marketing</b>, and <b>Marketing Automation</b> apps to build advanced, multi-channel campaigns.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><br/></h3>
        <h3 style="text-align: justify;"><span class="h2-fs">Manage your Website 🌐</span></h3>
        <hr/>
        <p>Build an online presence that adapts perfectly to your clients' needs. Odoo gives you the flexibility to easily integrate internal policies, customize forms, showcase your latest products, and so much more—no coding required.</p>
        <h3>✍️ Expand with a Custom Blog</h3>
        <p>Want to share industry insights or boost your SEO? Easily add a beautifully designed blog. Odoo’s website ecosystem offers endless layout and design options for a fully customized look and feel.</p>
        <h3>🔄 Connect Your Front-End to Your Pipeline</h3>
        <p>Your website doesn't just sit there—it actively helps to grow your business.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Automated Lead Generation:</b> Every submission on your "Contact Us" page instantly creates a brand-new opportunity in your <b>CRM App</b>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>From the CRM app:</b> Track client interactions in real time and use the <b>Sales App</b> to quickly send tailored quotations for B2B leads or custom customer requests.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary" rel="noreferrer">🎓 Website</a></p>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
        <h1 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></h1>
        <hr/>
        <p>Once your core operations are running smoothly, consider expanding your toolset:</p>
        <p>Want to do more?</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Accounting:</b> Automatically log payments, close sessions, and generate tax reports.</p>
            </li>
            <li><b>Payroll:</b> Use this feature to handle <b>employee salaries and manage holiday requests</b>.</li>
        </ul>
        <div data-oe-protected="true" class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status"> <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div data-oe-protected="false" class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p> <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a> </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify;"><br/></p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Arts &amp; Crafts Store</field>
        <field name="icon">🖌️</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True" />
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_3"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">41.40999999999994</field>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
