<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Coworking</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[<h1 data-heading-link-id="599577253909"><strong>Odoo for Coworking</strong></h1><p>Welcome to the Odoo Coworking Management package!</p><p>This suite of applications is designed to meet the needs of coworking spaces; whether you manage a boutique shared office, a multi-location coworking hub, or a community-driven workspace. With Odoo, you can centralize your operations in one place: from selling memberships and booking meeting rooms to engaging your community and organizing staff schedules.</p><p>With fully integrated apps such as CRM, Subscription, Website, Events, Helpdesk, and Planning, the solution streamlines daily management, enhances member services, and keeps your workspace running efficiently.</p><p>Focus on growing your coworking community, while Odoo takes care of the logistics. 💼</p><div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div><h2 data-heading-link-id="78703582913"><strong>Basics</strong><br></h2><p>You can access every installed app in your Odoo database from your main dashboard.</p><ul>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM &amp; Membership</font>: </strong>Track and manage coworking opportunities, follow-up, and convert them into active members.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Subscription</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Automate recurring memberships such as Business Address or Unlimited Monthly Access.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Generate and manage quotations for memberships, room bookings, and services.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Appointment</font></strong>&nbsp;: Allow prospects to book a free tour, shared desk, or meeting room online.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Website</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Promote coworking offers, showcase events, and provide member-exclusive tools and support forms.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Events</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Organize networking sessions, workshops, and community-building activities.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Email Marketing</font></strong>&nbsp;: Share news, updates, and promotions with your members.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Helpdesk</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Handle member requests and issues efficiently.</p></li>
<li><p><strong><font class="text-o-color-1">Planning</font>:&nbsp;</strong>Schedule reception desk coverage and other staff shifts.</p></li>
</ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
                </div>
            </div><h2 data-heading-link-id="615995671064"><strong>Use Case</strong></h2><p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p><p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p><p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p><div data-oe-role="status" class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
                <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                    <p><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Coworking&nbsp;Package </strong>and check the related box.</p>
                </div>
            </div><h3 data-heading-link-id="567035561385"><strong>Create and Sell Your Coworking Offers</strong></h3><p>Whether it’s a day pass, monthly membership, or virtual office service, Odoo makes setup and sales easy.</p><ol data-heading-link-id="1357542049814"><li>Create Your Products: Set up flexible coworking options for your clients:</li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li><strong>Business Address</strong> → subscription product for a registered business address.</li><li><strong>One-Day Pass</strong> → simple service product for single-day coworking access.</li><li><strong>10-Day Pass</strong> → product linked to a loyalty card (prepaid pack of 10 days).</li><li><strong>Monthly Unlimited Membership</strong> → subscription-based product for unlimited monthly access.<br><br></li></ol></li><li><u></u>Set Pricelists: Create a pricelist for unlimited members, for example: <strong>100% discount on coworking days</strong>, <strong>20% off meeting rooms</strong>, and <strong>10% off event space rentals</strong>.<br><br></li><li>Assign Membership Levels Automatically</li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li>Set the product type to <strong>Service – Membership / Partnership</strong> for subscription offers (Business Address and Unlimited monthly access).</li><li>Link each product to its corresponding <strong>Membership Level</strong>.</li><li>Link the Membership Level to a specific <strong>Pricelist</strong> (e.g., €0 for coworking days if included in Unlimited).<br>→ When a client buys the subscription, they are automatically assigned the level and related pricelist. On their portal, they’ll see eligible coworking access at the correct price (such as €0/day with Unlimited).<br><br></li></ol></li><li>Automate Renewals: For recurring plans like <strong>Business Address</strong> or <strong>Monthly Unlimited Memberships</strong>, activate automatic renewal using the <strong>Subscriptions</strong> module.<br><br></li><li>Manage Cancellations: Set an end date for the subscription to close automatically, or allow clients to cancel anytime via their Odoo portal.<br><br></li><li data-heading-link-id="303438730941">Use Loyalty Cards for Day Pass Packs</li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li>Create a product “10-Day Coworking Card”.</li><li>Go to <strong>Discount &amp; Loyalty</strong> and create a new <strong>Loyalty Card</strong>.</li><li>Set a Loyalty Rule to give <strong>10 points</strong> when the product is purchased.</li><li>Set a Reward where <strong>1 point = 100% discount on 1 coworking day</strong>.<br>→ As the client books coworking days, they apply their points at checkout. Once all 10 points are used, the standard day price applies for future bookings.</li></ol></li></ol><h3 data-heading-link-id="895436721524"><strong>Manage and Track Membership Opportunities</strong></h3><p>From first contact to confirmed member:</p><ol>
<li><p><strong>Website Form:</strong>&nbsp;</p></li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li><p>Create a “Contact Us for Membership” form on your website.</p></li><li><p>Configure it so each submission creates an <strong>opportunity</strong> in <strong>CRM</strong>.</p></li></ol></li>
<li><p><strong>Appointment Booking:</strong>&nbsp;</p></li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li><p>Allow prospects to schedule a free tour or trial desk online.</p></li><li><p>Each booking automatically generates an opportunity in CRM.</p></li></ol></li>
<li><p><strong>Follow-Up:</strong> Track the opportunity in the CRM pipeline, add notes, schedule calls or meetings.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Convert to Member:</strong> Once confirmed, create a quotation or start a subscription plan.</p></li>
</ol><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                    <p>&nbsp;Tag opportunities by interest type (e.g., “Day Pass,” “Private Office”) for better reporting.</p>
                </div>
            </div><h3 data-heading-link-id="211068273608"><strong>Automate Quotations &amp; Invoicing</strong></h3><p>Send quotes and invoices automatically.</p><ol><li>Send <strong>professional offers</strong> for meeting room packages, private offices, or custom services.</li><li>For subscriptions (monthly/yearly), invoices are generated and sent <strong>automatically</strong>.</li><li>Enable online <strong>payment methods</strong> (credit card, bank transfer) for convenience.</li></ol><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Offer discounts for yearly prepayments by creating a separate subscription plan.</p>
                </div>
            </div><h3 data-heading-link-id="277845278221"><strong>Stay Connected with Your Community</strong></h3><p>Keep your members informed and connected with emails and events.</p><ol><li>Send members the new Wi-Fi code, upcoming events, and important updates via <strong>Email Marketing</strong>.&nbsp;</li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li>Create a new mailing.</li><li>Select recipients using filters like Members, Prospects, or Event Attendees.</li><li>Design your message with the drag-and-drop editor.</li><li>Personalize content using dynamic fields (e.g., member name, booked room).</li><li>Send or schedule your email and track opens and clicks.</li></ol></li><li>Let members report issues (e.g., coffee machine broken, Wi-Fi down) via a website form and manage all requests in the <strong>Helpdesk app</strong>.</li><li><strong>Event Creation:</strong> Organize networking nights, workshops, or skill-sharing sessions; publish them on your website and allow online registration.</li><li class="oe-nested"><ol><li>Create events for members or the public.</li><li>Set time slots, ticket types, and attendance limits if needed.</li><li>Choose event visibility: make it public or accessible only to members via a shared link.</li><li>Customize the event page on your website with all the details (location, agenda, facilities).</li><li>Share event links via email or social media so members and guests can sign up easily.</li></ol></li></ol><h3 data-heading-link-id="1754494750762"><strong>Keep Your Website Engaging &amp; Member-Friendly</strong></h3><p>Your website is both your public shop window and private member space.</p><ul>
<li><p>Create public pages for coworking offers and event highlights.</p></li>
<li><p>Make <strong>member-only pages</strong> for internal events, resources, or booking links.</p><p>
 1. In Website → Pages, edit the page.</p><p>
 2. Under <strong>Visibility</strong>, set “Visible for” to a specific group (e.g., Members).</p></li>
<li><p>Hide booking options (e.g., meeting rooms) from non-members.</p></li></ul><h3 data-heading-link-id="435008030097"><strong>Schedule Your Reception &amp; Support Staff</strong></h3><p>Keep front desk operations running smoothly.</p><ol>
<li><p>Define <strong>Operating Hours</strong> (e.g., 8am–8pm, Monday–Friday).</p></li>
<li><p>Create and assign roles such as “Front Desk,” “Cleaning,” or “Event Support.” to employees in their records.</p></li><li><p>Use <strong>Auto-Plan</strong> to assign shifts based on availability.</p></li>
<li><p>Staff can view schedules in their portal or by email.</p></li>
<li><p>Make last-minute updates via drag-and-drop.</p></li></ol><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">🎉</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3"><p>You completed that demo use case! There are millions of other ways to adapt your Odoo setup to fit your business needs.</p><p>Discover more about Odoo by diving into our<a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/"> documentation </a>and <a href="https://www.odoo.com/slides/getting-started-15">academy</a>, and feel free to<a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus"> request a demo </a>if you need help!</p></div>
            </div><h2 data-heading-link-id="148297113146"><strong>Do You Want to Go Further?</strong></h2><p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your Coworking&nbsp;company:</p><ul><li>Use <strong>Rental</strong> to support a "Private office" offer in your coworking.</li><li>Manage all finances in one place with automatic entries from sales and subscriptions using <strong>Accounting</strong>.</li><li>Promote your space, events, and member stories on social media directly from <strong>Social Marketing</strong>.</li><li>Track and schedule repairs for equipment like printers, or coffee machines with <strong>Maintenance</strong>.</li><li>Manage walk-in visitors, check-ins, and instant bookings for desks or rooms using <strong>Front Desk</strong>.</li></ul><div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
                <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
                <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                    <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p><p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
                </div>
            </div><p><br></p>]]></field>
    <field name="icon">💻</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_15"/>
    <field name="cover_image_position">55.19999999999999</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="category">workspace</field>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
</record>
  </odoo>
