<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.1">Art Gallery</h1>
        <p>Welcome to the <strong>Odoo Art Galleries Package!</strong></p>
        <p>
            This package is ideal for any art gallery—whether you specialize in classic paintings, contemporary sculptures, or digital art collections. We will help you can engage collectors and prospective artists, manage purchases and
            conveniently sell online or in your art space. This guide will help you run your gallery efficiently with Odoo’s integrated tools.<br />
            <br />
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>Basics</h2>
        <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database from your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Website &amp; eCommerce</strong>: Your gallery’s online storefront, where customers can browse and purchase artworks anytime, anywhere.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>CRM</strong>: Manages customer relationships, tracks leads and inquiries, and boosts sales potential.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Sales</strong>: Validates orders, creates custom quotations, and streamlines the sales process.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>POS</strong>: Enables fast, in-store transactions for walk-in customers.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Contacts</strong>: Organizes and stores client information for personalized follow-ups.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Purchase</strong>: Helps manage vendor relationships and streamline procurement processes.</p>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <p><br /></p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>If you want to explore all features easily, try downloading the Demo Data in your Odoo database. However, once uploaded, demo data cannot be easily deleted, so consider testing it in a trial environment first.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><br /></h3>
        <h3>From Opportunity to Invoice 🤩</h3>
        <p>Since you have an integrated website, customer inquiries submitted via the contact form are automatically recorded as opportunities.</p>
        <p>A potential buyer has inquired about an artwork—how exciting! Let’s go through the steps to turn this inquiry into a sale.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong>, where you will find the new opportunity in the "New" stage.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Click on the opportunity to open its details.</p></li>
            <li><p>Use the "Send Message" button in the chatter to communicate with the client and gather necessary details.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Once the customer expresses interest, click <strong>"New Quotation"</strong> to generate a price proposal.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>
                    Important:<strong><br /></strong><br />
                    The <strong>Customer</strong> field is not required when creating an opportunity, but it must be filled before sending a quotation.<br />
                    <br />
                    If the field is empty, Odoo will prompt you to:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Create a new customer.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Link to an existing customer.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Proceed without linking, but no customer details will be stored.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>Once the customer confirms, you can send the <strong>Sales Order</strong>—congratulations on selling an artwork! For more details, check the official documentation on sending and creating quotations.</p>
        <h3>Adding Artwork to Your Collection 🎨</h3>
        <p>Once you acquire a new piece of art, adding it to your collection ensures proper inventory tracking and availability online.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create a Product</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Open the <strong>Inventory App</strong> and go to "Products" &gt; "New".</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Enter the artwork’s name, description and relevant attributes such as the artist or era.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>If it's a unique piece, set the quantity to <strong>1</strong>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            For multiple prints in a series, set the correct quantity.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Add Images &amp; Categorization</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Upload high-quality images of the artwork.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Assign the correct <strong>Product Category</strong> (e.g., Paintings, Sculptures, Prints).</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Set an <strong>eCommerce Category</strong> if you want it to be available for sale online.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Manage Online Visibility</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>If you want the piece available for online purchase, check <strong>"Available in eCommerce"</strong>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Set pricing and any applicable shipping details.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Publish the Artwork</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Click the "Go to Website" button to preview the product page.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Once satisfied, switch the <strong>"Published"</strong> toggle to make it live.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>In our Demo Data, we added <strong>Product Attributes</strong> such as Artist and Condition which your customers can filter by to find exactly what they are looking for. <strong> </strong></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>
            <br />
            Selling Art Online 🖼️
        </h3>
        <p>Selling art online is easy with Odoo’s <strong>Website &amp; eCommerce</strong> modules.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>Website App</strong> to create a visually stunning online gallery.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Add detailed product pages with high-resolution images, descriptions, and pricing.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Enable <strong>eCommerce features</strong> to accept payments and process customer orders.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Offer multiple payment options for convenience.</p></li>
            <li>
                <p>Use the <strong>Customer Portal</strong> to provide buyers with order history and invoices.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>You can also set up limited-edition collections or VIP access sales with <strong>Memberships &amp; Subscriptions</strong>.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Selling in the Gallery 🏪</h3>
        <p>For in-gallery sales, use <strong>Point of Sale (POS)</strong> for quick and seamless transactions.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>Open the <strong>POS App</strong> and select "Open Register" to begin sales.</p>
            </li>
            <li><p>Scan artwork barcodes or manually select items for checkout.</p></li>
            <li><p>Accept various payment methods, including cash, credit cards, and mobile payments.</p></li>
            <li><p>Capture customer details for future engagement.</p></li>
            <li><p>Automatically synchronize inventory with your online store.</p></li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>
                    To ensure your POS is set up correctly, follow the official guide:<br />
                    <br />
                        <a class="btn btn-fill-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/point_of_sale/configuration.html">POS Configuration</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3><br /></h3>
        <h3>Purchasing New Artworks 🎨</h3>
        <p>Acquiring new pieces for your gallery is seamless with <strong>CRM</strong> and the <strong>Purchase App</strong>.</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Track New Artwork Opportunities</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong> and create a new opportunity for the artist or supplier.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Enter details about the artwork, including style, artist, and potential pricing.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Use the chatter to discuss pricing, terms, and availability with the seller.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create a Purchase Order</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Once the artwork is confirmed, open the <strong>Purchase App</strong>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Click "New Purchase Order" and select the vendor (artist or supplier).</p></li>
                    <li><p>Add the artwork as a product, specifying quantity, price, and expected delivery date.</p></li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Confirm the purchase order and send it to the vendor.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Receive the Artwork</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>When the artwork arrives, go to the <strong>Purchase App</strong> and mark the order as received.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Update the inventory by adding the new piece to your catalogue.<br />
                            <br />
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Accounting &amp; Payments</strong>:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Generate a vendor bill in the <strong>Accounting App</strong>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Process payments according to agreed terms.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Keep track of expenses and ensure proper financial reporting.</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3><strong>Managing Commissions  👩‍🎨</strong></h3>
        <p>Managing consigned artworks efficiently ensures accurate sales tracking and commission payments.</p>
        <p><strong>1. Set up your commission plans</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Go to CRM → Configuration → Commission Plans</li>
            <li>Create the Commission Plans for the various split rates</li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>In the existing data, 50% Split Rate, and 5% Artist's Resale Right are provided as examples</li>
                    <li>Define the Product Category on which this applies, and the Rate (in percentage)</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>Define your Partner Levels</li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>Partner levels are Commission Plan categories, and have default commission plans</li>
                    <li>Partner Activation can be ignored for now. </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>2. <strong>Set up your Contacts</strong></p>
        <ul>
            <li>In your contacts, go to the "Partner Assignment" tab</li>
            <li>Define a partner level, and a default commission plan, as well as the activation level</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>Add tags to your contacts to make it easy to sort between Artists and Customers</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>3. <strong>Configure your art pieces</strong></p>
        <p>Since we applied the commission rate management to specific product categories, it is also necessary to assign the relevant product categories to the products</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Go to Sales → Products → Products</li>
            <li>On the "Category" field, define the Category to "Commissions / Standard Split Rate", for example</li>
        </ul>
        <p>4. <strong>Sell &amp; Manage commissions easily</strong></p>
        <p>
            Next up, all you need to do is make the sale, and specify the referrer on the sale order. Once the order is confirmed and invoiced, a <strong>Purchase Order</strong> will be created in parallel, to that specific vendor, with the
            associated commission.
        </p>
        <p>This process ensures <strong>transparent consignment management</strong>, allowing the gallery to sell artworks efficiently while accurately handling payments and commissions.</p>
        <h3 class="flex"><strong>Manage your agreements 📝</strong></h3>
        <div class="flex">Manage your Artist Consignment agreements through the <b>Sign app. </b>Upload new templates, and easily send and manage your agreements from one place. </div>
        <div class="flex"><br /></div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <div>You can send contracts from any app, by clicking the <strong>cogwheel icon, then "Request Signature". </strong></div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="flex"><br /></div>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <p>
                    <span class="h2-fs"><strong>Additional Tips for Success</strong></span>
                </p>
                <p>Setting the price of an artwork to "0" will replace the "Add to Cart" button with a link to your contact form if you use this configuration.</p>
                <p>
                    Integrate all sells and purchase flows directly in Odoo. Thanks to our extensive localization library, we can even generate your tax reports for you. <strong></strong>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/fiscal_localizations.html">extensive localization library</a><strong></strong>,<strong> </strong>we can even generate your tax reports for you at the click of
                    a button!
                </p>
                <p>You can make your product pages even nicer by adding additional images for eCommerce You can make your product pages even nicer by adding <strong>additional images for eCommerce.</strong></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h2>
            <br />
            Do You Want to Go Further?
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Events</strong>: Organize art exhibitions, artist meet-ups, and gallery openings.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Marketing Automation</strong>: Engage potential buyers with personalized campaigns and newsletters.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Memberships &amp; Subscriptions</strong>: Offer exclusive content, VIP access, and limited-event participation.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Projects</strong>: Manage large-scale exhibitions or arts festivals, integrating planning, tasks, and team collaboration.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Email &amp; Social Marketing</strong>: Promote upcoming exhibitions and special sales across different platforms</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>Accounting:Accounting:Accounting:<strong></strong> Easily generate tax reports and other financial documents thanks to our localization packages.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editable">
                <h2><strong>Extending the Workflow with Studio</strong></h2>
                <p>For galleries that want further automation and customization, the <strong>Studio App</strong> can be installed. This allows for:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Automated Commission Calculation: Set up a field that automatically calculates the commission based on the sales price and artist agreement.<br />
                        <br />
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Custom Consignment Agreements: Generate custom contracts for each artist, outlining commission rates, exclusivity, and sales terms.<br />
                        <br />
                    </li>
                    <li>Creative Document Layouts: Modify invoices, sales orders, and consignment reports to match gallery branding or provide a clear breakdown of commissions.</li>
                    <li class="oe-nested">
                        <br />
                        <br />
                        Please note that Odoo Studio is only available with a custom plan. For more information on this, please refer to our <a href="https://www.odoo.com/pricing">official website</a>.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-primary">Reach us</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
        <hr />
        <p>
            To be sure to stay updated, follow us on
            <a href="https://twitter.com/Odoo"><span style="font-weight: bolder;">X</span></a>,
            <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCkQPikELWZFLgQNHd73jkdg">
                <span style="font-weight: bolder;">
                    YouTube
                </span>
            </a>
            or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/odoo"><span style="font-weight: bolder;">Facebook</span></a>.
        </p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Art Gallery</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="icon">🖼️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_position">35.87578125000001</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    </record>
</odoo>
