<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1>
            <u>Sports Facilities</u>
        </h1>
        <p><br /></p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>To illustrate how this setup works, this database is configured for a tennis and
                    padel club appropriately named <strong>"The Club."</strong> Despite being a
                    small business, they juggle a wide variety of daily operations, including:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Court Rentals:</strong> Managing bookings and scheduling for
                            players.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Gear &amp; Equipment:</strong> Handling basic sports gear and
                            inventory.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Cafeteria:</strong> Running their on-site food and beverage
                            services.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>To keep all these moving parts organized, The Club manages its entire business
                    seamlessly using <strong>Odoo</strong>. Below are the detailed workflows they
                    rely on every day.</p>
                <p>💡                    <strong>Quick Reminder:</strong> Odoo is fully customizable. You can easily
                    change the configuration settings and add a wide variety of free apps to your
                    database to tailor it perfectly to your specific business needs.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Activities</h1>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Members&#160;🧑‍🤝‍🧑</h2>
        <hr />
        <p>Easily manage club memberships that grant exclusive perks, such as year-round free court
            access and automated discounts at the bar.</p>
        <h3>Automated Membership Workflow</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Subscription-Driven Tiers:</strong> Define your membership packages as
                    products in the <strong>Subscription App</strong>. When a customer buys one,
                    Odoo automatically assigns a specific partner level directly to their customer
                    profile.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Smart Pricelists:</strong> Link these membership levels&#160;to custom
                    pricelists. The system will automatically apply preferential rates, bar
                    discounts, or free bookings whenever the member makes a purchase.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3>Total Flexibility</h3>
        <p>This architecture allows you to fully customize your club's offerings. You can easily
            scale your business by creating multiple membership tiers (e.g., Gold, Silver, Junior)
            with distinct pricing rules and unique perks.</p>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Gears&#160;🎾</h2>
        <hr />
        <p>The Club sells its sports gear seamlessly across two primary sales channels, ensuring a
            smooth shopping experience whether players are at home or at the courts.</p>
        <h3>Ecommerce</h3>
        <p>Perfect for members browsing and buying online.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Flexible Fulfillment:</strong> Customers can choose between convenient
                    paid home delivery or free in-club pickup.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Smart Upselling:</strong> The system automatically maximizes revenue. For
                    example, when a customer purchases a racket, the eShop strategically suggests
                    relevant add-ons like towels or balls before checkout.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3>On-Site "Shop" (Point of Sale)</h3>
        <p>Designed for immediate, on-the-spot purchases.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Instant Checkout:</strong> If a player needs gear right before a match or
                    wants to buy items directly at the club, staff can process the transaction
                    instantly using the dedicated Shop POS system.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Bar Management&#160;🍻</h2>
        <hr />
        <p>Keep your food and beverage service running efficiently by launching a second, dedicated
            Point of Sale (POS) session specifically for the bar.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Streamlined Workflows:</strong> Easily organize your menu into clear
                    product categories to create an intuitive, fast-paced checkout screen for your
                    bar staff.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Unified Management:</strong> Oversee bar-specific inventory, track
                    customer tabs, and seamlessly accept every payment method your venue offers from
                    one screen.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>💡                    <strong>Pro Tips for Advanced Operations:</strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Instant Member Scanning:</strong> Link unique barcodes to your
                            members' profiles. Staff can simply scan a physical or digital
                            membership card at the bar to instantly apply their preferential
                            discounts or tab the drinks to their account.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <strong>Full Restaurant Capabilities:</strong> Do you have a kitchen or
                            seated dining area? Map out a visual table layout right in the system
                            and integrate a digital <strong>Kitchen Display System (KDS)</strong> to
                            seamlessly coordinate orders between the floor and the kitchen.</p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Streamlined Team Scheduling:</strong> Keep your operations running like
                clockwork by managing all bartender and floor staff shifts directly within the
                integrated Planning app.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Court Booking&#160;📅</h2>
        <hr />
        <p>The Club utilizes two distinct appointment types to accommodate both private sessions and
            social play:</p>
        <h5>1 Court Booking</h5>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Duration:</strong> 60-minute playing sessions.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Frequency:</strong> Slots start every 30 minutes to maximize court
                    turnover and availability.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h5>2 Friday Night Free Play</h5>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Availability:</strong> Exclusive to Friday evenings.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Purpose:</strong> Designed for social play, allowing individual players
                    to sign up and join open, existing games.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3>Key System Insights</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Shareable Court Resources:</strong> Because the courts are configured as <strong>shareable
                    resources</strong>, multiple players can register for the same court
                    simultaneously. The system will continue to accept registrations for a slot as
                    long as there are open spots available on that court.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Internal Counter Bookings:</strong> For walk-ins or phone reservations,
                    counter employees can seamlessly book courts on behalf of members by navigating
                    to the <strong>Appointments
                        &gt; Resource Schedule</strong> menu.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h2>Manage your Website 🌐</h2>
        <hr />
        <p>Build an online presence that adapts perfectly to your clients' needs. Odoo gives you the
            flexibility to easily integrate internal policies, customize forms, showcase your latest
            products, manage the booking spaces and so much more—no coding required.</p>
        <p>Your website doesn't just sit there—it actively works to grow your business.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Automated Lead Generation:</strong> Every submission on your "Contact Us"
                    page instantly creates a brand-new opportunity in your <strong>CRM App</strong>.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>From the CRM app:</strong> Track client interactions in real time and use
                    the <strong>Sales
                        App</strong> to quickly shoot over tailored quotations for B2B leads or
                    custom customer requests, or use the <strong>Subscription App</strong> for new
                    members.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-fill-secondary">🎓 Website</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
        <h1>Do you want to go further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p>Once your core operations are running smoothly, consider expanding your toolset:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Accounting:</strong> Automatically log payments, close sessions, and
                    generate tax reports.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Payroll:</strong> Use this feature to handle <strong>employee
                    salaries and manage holiday requests</strong>.
            </li>
            <li>Explore marketing possibilities with Email Marketing, SMS Marketing, Social
                Marketing and Marketing Automation apps</li>
            <li>Manage all your events from the Events module</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p>
                    <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a
                        demo</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Sports Facilities</field>
        <field name="icon">🎾</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
        <field name="cover_image_position">67.60000000000008</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
