<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
  <template id="welcome_article_body">
    <h1 class="oe-hint">Interior Design</h1>
    <p>Welcome to the Odoo Interior Design package!</p>
    <p>This module offers all the essential tools an interior design studio needs to run daily operations in one place. It covers everything from generating leads through a professional website and managing client inquiries, to creating proposals, signing contracts digitally, executing design projects, and handling procurement and billing.</p>
    <p>Interior design firms can capture leads, schedule site visits, send detailed Quantities, collect legally binding digital signatures, manage design phases and timesheets, procure furniture and materials from vendors, and invoice clients on a milestone basis — all within a single connected system.</p>
    <p>It's a streamlined way to keep sales, design execution, procurement, and finance under control while delivering a smooth and professional experience to clients.</p>
    <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"/>
    <h1>
      <span class="h1-fs">Basics</span>
    </h1>
    <p>You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Website App</font>
      </strong> generates leads by showcasing your portfolio and allowing clients to reach out through a contact form.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The CRM App</font>
      </strong> captures and tracks potential clients, manages site visit scheduling, and monitors lead progress.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Sales App</font>
      </strong> creates and manages quotations and sales orders for design projects.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Project App</font>
      </strong> organizes and tracks design phases such as Mood Board, Visualization, and Handover.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Timesheets App</font>
      </strong> tracks hours spent on creative design work for accurate costing and billing.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Planning App</font>
      </strong> to assign the tasks and plan the work for the resources.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Purchase App</font>
      </strong> manages vendor orders and procures furniture, materials, and fittings for projects.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>
      <font style="color: rgb(198, 123, 165);">The Document App</font>
      </strong> will have the designs shared with the customers at a centralised place.
    </p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h1>Use Case</h1>
    <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with sample contacts, leads, products, and project templates.</p>
    <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to get an overview of the various processes you can quickly run with this package using Odoo.</p>
    <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete or modify demo data, and test everything out!</p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>
            <strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps &gt; Industries &gt; Upgrade your Interior Design package</strong> and check the related box.
          </p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h2>Managing Projects</h2>
    <h3>
      <strong>Client Contact (Website)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Attract new clients and generate leads directly from your Odoo-powered website.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Configure your website to display your portfolio, featured projects, and services so clients can get a clear picture of your style and capabilities.</li>
      <li>Use the <strong>Contact Us</strong> page to allow potential clients to send inquiries directly, which automatically flow into your CRM as leads.</li>
      <li>Showcase design categories (e.g., Residential, Commercial) to help clients identify the right service for their needs.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/websites/website.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Website</a>
    </p>
    <h3>
      <strong>Initial Inquiry (CRM App)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Manage incoming leads and schedule site visits efficiently using the CRM App.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the <strong>CRM App</strong> from your main dashboard. When a new client inquiry arrives from the website, it appears as a new Lead in your pipeline.</li>
      <li>Use Custom fields to the CRM Lead form, such as "Site Visit Date" field and "Property Type" field (e.g. Residential, Commercial).</li>
      <li>Track your lead pipeline stage by stage — from first contact through to budget discussion and proposal readiness.</li>
      <li>Log notes, schedule activities, and set reminders directly on each lead to ensure timely follow-up.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/crm.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 CRM</a>
    </p>
    <h3>
      <strong>Proposal &amp; Quotation (Sales App)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Convert qualified leads into professional proposals with a detailed Quantities.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the <strong>Sales App</strong> and convert the Lead into a Sales Order directly from the CRM.</li>
      <li>
          <p>List your offerings as products and use <strong>Sections</strong> (a standard Odoo feature) to organize the proposal clearly:</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Section 1: Design Fees</strong> (Service)
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Section 2: Material Costs</strong> (Goods)
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Section 3: Labour Charges</strong> (Service)
            </li>
          </ul>
      </li>
      <li>Email the Quotation directly from Odoo. The client receives a well-formatted PDF they can download or print for reference.</li>
      <li>Apply discounts, optional lines, or expiry dates to make your proposal more compelling and professional.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Sales</a>
    </p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>Use the Reporting in the Sales app to analyze trends such as higher order volumes, helping you plan better for peak times.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <h3>
      <strong>Design &amp; Contract Agreement (Document &amp; Sign App)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Replace the print-scan-email process with a fully digital contract workflow using the Sign App.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Upload your standard Design &amp; Design Agreement document.</li>
      <li>Add <strong>Signature</strong>, <strong>Date</strong>, and any other required fields to the document using the drag-and-drop editor.</li>
      <li>Send the contract to the client via email directly from Odoo.</li>
      <li>The client receives a link, opens it on any device (smartphone, tablet, or desktop), signs using their mouse or touchscreen, and clicks <strong>"Complete"</strong>.</li>
      <li>A legally binding, signed PDF is automatically saved to Odoo and linked to the client record — no manual filing required.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Document</a>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/sign.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Sign</a>
    </p>
    <h3>
      <strong>Project Execution (Project &amp; Timesheets &amp; Planning)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Once the Sales Order is confirmed, manage the full design execution within Odoo's Project, Planning and Timesheets apps.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Click the <strong>"Create Project"</strong> button on the confirmed Sales Order. The project is automatically linked to the sale for full traceability.</li>
      <li>
          <p>Use <strong>Project Tasks</strong> to structure and manage your workflow across design phases:</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Task 1:</strong> Mood Board &amp; Concept — Designers log their time here using Timesheets.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Task 2:</strong> 3D Visualization — Track progress and revision cycles.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Task 3:</strong> Furniture &amp; Materials Procurement — Coordinate purchasing alongside design execution.
            </li>
          </ul>
      </li>
      <li>Monitor task deadlines, assignees, and priorities from the Project Kanban or Gantt view.</li>
      <li>Use <strong>Timesheets</strong> to accurately capture hours against each task, enabling cost analysis and billing transparency.</li>
      <li>Use <strong>Planning</strong> to assign the site or task to the resources for the clear assignment and understanding.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/project.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Project</a>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/timesheets.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Timesheets</a>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/services/planning.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Planning</a>
    </p>
    <h3>
      <strong>Procurement (Purchase App)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Source and order furniture, materials, and fittings for your projects using the Purchase App.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open the <strong>Purchase App</strong> and create a new Purchase Order when materials or furniture are required for a project.</li>
      <li>
          <strong>Link the Purchase Order to the specific Project</strong> to ensure all procurement costs are directly tied to the corresponding revenue — giving you accurate project-level profitability.
      </li>
      <li>Select your preferred vendor based on pricing, lead time, or past performance.</li>
      <li>Send the <strong>Request for Quotation (RFQ)</strong> to the vendor via email or confirm it manually.</li>
      <li>When goods arrive, validate the incoming shipment using the <strong>Receipt</strong> smart button to update your inventory automatically.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/purchase.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Purchase</a>
    </p>
    <h3>
      <strong>Billing &amp; Handover (Invoicing App)</strong>
    </h3>
    <p>Invoice clients on a milestone basis and manage the final project handover smoothly.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
          <p>Use <strong>"Down Payment"</strong> invoices in Odoo to bill clients in stages. A typical milestone structure looks like:</p>
          <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>20%</strong> Advance upon contract signing
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>40%</strong> After materials are procured and delivered
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>40%</strong> Upon project completion and handover
            </li>
          </ul>
      </li>
      <li>The client receives each invoice via email with a <strong>"Pay Now"</strong> link (if you have Razorpay, PayPal, or another payment gateway configured). Once payment is received, the invoice is automatically marked as <strong>"Paid"</strong> in your system.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Invoicing</a>
    </p>
    <hr/>
    <h1>Do you want to go further?</h1>
    <p>Engage your clients using <strong>Email Marketing</strong>, <strong>SMS Marketing</strong>, and <strong>Marketing Automation</strong> to share new projects, promotions, and design tips.</p>
    <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
      <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
      <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
          <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
          <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary" rel="noreferrer">Schedule a demo</a>
          </p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <p>
      <br/>
    </p>
  </template>
  <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
    <field name="name">Interior Design</field>
    <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    <field name="icon">🛋️</field>
    <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_1"/>
    <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
    <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
    <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
  </record>
</odoo>
