<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <div data-oe-version="2.0">
            <span style="font-size: 36px;"><strong>Yoga &amp; Pilates Studio</strong></span>
        </div>
        <p>
            This setup is perfect for yoga and pilates studios offering <strong>group classes, private sessions, memberships, and wellbeing events</strong>. Odoo helps you streamline your
            <strong>class scheduling, memberships, instructor management, and customer engagement</strong> in one place.
        </p>
        <p>
            With the <strong>Appointments App</strong>, you can easily set up class planning, and with the <strong>Subscription App</strong>, you can manage recurring memberships like <em>Unlimited Monthly Access</em>. The
            <strong>Website App</strong> allows you to showcase your offers and let members book sessions seamlessly.
        </p>
        <p>Move with ease, book with clarity, and stay aligned with your practice—seamlessly renew and flow through your wellness journey. 🧘‍♀️</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2><strong>Basics</strong></h2>
        <p>You can access every installed app in your Odoo database from your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Appointment App</font></strong> schedules yoga and pilates classes for easy booking.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Subscription App</font></strong> manages memberships like The Flow Membership: Unlimited Yoga for one month.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Planning App</font></strong> assigns instructors based on expertise and availability.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Website App</font></strong> promotes your studio, explain your approach and enables online class bookings.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);"><strong>The Event App</strong> </font>organizes wellbeing session to engage your community
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Survey App</font></strong> collects feedback to ensure your wellbeing offerings align with your clients' expectations.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Employees App</font></strong> tracks schedules, roles, and expertise.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The CRM App</font></strong> converts leads into long-term members.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong><font style="color: rgb(113, 75, 103);">The Sales App</font></strong> simplifies membership purchases and upgrades.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true"><p>Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to turn your phone into a tool to manage your entire workflow.</p></div>
        </div>
        <h2><strong>Use Case</strong></h2>
        <p>By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.</p>
        <p>You should be able to execute the following flows to have an overview of various processes you can quickly execute with this package using Odoo.</p>
        <p>Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps, delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <div><strong>You didn't import demo data?</strong> You can still do it. Go to <strong>Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Yoga &amp; Pilates Studio Package </strong>and check the related box.</div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Defining your Yoga and Pilates offer</h3>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Create Your Products</strong><br />
                    Set up flexible options for your clients:
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li><p>Single class entries</p></li>
                    <li><p>5-class passes</p></li>
                    <li><p>Monthly unlimited memberships (subscription-based)</p></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Set Pricelists</strong><br />
                    Create a pricelist for each membership level to define what the client pays for each product; whether it’s full price, a discount, or free.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Assign Membership Levels Automatically</strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Set the product type to <strong>Service – Membership / Partnership</strong></p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Link the product to a <strong>Membership Level</strong></p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Link the <strong>Membership Level</strong> to a specific <strong>Pricelist</strong> (e.g., 100% discount on Pilates classes)<br />
                            → When a client buys the membership, they are automatically assigned the level and the related pricelist. When they return to the website, they’ll see the eligible classes at the correct price → such as €0 for Pilates if
                            that’s included in the plan.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Automate Renewals</strong><br />
                    For recurring plans like monthly unlimited passes, activate automatic renewal using the <strong>Subscriptions</strong> module.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Manage Cancellations</strong><br />
                    Set an end date for the subscription to close automatically, or let clients cancel their subscription anytime via their <strong>Odoo portal</strong>.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Use Loyalty Cards for Class Packs</strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Create a product (e.g., <strong>5-Class Yoga &amp; Pilates Card</strong>)</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>Go to <strong>Discount &amp; Loyalty</strong> and create a new <strong>Loyalty Cards</strong></p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>Set a <strong>Loyalty Rule</strong> to give 5 points when the product is purchased</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            Set a <strong>Reward</strong> where 1 point = 100% discount on a single class<br />
                            → As the client books classes, they can apply their points at checkout. Once all 5 points are used, the standard class price will automatically apply for future bookings.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Organize your class schedule &amp; assign instructors</h3>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>Create your Yoga and Pilates schedule:</strong></li>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        <p>Set up class types in the <strong>Appointment app</strong> (e.g., Vinyasa Yoga, Pilates Reformer).</p>
                    </li>
                    <li><p>Define the class schedule and assign specific resources (e.g., Garden room) with capacity limits.</p></li>
                    <li><p>Link each class to a product (e.g., "Yoga Single Entry" for a Morning Flow class).</p></li>
                </ol>
            </li>
        
            <li>
                <p><strong>Define instructor expertise: </strong>In the <strong>Work Information</strong> section of an employee, define employee's expertise by using the <strong>Role</strong> field.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Set up your yoga instructor planning: </strong>Create your class planning based on the studio’s operating hours.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Assign instructors automatically: </strong>With the <strong>auto-plan</strong> option, instructors will be assigned to classes based on their expertise and availability.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>Keep your community engaged with an interactive website</h3>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Present studio offerings</strong>: In the <strong>Website app</strong>, showcase your wellbeing approach and membership options.</p>
            </li>
            <li><strong>Create engaging events</strong>: Use the <strong>Events app</strong> to organize and promote special sessions like prenatal yoga.</li>
            <li><strong>Enable easy online bookings</strong>: Utilize <strong>eCommerce features</strong> to set up online booking and secure payment options for classes.</li>
            <li><strong>Track and engage members</strong>: In the <strong>CRM app</strong>, each time a new yogi books a session, a new opportunity will be created to track and engage with potential long-term clients.</li>
        </ol>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Go beyond a classic ecommerce page: Customize your pricing page to explain your different membership, make them attractive and link them to the right product.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Special sales for private sessions and customized client requests</h3>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Create private session products</strong>: Set up offerings like "Private Yoga Class – Group Session" for tailored experiences.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><strong>Customize the "Contact Us" form</strong>: Adjust on your Studio Website, the form to handle specific requests such as corporate events or wellbeing retreats.</p>
            </li>
            <li><strong>Generate customized quotations:</strong> Use the "Private Yoga Class – Group Session (15+ People) Quotation Template" to quickly create tailored proposals for private or group bookings based on client requests.</li>
        </ol>
        <h2><strong>Do you want to go further?</strong></h2>
        <p>Odoo offers endless customization possibilities for your Yoga &amp; Pilates Studio:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Integrate <strong>WhatsApp</strong> to send automatic reminders to members about their upcoming sessions.</li>
            <li>Set up a<strong> Point of Sale (POS)</strong> system to sell yoga mats, blocks, reformer socks, or a 5-class yoga package at your studio.</li>
            <li>Leverage <strong>Social Marketing</strong> to promote your classes, share testimonials, and attract new members online.</li>
            <li>Easily handle your <strong>accounting</strong> with the integrated <em>Accounting App</em>.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>These all go free in your current subscription; feel free to explore! 🙃</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false" data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus" class="btn btn-secondary">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br /></p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Yoga &amp;amp; Pilates Studio</field>
        <field name="icon">🧘‍♀️</field>
        <field name="cover_image_position">85.777</field>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
