<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <record id="knowledge_article_2" model="knowledge.article" context="{'studio': True}">
        <field name="body">&lt;h1 data-last-history-steps="2782856764780564"&gt;Talent Acquisition Agency&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1&gt;
                        &lt;hr&gt;&lt;div class="o_knowledge_behavior_anchor o_knowledge_behavior_type_toc" data-oe-protected="true"&gt;&lt;div class="o_knowledge_toc_content"&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="0" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0"&gt;Talent Acquisition Agency&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="1" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_0"&gt;Business Flows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="2" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1"&gt;Flow 1 : Website --&amp;gt; CRM --&amp;gt; Invoice&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="3" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2"&gt;Website : Create an Opportunity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="4" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2"&gt;CRM : Manage the business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="5" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2"&gt;Invoicing :&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="6" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_1"&gt;Flow 2 : Apply for a job and manage applicants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="7" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2"&gt;Website :&amp;nbsp;Apply for a job&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="#" data-oe-nodeid="8" class="oe_unremovable o_no_link_popover d-block o_knowledge_toc_link o_knowledge_toc_link_depth_2"&gt;Recruitment :&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p&gt;This setup is for Talent Acquisition Agency / Recruitment Agency / Staffing Agency. Those agencies work on two levels and with two different audiences. The customers will comes through their website, contact them and will be managed under market opportunities. The consultants or freelances will apply through the career pages and be managed by the company to match with the market opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The business is based on two flows :&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Managing customers, creation of a lead, qualification, agreement proposition and close on a sales order.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Managing applicants, application, interview, reserve, assignment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Business Flows&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Flow 1 : Website --&amp;gt; CRM --&amp;gt; Invoice&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Website : Create an Opportunity&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the Website, go to the Contact Us page and fill the contact form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This customized form will create an opportunity in the CRM, with the right information and in option, the jobs they're interested in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;CRM : Manage the business&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the CRM, an activity is created for the salesperson to contact the opportunity and qualify the lead (Studio : Automated Action)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Opportunity will be qualified and when the need is understood move the Opportunity to Proposition. It will automatically send an email with a Signature Request (Studio : Automated Action). That Signature Request hold an already signed, from Company, Service Agreement with default terms and filled values.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Service Agreement is signed, the opportunity is manually moved to "Agreement Signed", the Sales can open a discussion with the Recruitment team, and Opportunity will go, and stay, in Recruitment stage, for a while.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, when Recruitment team fullfill the job, the Sales create a quotation, based on the service agreement and the salary of the hired applicant. The quotation will lead to a Sales Order, and an Invoice will be sent to the customer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On payment, the Opportunity is moved to "Done".&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Invoicing :&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the database, you have two kinds of product.&lt;br&gt;Hired Candidate Plan is an undefined price product, the amount of money will be based on the applicant's salary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Other products can be services sold by the Recruitment agency for various missions and based on a standard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quote-Sales Order - Invoice flow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Flow 2 : Apply for a job and manage applicants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Website :&amp;nbsp;Apply for a job&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the Website, go to the Career&amp;nbsp;page and find the right job, from the "apply now" page, Applicants can submit their Resume or a LinkedIn profile link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This&amp;nbsp;form will create an applicant&amp;nbsp;in the Recruitment app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Recruitment :&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the applicant is created, an activity for a call will be automatically created and assigned to the Recruiter (Studio : Automated Action). The applicant will get a confirmation email from Recruitment Stage configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the qualification, applicant will be moved to third stage "First Interview", he'll receive a mail template with a link for an Interview (managed by Appointment) where he can select slots at his convenience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Interview, his skills will be assessed and added to his record. He'll be put in the Reserve stage. He can also receive the "Reserve" tag from any moment in the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Opportunities will open, and the applicant is matching requirements, you can link the Opportunity/ies to his Applicant record with a Many-to-Many object linked to the CRM (Studio : Customization of the Applicant view).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Linking Applicants to Opportunities, will allow you to filter data more efficiently and always work in the same pipe, for all missions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once assigned, Applicant can move to second interview and finally to Contract Signed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's always possible that after his mission, he'll come back to the reserve for another incoming opportunity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                </field>
        <field name="icon">📘</field>
        <field name="category">workspace</field>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="inherited_permission">write</field>
        <field name="name">Flows</field>
        <field name="sequence">4</field>
        <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
