<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <div>
            <span class="display-4-fs"><strong>Talent Acquisition Agency</strong></span>
        </div>
        <p>
            <font color="#343541">Welcome to the </font><font color="#343541" class="text-o-color-1"><strong>Talent Acquisition package.</strong></font>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            This comprehensive solution manages the entire talent acquisition lifecycle, streamlining two primary workflows.
            First, it handles <b>client relations</b>, from capturing requirements and managing quotations to sales orders and
            invoicing.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            Second, it optimizes the <b>headhunting process</b>, encompassing talent management, recruitment pipelines, and
            interview scheduling
        </p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"> <strong>Basics</strong> </span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify">You can access every installed App in your Odoo database on your main dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">CRM</font>:</b> Streamlines daily discussions with potential clients.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">Sales &amp; Invoicing App</font>:</b> Maintains a clear, automated record of all
                financial transactions.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">Website App:</font></b> Drives visibility about open positions
            </li>
            <li>
                <b><font class="text-o-color-1">Recruitment app:</font></b> Tracks all Talent and application of those within a clear pipeline
            </li>
            <li class="oe-nested" style="text-align: justify"><br /></li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true">
                <p style="text-align: justify">
                    Odoo is entirely integrated into an App. Download it to
                    <b>manage your entire business from your phone</b>.<s> <br /> </s>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs"> <strong>Activities</strong> </span> <br />
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            By uploading this module's demo data, your database has been filled with a few contacts.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            To get a rapid understanding of the processes this Odoo package offers, you can execute the following flows and
            configure the settings to suit your Coffee &amp; Tea Store.
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            Of course, this is just an overview of the features included in this package. Feel free to add new apps,
            delete/modify demo data, and test everything around!
        </p>
        <div
            data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Warning" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    You didn't import demo data? You can still do it. Go to Apps > Industries > Upgrade your Talent Acquisition
                    package and select the relevant checkbox
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <ul>
            <h3><br/></h3>
        </ul>
        <h3><span class="h2-fs">Manage your customer expectations 📜</span></h3>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            To ensure client expectations are consistently met, please follow this standardized workflow:
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify"><b>Opportunity Creation → Quotation/Sales Order → Invoicing.</b></p>
        <h4><u>1. Opportunity Management</u></h4>
        <p>
            Centralize all client interactions via the <b>CRM App</b>. Opportunities can be generated manually or automatically
            via the website’s "Contact Us" page. Use the unified Opportunity form to log meeting notes, schedule appointments,
            and track all relevant client data in one place.
        </p>
        <h4><u>2. Job Intake &amp; Integration</u></h4>
        <p>
            Initiate the recruitment process directly from the Opportunity by clicking the <b>"Create New Job"</b> button. This
            links the CRM to the <b>Recruitment App</b>.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Define Requirements:</b> Input essential details such as target profile, salary range, and job description.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Status Management:</b> New positions are created in <b>Draft</b> mode by default, preventing premature
                    publication or applications.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Activation:</b> Once the Sales Order is validated by the client, manually update the status to
                    <b>"Open"</b> to begin active sourcing.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h4><u>3. Sales Orders &amp; Financials</u></h4>
        <p>
            Generate quotations directly from the Opportunity. Add the relevant services and send the document to the client for
            <b>online signature</b>.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Flexible Billing:</b> Customize payment terms within the Sales Order based on the specific contract type.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Invoicing:</b> Once the Sales Order is signed, you can proceed to generate the invoice according to the agreed-upon terms.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    You can generate sales orders directly from a job position or manually link opportunities, sales orders, and
                    job positions. This flexibility ensures that regardless of your workflow or any unique exceptions, your data
                    remains accurately connected
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    Quotations and invoices are fully customizable, allowing you to include detailed information essential to
                    your business. Please refer to our documentation to create and tailor them to your specific requirements
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            <b><a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/sales/sales/sales_quotations.html" class="btn btn-secondary">Sales</a></b><br />
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify"><b>See It In Action!</b></p>
        <ol>
            <li class="oe-nested">
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Initiate:</b> Open the CRM app and create a new <b>Opportunity</b> for your client.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Generate Job:</b> From the Opportunity, select <b>Create New Job</b>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <b>Draft Sales Order:</b> Once the details are finalized, generate a <b>Quotation</b> from either
                            the Job Position or the Opportunity; both methods will link the records correctly.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Activate:</b> After the quotation is signed, update the Job Position status to <b>Open</b>.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Recruit:</b> Your recruitment team can now begin their search.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Bill:</b> Once the successful candidates are hired, proceed to <b>invoice</b> the Sales Order.</p>
                    </li>
                </ol>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <div>
                    Ensure service products are configured correctly to prevent physical inventory records from polluting the
                    database. Additionally, set the invoicing policy to <b>'Invoice on Delivered Quantity.'</b> For example, if
                    a Sales Order includes three recruitment hires, you should update the delivered quantity as each person is
                    hired to trigger individual automated invoices
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>Master the Art of Recruiting Top Talent 🎯</h3>
        <hr />
        <p>The Recruitment app provides a central hub for managing three core areas:</p>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><b>Job Positions:</b> Define your requirements, website listings, and necessary skills.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Talent Pools:</b> Maintain a database of qualified candidates ready for future roles.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Applicants:</b> Track active candidates through the recruitment pipeline for each job position.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <h4><u>1. Managing job positions</u></h4>
        <p>
            Job positions can be pre-populated through the CRM process. To maximize the app's effectiveness, it is important to
            understand these key settings:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Status Indicators:</b></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <b>Draft:</b> Used for job position awaiting final client approval. You cannot publish these or add
                            applicants yet.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Open:</b> Active roles that are ready for publication.</p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <b>Done:</b> Fulfilled or inactive job position; these are hidden from the website and automatically
                            filtered out of your main view.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Recruitment Type:</b> Distinguish between <b>Internal</b> (hiring for your own firm) and
                    <b>External</b> (hiring on behalf of a client).
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>External Settings:</b> For client-based job positions, you can designate the Customer and the
                    <b>Hiring Team Contact</b>. Members of the Hiring Team Contact will receive emails whenever new CVs are
                    submitted.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Website Integration:</b> Once a position is set to "Open," ensure the public listing is formatted
                    correctly for your website.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <strong>Target:</strong> It specifies the total number of positions for this job. Each successful hire
                    automatically reduces the remaining target count by one.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    To allow new talent to contact you even if they don't see any interesting open job positions, create an
                    'Open Application' job position
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div><strong>See It In Action!</strong></div>
        <div><br/></div>
        <ol>
            <li><b>Create</b> a new job position</li>
            <li><b>Configure</b> client details and grant portal access to the hiring team.</li>
            <li><b>Define</b> key skills required for the job</li>
            <li><b>Go Live</b> by switching the status to "Open."</li>
            <li><b>Publish</b> and customize the job description on the website</li>
            <li><b>Source</b> the perfect candidate from your existing talent pool or new applicants.</li>
        </ol>
        <h4><u>2. Managing Talent Pool</u></h4>
        <p>
            Talent Pools allow you to categorize and nurture potential candidates outside of specific vacancies. You can build
            these pools manually or by sourcing standout applicants from existing job positions. Once a candidate is in a pool,
            they become a "Talent" who can be easily matched to multiple job positions.
        </p>
        <div><strong>Key Functionality</strong></div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Seamless Application: </b>When a Talent is moved to a job position, the system creates a linked duplicate
                    for that specific role, ensuring organized record-keeping.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Smart Syncing:</b> Most data is shared between the Talent profile and their specific job applications.
                    For example, updating a candidate's <b>availability</b> in the Talent Pool automatically updates it across
                    all their active applications.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Independent Pipelines:</b> While core information is linked, each application follows its own unique
                    recruitment journey, allowing you to track progress for different roles simultaneously.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div><strong>See It In Action!</strong></div>
        <ol>
            <li>
                <p><b>Submit an Entry:</b> Go to the website and apply for the <b>Open Application</b> job.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Locate the Candidate:</b> Find the new application within that Job Position in the back-end.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Add to Pool:</b> Select the application and click the <b>Add to Pool</b> button.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Convert to Talent:</b> The candidate is now a "Talent." From their profile, you can now instantly apply
                    them to any other open positions.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    To proactively share talent with a potential customer, you can either send a profile directly or create a
                    dedicated 'Spontaneous Outreach' job position for each target client.
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h4><u>3. Managing Applicants</u></h4>
        <p><br/></p>
        <p>
            Our system offers a flexible architecture for managing candidates. You can source applicants through three primary
            channels:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>Talent Pool:</b> Promoting an existing talent record using the "Apply Job" button.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Website Integration:</b> Direct applications from your website’s job board.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Manual Entry:</b> Creating a record directly within the specific Job Position pipeline.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div><b>Key Configuration Rules</b></div>
        <div><br/></div>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Availability Tracking:</b> For every applicant, you can toggle their status (Available/Unavailable) or
                    set a specific "Available From" date.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>Document Management:</b></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <b>Internal Files:</b> Documents attached to the <b>Chatter</b> are private and for internal use
                            only.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p>
                            <b>Shared Files:</b> Documents uploaded to the <b>Shared CV</b> field are customer-facing. These are
                            the files sent via email to clients and published on the Customer Portal.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Automation:</b> Each pipeline stage can be configured to send automated emails to maintain consistent
                    communication with candidates.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Scheduling:</b> Ensure your Appointment app is synced to allow candidates to book meetings based on your
                    real-time availability.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <h3><b>Step-by-Step Recruitment Process</b></h3>
        <div><b>1. Creation &amp; Initial Contact</b></div>
        <p>
            Candidates enter the pipeline via the website, manual entry, or by being moved from the Talent pool into a specific
            job pipe.
        </p>
        <div><b>2. Screening &amp; Data Enrichment</b></div>
        <p>Review the CV to update the candidate’s skill set, experience, and any additional metadata required for the role.</p>
        <div
            data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Success" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    To streamline your workflow, enable <b>Resume Digitization (OCR)</b> in the Recruitment settings. This
                    AI-powered feature automatically scans uploaded CVs and extracts key candidate information, saving you
                    manual data entry time (requires available credits).
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div><b>3. Interview Scheduling</b></div>
        <p>
            When a candidate reaches the <b>First Interview</b> stage, the system automatically emails them a link to the
            recruiter’s calendar to book a meeting.
        </p>
        <div><strong>4. Contract Management</strong></div>
        <p>
            If a preliminary agreement is required, use the <b>Sign</b> application to generate and send standard contracts for
            rapid electronic signature.
        </p>
        <div><strong>5. Client Submission &amp; Portal Reporting</strong></div>
        <p>
            At any point, you can click <b>"Send CV"</b> to forward the documents in the "Shared CV" field to the hiring contact team.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Automatic Tracking:</b> This action automatically creates a line for this candidate into the
                    <b>"Reporting / Cv sent Report."</b>
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>The Customer Portal:</b> Clients can log into their Odoo portal to view their Sales Orders, Invoices, and
                    the <b>Applications</b> you have shared from the previous report.
                </p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p>
                    <b>Real-Time Synchronization:</b> This centralized view ensures that if you update a candidate’s
                    availability (e.g., they are hired elsewhere), that status updates instantly across all client portals where
                    that CV was shared.
                </p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div
            class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o-contenteditable-false lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3"
            data-oe-role="status">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal" data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info">💡</i>
            <div class="o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true w-100 px-3">
                <p>To preview the interface, please log in to your database using the following credentials:</p>
                <p><b>Login:</b> john.smith@fifth.example.com <b>Password:</b> john</p>
                <p>Once logged in, you will be able to view the application as published for this client.</p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div><strong>6. Managing Visibility</strong></div>
        <p>
            If you need to remove a candidate from a client’s view, you can use the <b>"Unpublish"</b> action directly from the
            Sent CV Report or all Talent and applicant views.
        </p>
        <p><br/></p>
        <h1 style="text-align: justify">Do you want to go further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <p style="text-align: justify"><strong>Accounting made easy 🧮</strong></p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">Use the <strong>Accounting</strong> app to easily handle:</p>
        <ul>
            <li style="text-align: justify">The customer reminders.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify">The vendor bills payment.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify">The Synchronization with the banks.</li>
            <li style="text-align: justify">The financial reporting.</li>
        </ul>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/finance/accounting.html">🎓 Accounting</a>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            <span class="h6-fs"><b>Centralize documents 📄</b></span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            <span class="h6-fs">Use the <b>Document</b> app to manage all your internal and external documents and use the Sign App for automated customer signatures</span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify">
            <span class="h6-fs">
                <b>
                    <a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/documents.html">🎓 Documents</a>
                    <span class="h6-fs">
                        <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/productivity/sign.html" class="btn btn-secondary">🎓 Sign</a>
                    </span>
                </b>
            </span>
        </p>
        <p style="text-align: justify"><br /></p>
        <div
            data-oe-role="status"
            class="o_editor_banner lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3 o-contenteditable-false"
            data-oe-protected="true">
            <i data-oe-aria-label="Banner Info" class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">🚀</i>
            <div class="w-100 ms-3 o_editor_banner_content o-contenteditable-true" data-oe-protected="false">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or go even further?</p>
                <p><a class="btn btn-secondary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Schedule a demo</a></p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p><br/></p>
        <p><br/></p>
    </template>

    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Talent Acquisition</field>
        <field name="icon">📘</field>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_11"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body">
            <![CDATA[]]>
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
