<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<odoo>
    <template id="welcome_article_body">
        <h1 class="oe-hint" data-oe-version="1.1">
            <span class="display-4-fs">
                <strong>Wedding Planner</strong>
            </span>
            <br />
        </h1>
        <p>An ideal pre-configured module for your Wedding Planner needs in Odoo, from lead management to project planning and budgeting.</p>
        <div data-embedded="tableOfContent"></div>
        <h2>
            <span class="h1-fs">Basics</span>
        </h2>
        <hr />
        <p>Your Odoo Wedding Planner Package helps you streamline your operations by:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Using the <strong>CRM</strong> to manage opportunities</li>
            <li>Using the <strong>Projects app</strong> to coordinate on to-do's, vendors, track tasks</li>
            <li>The Social <strong>Marketing app</strong> helps you keep in touch with your community, and find new leads</li>
            <li>The <strong>Sign app </strong>helps you manage agreements between you and your customers</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-warning pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">⚠️</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>If you want to easily discover every features of this package, try downloading the Demo Data.</p>
                <p>You can still do it by upgrading your package in Apps.</p>
                <p>Just be careful, once demo data are uploaded, it cannot be easily deleted. But you can restart a fresh database on <a href="http://Odoo.com/trial">Odoo.com/trial</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>🚀 Manage your opportunities and prospective customers</h3>
        <p>
        Our CRM is designed to streamline your sales process, ensuring seamless management of leads, opportunities, and client interactions. With intuitive tools and automation, you can stay organized, improve efficiency, and close deals
        faster.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Opportunity Management: </strong>Track every stage of your sales process, from initial contact to closing the deal. Log communications, monitor progress, and schedule follow-ups to ensure no opportunity falls through the
        cracks.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Lead Categorization: </strong>Easily segment and organize your leads with custom tags. This allows for better targeting, prioritization, and personalized outreach, helping you focus on the most promising prospects.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Follow-Up with your opportunities: </strong>Never miss a follow-up again. Create and assign tasks to team members, set reminders, and track progress to maintain consistent engagement with your leads.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Schedule meetings: </strong>Simplify your calendar through the calendar smart button in the opportunity.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Quotation Management: </strong>Create professional quotations and share them online in just a few clicks. Track their status, make revisions, and secure approvals efficiently to speed up the sales cycle.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Contract &amp; Agreement Handling: </strong>Send, manage, and store contracts or formal agreements within the CRM. Ensure quick approvals, track signatures, and maintain a clear record of all client commitments.</p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <ul>
                    <li>If Studio is enabled (not included), it becomes possible to set up automations that save time</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h3>📊 From sales quotation to project management</h3>
        <p>Seamlessly transition from sales to project execution with an integrated workflow. Our system ensures that your sales orders automatically transform into structured projects, saving time and improving efficiency.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Sales Order Templates: </strong>Load up predefined sales order templates that include structured sections, products, and essential details. Add extra notes for descriptions and easily include terms &amp; conditions to ensure
        clarity in every transaction.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Automated Project Creation: </strong>When a sales order includes a specific service—such as "MyWeddingCompany Service"—a corresponding project can automatically be generated based on the predefined product template. This
        eliminates manual setup and ensures consistency in project execution.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Task &amp; Subtask Management: </strong>Each project consists of structured tasks essential for preparation, such as wedding planning steps. Tasks can be further broken down into multiple subtasks, each with a detailed view to
        track progress effectively.
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Comprehensive Tracking &amp; Insights: </strong>Monitor key project metrics effortlessly. Use the dashboard button within the kanban view to track timesheets, vendor bills, milestones, and other critical indicators, ensuring smooth
        project management from start to finish.
        </p>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <ul>
                    <li>Add costs to your products and display your margins in the settings app to get an overview of your net profits per sale</li>
                    <li>Make your quotations yours by using the quotation builder!</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <a href="https://www.odoo.com/documentation/latest/applications/inventory_and_mrp/inventory.html" class="btn btn-outline-primary">🎓 Inventory</a>
        </p>
        <h3>📝 Streamline Vendor Quotations &amp; Customer Offers</h3>
        <p>Optimize your procurement process by efficiently managing vendor quotations and presenting the best options to your customers.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Multi-Vendor Quotation Requests: </strong>Easily request quotations from multiple vendors and receive competitive offers for your products or services.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Side-by-Side Comparison: </strong>Compare vendor quotations directly using the <strong>"Compare Product Lines"</strong> feature to make informed purchasing decisions.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Seamless Purchase Confirmation: </strong>Confirm purchases with selected vendors and coordinate deliveries effortlessly to ensure smooth operations.</p>
        <p>
            <strong>Vendor Pricing &amp; Agreements: </strong>Leverage vendor price lists or pre-negotiated agreements when applicable, ensuring cost efficiency and consistency.</p>
        <p>
            <img class="img-fluid" src="wedding_planner/static/src/binary/ir_attachment/1.png" />
        </p>
        <p>
            <strong>Project integration </strong>: Requests for Quotations (RFQs) or vendor orders can be created directly from your customer projects.</p>
        <h3>🧶 Social Media Marketing</h3>
        <p>Manage your social media presence seamlessly across multiple platforms from a single, centralized dashboard.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Plan, schedule, and publish posts</strong> across all major social media channels.</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Track engagement</strong>, reach, and performance metrics with real-time analytics.</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Manage multi-platform campaigns</strong> effortlessly without switching between accounts.</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Collaborate with your team</strong> to streamline content creation and approvals.</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>✍️ Manage agreements through the Sign app</h3>
        <p>Need to work with contracts, agreements, or other documents that need signing?</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Use the Sign app, upload your contract templates, and send them to your leads or customers in just a few clicks!</li>
            <li>The Sign app is integrated in most other apps, from CRM, to Sales, to Projects.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-success pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">✅</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>
                    <strong>
                        <span class="h2-fs">Tips for Success</span>
                    </strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Make your quotations personal by adding beautiful cover and footer pages</li>
                    <li>Create a beautiful website that shows off some of the events you've organized</li>
                    <li>Leverage social media effectively, and obtain new leads</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
        </div>
        <h1>Do You Want to Go Further?</h1>
        <hr />
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Use the Appointments App</strong> to allow customers to book consultations with you</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Use the Attendance App</strong> to track when guests arrive</li>
            <li>
                <strong>Create a Website </strong>and link the contact form to your CRM</li>
            <li>Manage your <strong>Calendar </strong>within Odoo to see everything in one place</li>
            <li>Use the <strong>Accounting App </strong>for financial reporting, tax reports, making and receiving payments, and so on.</li>
        </ul>
        <div class="o_editor_banner user-select-none o_not_editable lh-1 d-flex align-items-center alert alert-info pb-0 pt-3">
            <i class="o_editor_banner_icon mb-3 fst-normal">💡</i>
            <div class="w-100 px-3">
                <p>Would you like to discuss your Odoo setup with us or explore more features?</p>
                <p>
                    <a class="btn btn-primary" href="https://www.odoo.com/contactus">Reach us</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </div>
        <p>
            <br />
        </p>
    </template>
    <record id="welcome_article" model="knowledge.article">
        <field name="name">Wedding Planner</field>
        <field name="icon">👰</field>
        <field name="is_locked" eval="True"/>
        <field name="cover_image_id" ref="knowledge_cover_10"/>
        <field name="internal_permission">write</field>
        <field name="is_article_visible_by_everyone" eval="True"/>
        <field name="body"><![CDATA[]]></field>
    </record>
</odoo>
